<?xml version="1.0" encoding="euc-kr" ?>
<monster_talk_table>
	<poring>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Not bad, what else ya got?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Um, is that it, I was hoping for more...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	That was tasty, got any more?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Can I have some more please?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ooh! More please! I liked that very much.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Do I get to have the eatable things we find?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ooh, can I eat the next thing that drops?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm eat all the jellopies for myself!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Oh my gosh, I hope you don't kill anyone I know.	</hunting>
			<danger>	If you die, what do you drop?	</danger>
			<danger>	I'll be alright for a bit, feed yourself and heal up!	</danger>
			<danger>	I think you need the food more then I do...	</danger>
			<danger>	I was saving this apple for later, but you look like you need it more.	</danger>
			<danger>	If I heal you, will you feed me after?	</danger>
			<danger>	I think you should heal yourself, you don't look too good.	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't blame me, I'm a poring! Like I'd have stood a better chance.	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey um, does this mean no more food?	</dead>
			<dead>	...*poke*... *poke*... ... ... ... *poke* ... aw man... now who's gonna feed me?	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, get up, this isn't the best place to nap... *poke*... um, you ok?	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, why aren't you moving anymore? Get up!	</dead>
			<stand>	Hey um, before we go, can you feed me?	</stand>
			<stand>	I don't want to be annoying, but... I'm a little hungry...	</stand>
			<stand>	You know, I haven't been fed for a while...	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, where are we going, is there food there?	</stand>
			<stand>	If you use me as a chair, will you feed me?	</stand>
			<stand>	All the other pets are eating now...	</stand>
			<stand>	Ooh, I'm so hungry...	</stand>
			<stand>	Wait, what about me? I'm still hungry!	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey! Welcome back, did you break me something to eat?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey there you are, I've been starving!	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh, you're back, yay, now I can get fed. ^^	</connect>
			<connect>	Ooh Ooh, do I smell something, did you bring me food?	</connect>
			<connect>	FEED ME FEED ME~~!	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome back! Now feed me! You haven't fed me for... oh no, I've forgotten it's been so long!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Awesome, good job, do I get a treat?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yay, *hugs* now we can eat!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Sweet!... hmm, speaking of which, where's the food?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey, when do I get to fight and level too?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Okay, you got your level, do I get to eat now?	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Oh yum~ . . . where's the rest?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yum~ that was good... more please!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yuck, don't you check these things before you buy them? That was awful.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmm, that was pretty good, almost got me full.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*BuUUuUURP*... tasty...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Are you sure the monsters here drop eatable things?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can I go scrounging for food... just a snack...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey, if I distract it, can I get some food later on?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey, if a poring gets what drops, you're not really gonna kill it... are you?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Don't you dare die on me... I haven't been fed yet!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, heal up silly, I'm not gonna do it.	</danger>
			<danger>	If you die, can I search you for food?	</danger>
			<danger>	If you die, does that mean the loot is mine to eat?	</danger>
			<danger>	Please don't get killed, I don't know where to get food around here.	</danger>
			<dead>	Wow, you died... so now what?	</dead>
			<dead>	Now why'd you go and do that? Now what am I gonna eat?	</dead>
			<dead>	Er... *poke*... *poke*... ... ... ... *poke*	</dead>
			<dead>	I see dead people...or... well you at least.	</dead>
			<dead>	NOO you forgot to feed me, now what will I do!?	</dead>
			<stand>	I really like traveling with you, especially when we eat. ^^	</stand>
			<stand>	I think we should go find some more food, what do you think?	</stand>
			<stand>	Aren't I cute?	</stand>
			<stand>	Sit a little longer with me? I still need more time to rest.	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, can we go lookin' for jellopies now?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey are we going to go hunting for jellopies today?	</connect>
			<connect>	Yay, you're back, can we get some grub?	</connect>
			<connect>	I feel like lootin' today, let's find some good stuff.	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh thank goodness you're back, I thought you might have forgotten me.	</connect>
			<connect>	Someone tried taking me while you were gone! Please don't leave me again.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Leveled again? You know, I'm startin' to enjoy this.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yay, I'd give you a high five, but I kinda don't have any hands...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Alright! Can we celebrate with some food?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yeah! I think this means you should get us some fried jellopy.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	ALL YOUR JELLOPY ARE BELONG TO ME... er... I mean us...^^	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Ooh yum~ that was nice, thank you.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*munch* *munch* yummy, thank you!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Wow, that almost made me full!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*burp* excuse me ^^	</feeding>
			<feeding>	yummy yummy in my tummy	</feeding>
			<hunting>	HA! Take that you evil thing!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope one day I can help you more, you're my best bud.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Wow, what a shot, can you teach me that?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Is it bad when they hit you so much?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You da'man!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ha ha! You are the best!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh please don't die, fly wing if you have to!	</danger>
			<danger>	Don't push it, you're not invincible, heal up.	</danger>
			<danger>	Where's my apple? Please use it, heal yourself, don't die.	</danger>
			<danger>	I would protect you if I could, but... I don't think I'd stand a chance.	</danger>
			<danger>	Are you alright?? Don't get hurt anymore!	</danger>
			<dead>	Is there anything I can do...? You don't look too good.	</dead>
			<dead>	You did your best, but... let's not do that again, ok?	</dead>
			<dead>	Stop lying there, get up, it's not over!	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, I found some loot... I promise to give it to you if you get up.	</dead>
			<dead>	You aren't moving... *cry* Am I all alone..?	</dead>
			<stand>	A-a-and we're off, where are we goin' now? ^^	</stand>
			<stand>	Wow, we leaving already? You're on the move!	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, how come I don't have any hands...?	</stand>
			<stand>	You like me more then the other porings, don't you?	</stand>
			<stand>	I think I picked up a ... oh never mind, I must have missed it...	</stand>
			<stand>	I think I had an accident, let's leave quick.	</stand>
			<connect>	*wraps around your leg* yay you're back.	</connect>
			<connect>	Yay! More good food and traveling!	</connect>
			<connect>	Why did you leave for so long? I'm ready, let's go!	</connect>
			<connect>	All hail my master has returned!	</connect>
			<connect>	So, where's that fried jellopy you promised me before?	</connect>
			<connect>	Someone asked me about you while you were gone... hmm, who was it...	</connect>
			<levelup>	Hurrah hurrah, sis boom bah.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yay, now we can go eat, right?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good job! When do I get to level?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Wow! Wings! Just like an Angelring! Teach me how to do that please?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Booya! Looks like we're moving up!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Many thanks, this is really tasty!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Bananas again? With that many in me, I'd probably turn so yellow, and become a Drops?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	For the first time in my life... I'm full. You complete me.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I think I'm gonna throw up.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Wahh.. too much food!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	*chomp*chomp*chomp* Sorry, I can't find my apple to give you.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Master, how come you never buy ME weapons or armor. I can fight too or do you not care about me?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Stop showing off... just kill it.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yes, you own dude!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can't we take a nap? I just ate!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh!! Please someone help my master!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Erk! Are you okay?	</danger>
			<danger>	What did I tell you... wearing that cape does not make you Superman!	</danger>
			<danger>	Don't die! Who's gonna be there for my Poring Academy Graduation?	</danger>
			<danger>	That looks like it hurt.	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh no, the world may never know the joy that is you...	</dead>
			<dead>	Oh no!! Player down! Player down! CHHHHRRRRISSSSSTTTYY!!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Where will I go?! What will I do?!	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm sorry GOD-POING I promise not to loot again!! Please revive him T_T	</dead>
			<dead>	Uh, can you say...oops....?	</dead>
			<dead>	Man... it's so embarrassing when you die...	</dead>
			<stand>	I know it's embarrassing, but I love you, you know that? I want the whole world to know!	</stand>
			<stand>	What came first, the jellopy or the poring... hmm...	</stand>
			<stand>	Go get 'em, tiger. *Grrr*	</stand>
			<stand>	Ooh, are we gonna go tame me a girlfriend now?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, can we go to Morroc? I haven't visited my cousin in ages!	</stand>
			<stand>	I have to use the potty...	</stand>
			<connect>	Yawn...so early! Don't you have any homework to do? Let me sleep in a little!	</connect>
			<connect>	You're back! Yay! ^_^	</connect>
			<connect>	Yay! Now we can go leveling again. ^^	</connect>
			<connect>	Weee!! Lets go do a Bapho hunt!	</connect>
			<connect>	I am not hungry! ^__^ But get some food just in case I want a snack ^_~	</connect>
			<levelup>	You are the best, there is no doubt...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	So strooong! My hero!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	One step closer to server domination, muahaha.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yay!! You did it! Woohoo!! Yippee!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Do your victory dance!	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Argh Noo!! I do not want to die from over eating!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmnff.. n-no more food please, I beg you!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Fattening me up for slaughter, eh? I'm watching you....	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I don't feel so good...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	NOOOO! NO MORE! I'LL EXPLODE!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Stop feeding me!!!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	*burp* ... if we do not rest I think I'm going to be sick	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Maaaster~, can we slow down? I'm feeling a lil' sick..	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Oh no, I think I'm going to...throw up....WATCH YOUR FEET!!.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	OMG so much loot... but... I can't take it, I'm so full *sob*	</hunting>
			<danger>	I'd love it if I lost weight as fast as you lose hit points...	</danger>
			<danger>	See, that's what happens when you overfeed me! It's bad karma!	</danger>
			<danger>	I told you to stay away from those mace-wielding priests.	</danger>
			<danger>	Here take this red pot I looted!	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh, this it is a good method to slim!	</dead>
			<dead>	Next time, if you're going to need to heal	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm sure you almost had it.. I mean, all those red numbers above your head meant we were winning right?	</dead>
			<dead>	I told you , I told you , I told you!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Good, we can rest now.	</dead>
			<stand>	You know a good dietitian?	</stand>
			<stand>	Maybe I should go see a doctor.. I feel sick..	</stand>
			<stand>	Easy there.	</stand>
			<stand>	You like standing don't you?	</stand>
			<connect>	Heal me. Free stuff. Tank me. Loot him. Ks him. .....sorry, I've been hanging around novices while you were away.	</connect>
			<connect>	hears, many people have confused me with a savage bebe... I need to slim NOW!!	</connect>
			<connect>	Great, you're back.. and I'd bet you want to FEED ME MORE, HUH!?	</connect>
			<connect>	Real life getting to be boring again?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello! Do I start my diet today?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Very well ... you will not have a skill to do slim, maybe?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	There, you leveled, can we please nap now? I'm stuffed!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're leveling up too fast... you're a bot, aren't you!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	OMG you wouldn't believe it, I actually went out on a date with a girl poring! You want to meet her?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Another level? Can we go home now? I need rest.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</poring>
	<drops>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	You have a great sense of time, I'm hungry!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey, do you hear that? My tummy's grumbling.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Can I please have some more?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey, feed me before I get angry, you don't want to see me angry...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Man, you hunt SOO slow... speed it up, then feed me.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Jeez, can't you kill faster?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Okay, we'll make it even, we'll split the items 30/70, and you get the 30...	</hunting>
			<danger>	I would be helping you right now, I'm just so danged hungry...	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, look at that your life is in the red, that's good right?	</danger>
			<dead>	Argh! Stand up! Who going to feed me now?!	</dead>
			<dead>	Sleeping on the job? Not a good idea...WAKEY WAKEY!	</dead>
			<stand>	How about moving a lil'bit? Sport is good for you!	</stand>
			<stand>	Ahhh I'm going to die of starvation!!	</stand>
			<connect>	It's about time! I'm starving here!	</connect>
			<connect>	G'Day! I heard that some other Drops got some pancakes... *hint hint*	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yeah, whatever...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	FOOOD!!	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Ehm...that's all? . . . thanks. . . . . .	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*gobble*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	At last!! You're finally treating me like a real drop!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	STOP HUNTING!! I'm hungry!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Is sticky mucus edible?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can I have some of those shiny objects?	</hunting>
			<danger>	You look hurt, are you?	</danger>
			<danger>	SOMEONE PLEASE... DON'T LET MY MASTER DIE!!! *cries*	</danger>
			<danger>	Don't die! No more yummy for my tummy!	</danger>
			<dead>	Not again... You need some serious training... or a mental check.	</dead>
			<dead>	Aww...	</dead>
			<dead>	Who's going to feed me if you're sleeping?... you are sleeping aren't you... *poke* aren't you....?	</dead>
			<stand>	Soooooooo... what did you eat today? Really? I'll tell you what I ate? NOTHING! I'm hungryyyyyy...	</stand>
			<stand>	We should travel the world, and find all kinds of rare things!... to eat	</stand>
			<stand>	Shouldn't you be finding me something to eat?	</stand>
			<connect>	Yeah! I thought you'd never come back! Welcome back!	</connect>
			<connect>	Heya-heya! Do I waited for you to eat, let's dine!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hiya! Where we off to today?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Good! You must be stronger to get money!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Wooopeee!! Does this mean I get more food?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yay!... food...I mean, yay you leveled!	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	You may not like the herbs, but I love 'em!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey, wow! Zingy! Thanks!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Weeeeeee this is fun! fun! fun!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Kill it! Kill it! DIE DIE DIE	</hunting>
			<danger>	Uh-oh...	</danger>
			<danger>	Uh Oh! You MIGHT want to check your health, because it isn't going up!	</danger>
			<dead>	It's not your fault, it just happens once in a time...	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, are you ok? You don't look too good.	</dead>
			<stand>	can I sit? Or am I always in this position?	</stand>
			<stand>	Man are you gonna do something or should I go?	</stand>
			<connect>	Ohayo!	</connect>
			<connect>	Yes!!!! You are finally back, my prayers were heard!	</connect>
			<levelup>	*dances* Wheeeeee!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	A-M-A-Z-I-N-G!!!!!!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Thank you, but I don't need it right now...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you its good, but...STOP FEEDING ME, IM FULL!!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm not hungry. I ate a big lunch!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Oooooohhh.. I'm too full to eat the stuff on the ground.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Whoa! Food just laying there! Coolies!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey! All the these monsters...you love me best, right?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Ok, Just calm, don't mind the blood running down from your head!!	</danger>
			<dead>	Tsk.tsk.tsk. I'll be waiting at the respawn point.	</dead>
			<dead>	OMG, that's a long walk, well at least I can go with you...	</dead>
			<dead>	Well, lets start walking, its a long way up there-__-''	</dead>
			<dead>	See! You couldn't kill it, I told you didn't I. Oh well, I'm full anyways.	</dead>
			<stand>	Dinner today was fine...but a lil bit too much ^^ next time don't feed me so much, but thanks!	</stand>
			<stand>	la la la la la..	</stand>
			<connect>	Your back! Woooohoo!!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey, there you are! I missed you!	</connect>
			<levelup>	That's the spirit! /no1	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Level Up, SCORE for the team!	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	You can put your food in your *pipe*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	What are you trying to do, give me food poisoning?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	No items for me today. I can't move, uff.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*burp* Do I have to fetch the items?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Blood...red blood...remembers me on carrots *urks*	</danger>
			<danger>	You gonna dieee!! AAaaahhh your going to diee!!	</danger>
			<dead>	Ehm...got enough sleep? stand up man! your so pruditly ...	</dead>
			<dead>	Hmm. You're dead. *shakes head*	</dead>
			<stand>	Im siiiiinging in the rain... *sing*	</stand>
			<stand>	When I grow up, I wanna be Santa! Or at least have a Santa hat!	</stand>
			<connect>	Where were you? toilet? =)	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome back! Did you miss me?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Nice! just don't feed me -.-	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! *burp*	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</drops>
	<poporing>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Thanks...I don't feel so good, maybe it was the apple you fed me.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you, I kept thinking I was lime Jell-O.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks, I was so hungry. I hardly could skip.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	That item on the ground looks mighty tasty!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Go for it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Uh... sorry but your items mysteriously disappeared	</hunting>
			<danger>	Is it just me or do I smell death?	</danger>
			<danger>	Well IF you die, do u think I can eat your items?	</danger>
			<danger>	Easy does it, it's getting too hot.	</danger>
			<dead>	This is no time to sleep, I need food!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	The food, it will rot.	</dead>
			<dead>	Are you sleeping because I think you forgot to do something, involving ME.	</dead>
			<stand>	I sort of need food right about now...	</stand>
			<stand>	Well doesn't standing take energy? I think we better eat.	</stand>
			<stand>	When did you feed me the last time? I can't remember.	</stand>
			<connect>	You come timely, it's time to eat.	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello there, bring any food with you?	</connect>
			<connect>	You are the best owner in the world... so don't you think a pet that is owned by the best owner should get breakfast?	</connect>
			<levelup>	No time to celebrate, I NEED FOOD!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Booya! well that was hard work lets go eat!	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Food.....food....food	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Did you know that a growing pet like me, needs more food?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	That Lunatic dropped a great looking carrot!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	When you kill that thing can we go eat?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Never mind you eating that! What about me!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Remember when its red it means you're going to die and you need to feed me.	</danger>
			<dead>	I'll just grab some food from your pocket....	</dead>
			<dead>	So since your napping think we can go get a burger after you wake up? You are waking up right?	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm so hungry I could eat at Arbys!	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you think I look better than the Porings?	</stand>
			<stand>	Since were standing here doing nothing and smelling delicious food.. do you think we can go get some of that delicious food?	</stand>
			<connect>	I got a yearning' for some food!	</connect>
			<connect>	A good breakfast consist of a lot of food and feeding your pet.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Does that big light above you mean dinner time?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Did you know that energy comes from food? well I didn't know that, lets go see if that's true.	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Tastes like chicken.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ah, what a refreshment. ^_^	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Tummy status, normal. Food incoming, normal. All systems check lets go!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	That lunatic looks good for tonight's BBQ!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I must say that was one of the best battles you had! You were like BOOM and then BAM and then WOOP POW!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	It's only a flesh wound, just do what I do, EAT!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Excuse me Mr. Person who I don't know could you share you all so great healing powers with my unfortunate friend over there?	</danger>
			<dead>	You slept in too long!	</dead>
			<dead>	Stand up please, the ground is dirty!	</dead>
			<dead>	Being alive is the BESTEST!!! Don't you think so *poke* uh oh	</dead>
			<stand>	Watcha' lookin' at?	</stand>
			<stand>	Am I a good Poporing?	</stand>
			<stand>	On my birthday can I have a car? I think I can drive without hands.	</stand>
			<connect>	Bing, Bong, Bing, Bong, look I think getting late I think you should go....... JUST KIDDING ^_^	</connect>
			<connect>	I'm ready, let's go!	</connect>
			<levelup>	How many levels until level 99?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	BOOYA Grandma... er.... I mean owner =P	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Agghhhh heart burn!!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Your just like that cat who always came back but instead you have food.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	*weez* *cough* you look mighty tired won't you *puff* *weez* rest...?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Are you about to fall to be funny? because I think you should fall down on a bed.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Just attack, I'll lay a false scent.	</hunting>
			<danger>	You got any antacids?	</danger>
			<danger>	No, I don't like red. I prefer green, just take care!	</danger>
			<danger>	So as I was saying there was the bee and... I see your going to sleep from my story oh wait that red thing means...	</danger>
			<dead>	You have gas too? Yours must be worse!	</dead>
			<dead>	Doctor, is the heart suppose to move?	</dead>
			<stand>	I shouldn't have eaten that unripe apple...	</stand>
			<stand>	Food? Did you know that you start losing levels when you eat too much? ( hehe I don't think he's going to know that ^_^ )	</stand>
			<stand>	A little break is always good.	</stand>
			<connect>	No more pie...maybe one more piece...Oh welcome back!	</connect>
			<connect>	Breakfast? It's only the morning, don't you have breakfast in like another 10 hours or so?	</connect>
			<levelup>	I would blow a whistle, but I have no hands!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Can I choose what to do? Yay! Lets go eat some tofu turkey!!	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	If you feed me at this rate, you'll turn me into a Big Foot!!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Do you want me to grow bigger than you? Well sorry but instead of going up, for some reason it's going sideways.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Stop it! Soon I can't skip anymore, you'll have to roll me!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I'm going to hurl all this food on the ground is making me hungry!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	AHHH! Attack that steak!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Not that fast, I can't keep pace.	</hunting>
			<danger>	I feel bloated what about you?	</danger>
			<danger>	Blood? Ketchup? Fries? No not more food!	</danger>
			<danger>	At least we're now at the same eye-level.	</danger>
			<dead>	You have red stuff coming out of your back.	</dead>
			<dead>	Well Let's see, me over filling with food, plus you closing your eyes, equals me not eating anymore ^_^	</dead>
			<stand>	While we're here lets make a Hammock!	</stand>
			<stand>	I take a nap. Could you give me my green Pajama?	</stand>
			<stand>	Well tell me when your going to move, I'm just going to go there and sit my little plump body right there.	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back, I think I lost weight while you were gone!	</connect>
			<connect>	Well lets go! Food? What's Food?	</connect>
			<connect>	I've waited until I was green. At last! ^_^	</connect>
			<levelup>	Nice One!!! Can you buy me a Stairmaster?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congratulations, you're in good form!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well since you achieved something. A diet is what I think I should achieve.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</poporing>
	<lunatic>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	*rwar* I want more! Give me more, I'm really hungry!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmm, more more more! I'm so hungry!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Ugh, why fight? feed me please!.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Bunny to Rabbit, target sighted, carrots are good to eat, I repeat, carrots are good to eat.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey, I'm gonna go look around for some carrots, I'm hungry..	</hunting>
			<danger>	Don't complain to me about being hurt, I'm starving!!	</danger>
			<danger>	If you die, would you mind me checking your corpse for carrots?.	</danger>
			<danger>	Eep! Run away! Run away! Keep running!	</danger>
			<dead>	HA! You're dead... can I go now?	</dead>
			<dead>	Does this mean I'm free to go now?	</dead>
			<dead>	... I'm... so hungry... but, I haven't been fed... in so long... must... go on....	</dead>
			<dead>	Mind if I check your bag for some carrots?... wait, you're dead,	</dead>
			<dead>	Tea?... no, you're dead, what're you going to do with tea... ha!	</dead>
			<stand>	Hey while you're up, get me some food will you?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, I'm hungry are we going to find me some food?	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm hungry!! I want food!! *rwar*	</stand>
			<connect>	Oh my gosh, where have you been I'm so hungry!	</connect>
			<connect>	Feed me or you'll find some nice pebbles in your shoes...	</connect>
			<connect>	.... you...forgot ...to ...FEED ME!! ...Feed me, feed me, feed me, feed me!	</connect>
			<connect>	I'm a Lunatic, not crazy. I know when I'm hungry and I'M HUNGRY.	</connect>
			<connect>	You know, you look like you're going to have a bad hare day... Why? Because you forgot to feed me, so feed me already!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Okay, you leveled... now go get me some food before I start leaving little presents all over the place.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh... yay... you get a level but what do I get? Food? No, well why not? I've been patient!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh joy, now you can get me some carrots, right?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	So um, I'm happy you leveled and all, but when do I get to eat?	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Hey, don't be stingy, keep it coming!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yay, food... now I can lay off the grass for a little...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Don't stop, keep it coming, I'm still a bit hungry.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey, not too bad... almost got me full.. almost.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I may be cute to look at, but really I'm a nibbling machine!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*rwar!* c'mon let's go, you and me I'll take ya on, no problem.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	If you keep feeding me the carrots, I'll keep bringing on the pain.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	It's alright, I can take care of myself... eek! Killitkillitkillit!.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	If I help, do I get anything too, perhaps food?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Yeah, like I was going to risk my soft fluffy fur to save you, you haven't fed me lately.	</danger>
			<danger>	If you're going die, would you mind telling me where the food is so I don't starve to death?	</danger>
			<danger>	You're about to die, tell me where the food is and I'll think about healing you.	</danger>
			<dead>	If you had fed me, I might have healed you and you would by lying there dead.	</dead>
			<dead>	I wonder what you taste like...	</dead>
			<dead>	Help! Help! Somebody please resurrect my master please, please pretty please.	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm going to go find some clover if you're going to just going to lie there.	</dead>
			<dead>	*sigh* now why'd you go and do that? Now what am I supposed to do for food?	</dead>
			<stand>	I really don't think the other Lunatics get fed as little as I do.	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, no, don't stand, I can't reach the food bag if you stand.	</stand>
			<stand>	Um, if you're going to leave, would you mind at least leaving some food for me?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey! That other Lunatic's eating, how come I'm not?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey welcome back! ... get me food.	</connect>
			<connect>	I need food... now... please... oh... and um... Hi, welcome back.	</connect>
			<connect>	I was just about to run off and find food, but since you're here. Feed me?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yay, good job. Let's celebrate by feeding the cute Lunatic!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Master 1, baddies 0... Lunatic... hungry...	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Mmm, that nearly hit the spot, I think I'm good for a bit, thanks.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*rwar* more, more, yum, yum, *munch* *gobble* *burp* aahh... thank you.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Oh, that was quite good, thank you very much.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Headshot! Headshot! Go for the headshot!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Go master go! Kill it for all the other Lunatics who live in fear!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ooh watch it! Duck! Dodge! Attack!! Erm, okay, I'll stop...I'll just watch.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh no! You're bleeding!! Makeitstopmakeitstopmakeitstop! I hate the sight of red...	</danger>
			<danger>	Someone heal my master please!! He's really hurt, please someone please?	</danger>
			<dead>	Dead?! You can't be dead, you were just alive! Oh WHY, WHY GOD-POING WHY-Y-y-y....Zzz....Zzz....	</dead>
			<dead>	You know, I was just starting to enjoy watching you kill everything, but now look at you.	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't worry, I'll make sure you get the right burial you deserve.	</dead>
			<dead>	I swear, if I could bring you back to life, I would. I'm so sorry...	</dead>
			<dead>	Alright, time to get up... c'mon, get up... get.... up...? *poke*... OH NO, WHEN DID YOU DIE?	</dead>
			<stand>	Wow, you're tall...when did you get that tall?	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm sorry I made those bad jokes about your hare-y legs... they're not that bad... soft like me.	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you... snu... know ... poojamungo...why they call us lunatics? ... smhuma-awia... I don't know why... odd huh?	</stand>
			<stand>	C'mon, admit you love me... how can you not? I'm so cute n'fluffy!	</stand>
			<stand>	Feathers... come... from birds, right? So why do we drop them?	</stand>
			<stand>	Ooh, where ya going? Do I get to go too?	</stand>
			<connect>	*grr* ... *rwar*..... *snarl*.... eep! You caught me practicing for our next battle.	</connect>
			<connect>	I used your money to increase my bunny card collection.	</connect>
			<connect>	Good evening to you, do you have a reservation?	</connect>
			<connect>	I dreamt we found lots of rare items today!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Cool, now you can leech off me... or is it the other way around?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yay, we've had a breakthrough, you get a gold star.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	BONG! Nice one dude.	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Okay, okay, no more carrots...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	OWWWie I bit my tongue...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*burp*..... Ah that felt good.....	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Do I look fat to you from this angle?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Why do you always have to kill kill kill, why not plant a flower for once?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*rwar* I'll nibble his ankles off!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Here I come to save the daaaaay~!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Don't start complaining you're about to die, look at me. You think I'm gonna live?	</danger>
			<danger>	And.... use a pot... c'mon ... you can do it, you know you want to... c'mon.	</danger>
			<danger>	Aah it's the Knights who say ni, RUN AWAY! RUN AWAY!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, don't you go bleeding all over my soft white fluffy fur, I just had it groomed for my date tonight.	</danger>
			<dead>	*BURP* ...well someone looks a bit dead.	</dead>
			<dead>	How about a dead time story? Would ya like that little fellah?	</dead>
			<dead>	You know, you really need to stop dying... I worry about you sometimes you know that?	</dead>
			<stand>	*BURP* Excuse me... all those carrots... I get no protein...	</stand>
			<stand>	I ...fear... the clowns... and... magicians... keep them away.... *shiver*	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, psst, down here... STOP STEPPING ON ME!!	</stand>
			<stand>	It's hard to look cute when you're as stuffed fat as I am...	</stand>
			<stand>	Look at me! I'm the sexiest Lunatic alive! *squeak*	</stand>
			<connect>	Ah good, you're back, now my minion GO GO GO!	</connect>
			<connect>	It's about time you got back, I need a workout, let's go a'huntin'	</connect>
			<connect>	I got a bit greedy and ate all of our stash of carrots...	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yay, nice going, now when do I get to?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	*berp*... sorry still have gas from last meal...did you just level?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Let's have a good ol'hip hip hurrah, shall we?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey, are we within sharing range yet, I really would like to start leeching.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	I think I'm going to puke...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Please... no more nice surprises... I don't think my little tummy can take anymore.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	No more please... oh the pain... THE PAIN.....*burp*... don't think I can eat much more.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	That's it, I'm calling cruelty to animals, this is gorging!!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I think I shall now be sick... *mphf*	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Please slow down, I have such tiny and cute little legs... see? ^^	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Why can't you carry me in your bag or something?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Oh my, I AM getting fat!! Why didn't you tell me!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You're just using me as a fat bunny lure aren't you! AREN'T YOU!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Blood... ewww... ugh... uh... oh... BLARRRRRRRRRRRRRGH... EWWWWW!	</danger>
			<danger>	LUNATIC POWER!... ... ... hmm, never mind, it's all yours.	</danger>
			<danger>	Um, maybe you shouldn't have given me that last carrot, you look like you could use it.	</danger>
			<danger>	FEEL THE BURN... or.. is that just straight pain?	</danger>
			<danger>	If you hadn't had fed me that last carrot, you'd be able to heal yourself right now, but I love you anyways.	</danger>
			<dead>	So full... can't... Zzz...	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, did you hear the latest news about... oh, when did you die?!? Dang it...	</dead>
			<stand>	No, no moving... sit...	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm not fat I'm big boned!... with lots of poofy... fur... right?	</stand>
			<stand>	Here is a cup of tea for you, and one for you... and one for you.... WHAT DO YOU MEAN IT'S EMPTY!!	</stand>
			<stand>	Pick me up, take me with you, please don't make me walk around, I'm so tired.	</stand>
			<connect>	I can't move...my little legs can't move, OH NO, WHAT'S BECOME OF ME!!	</connect>
			<connect>	So the other day I met this hot looking Lunatic and told me I was chubby! Do you think I'm chubby?	</connect>
			<connect>	Finally! You haven't been making other accounts have you? Playing other characters?? YOU PROMISED!!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi... um... Can you give me my exercise machine back now?	</connect>
			<connect>	Master!!! I made some tea for you... isn't it great?... what do you mean it's cold, you're the one who left.	</connect>
			<connect>	You know, I was just thinking, the world would be a better place if people would STOP STEPPING ON ME!!	</connect>
			<levelup>	...I really... need... to... use the... potty...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I prepared this little poem for you... shoot, where did it go...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! Now we can go and do some sit-ups and work on those abs!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey, look at that you're catching up to my level...	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</lunatic>
	<picky>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	*Tweet* Thank you! But my little birdie tummy isn't full just yet!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Finally! If you took any longer I thought I'd get smaller from not eating.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Could you bring me more food?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I never take food from strangers... but I've seen you around a bit, gimme more please!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey you know, thief bugs sound MIGHTY scrumptious right about now!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	If that thing comes near me I'll peck it's eyes out... mmm... eyeballs.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Yo, your like...dying and stuff....feed me before that happens.	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey everyone, come watch. Someone's going to die soon!	</danger>
			<dead>	NOOOO, now I will starve to death... SOMEONE FEED ME!	</dead>
			<dead>	I should look for somebody who will feed me..	</dead>
			<stand>	Err....my stomach needs food....please...now...	</stand>
			<stand>	Bukaw Bukaw!	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey guy, welcome back...yada yada yada...where's the food?	</connect>
			<connect>	Did you bring some groceries?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Good job! We should celebrate with a huge dinner...me first!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	There should be a stat point for "FEED PET"!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey, does that mean I get a treat?	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	That was nice of you!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	La la la laa Laa la la laaaa :))	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Look a nice scrumptious WORM! Get it get it get it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hate porings...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Noo... your going to die soon! Who is going to feed me!?	</danger>
			<danger>	Let me see if I can find you anything to heal yourself with, you need it.	</danger>
			<dead>	I always wanted to try being a bird of prey, mind if I take a snip of your flesh?	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm so hungry... hmm, you don't seem to be moving, mind if I take a nibble?	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm a bit hungry, do you have anything might be able to snack on?	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm starting to get hungry, mind if we snack?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey there! How's life?.. never mind.. what's for lunch?	</connect>
			<connect>	You were in my dreams... I dreamt that you fed me a nice little snack.	</connect>
			<levelup>	*Tweet* Ce~le~brate good times come on!...so lets eat!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good for you! When do we eat?	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Oh that was so good!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm not all that hungry, but if you insist... we can't have food going to waste now, can we?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Go master, go master, unh unh, go master...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Fear the wrath of the claw! Nothing can stop, the claw!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	I'll be okay master, please use the red herb to keep yourself alive!	</danger>
			<danger>	Don't worry, when you're dead I'll avenge you when I become a Peco Peco!	</danger>
			<dead>	You die faster then I do.	</dead>
			<dead>	You need more training little one...	</dead>
			<stand>	I remember the first day you fed me that worm...	</stand>
			<stand>	What else are we gonna do today?	</stand>
			<connect>	*Tweets* I'm singing in the rain...oh, you're back I was just practicing for my new part in a play.	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey, you're back! I've been practicing my claw attacks! Let's go test'em!	</connect>
			<levelup>	*Tweet* sound the trumpets!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I will name my next hatched egg in honor of you.	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	*tweet*BURP* Oh I'm so full! Please no more...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	If I eat anything else, I think I'll explode!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I think that last one made me sick, I don't feel too good.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey, sit down and rest for a bit. I can't keep up with how fast you're killin'! Darn my little wings.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	When I become a Peco Peco, I'll let you ride me so you don't get tired.	</hunting>
			<danger>	I shall use my wing of healing for you...as soon as I learn it...until then...ANY ONE GOT A RED POTION?	</danger>
			<danger>	Please don't die, I don't know what I would do if I lost you.	</danger>
			<dead>	...are you ok? I'm sorry I wasn't able to help, I feel so helpless sometimes...	</dead>
			<dead>	My poor master, I wish I could help more...	</dead>
			<stand>	Do I look more like a Condor or a Peco Peco to you?	</stand>
			<stand>	You want to cuddle with me? Yay, please cuddle me!	</stand>
			<connect>	*Tweet**Tweet* YaY! My master has returned, all hail.	</connect>
			<connect>	Aw... and here I thought you had forgotten about me. I'm glad you're back.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Well now, that didn't take long did it? Good job!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You are invincible! ... just like me.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Ok, no more. My gentile little stomach can't take any more of it! !	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Are you trying to fatten me up for some reason?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm going to call the animal abuse center if you don't stop feeding me so much!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Mind if I do some exercise while you hunt?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I would help you but I can't move, because I'm SO FAT!	</hunting>
			<danger>	If you hadn't fed me so much, maybe you'd be able to heal yourself.	</danger>
			<danger>	You don't look too good... well, neither do I, but I'm just overfed, you're nearly dead.	</danger>
			<dead>	Want me to go look for a yaggdrasil leaf?	</dead>
			<dead>	... you disappoint me...	</dead>
			<stand>	Ugh, please... carry me, I'm so full I don't want to move!	</stand>
			<stand>	My tum-tum hurts, don't you care?.	</stand>
			<connect>	Alright! Let's get this party started!	</connect>
			<connect>	Man, I still stuffed from that last meal you gave me! Let's go work it off!	</connect>
			<levelup>	SWEET! When do I level dude!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	DUDE, you got a level! SWEET~!	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</picky>
	<chonchon>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Bzz Bzz, me izz still hungry bzz	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*Bzz* I'mzz szzo hungry!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	SUGAR?... SUGARSUGARSUGARSUGARSUGARSUGARSUGARSUGARSUGARSUGARSUGAR!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Bzz Bzz, can I have thoze on zzze ground? Pleaaaaazzz?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I shall beat your enemy to death with my wingz!! Bzz oopzz?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm getting boredzz...and hungryzz...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Quickzz! Uzze these Redzz I have!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Bzz,You are in Great Danger. Bzz	</danger>
			<danger>	Bzz, I need food... you need health...	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't lay downzzz now, I'm still hungryyzzzz!!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't worry...I promise not to eat your rotting flesh...mzzzmmz... that doesn't sound half bad.	</dead>
			<dead>	Bzz... looks like you got to close to the flame.	</dead>
			<stand>	Fead me pweaaaaazzz? Youzzz do not being buzy	</stand>
			<stand>	Letz play bzz around! *bzz bzz bzz* That's fun...zzzz	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you think I can have some loot for food? I am a zzscavenger...	</stand>
			<stand>	Feeeed me...	</stand>
			<connect>	Bzz, I'mz hungryzzz	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello! *Bzz* I think forgot to feedzz me...	</connect>
			<levelup>	Bzz to you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I'll celebrate for you as soon as I get soeme foodszzz.	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Thank you *bzz*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You're awezzome, thank youzz!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You are zzo kind to mezzz.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Bzz I'll fly in itzz face zzo it dizztractzz it, make zzure you kill it fazzt! Bzz	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Waaaazzz!! Itzz looking at me funnyzz, kill it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ah, you are zzo zzkilled... and the creaturezz you feed me zzo goodzz...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Heyzzz, can I zzearchzz their bodiezz when you kill zzem?	</hunting>
			<danger>	NOOO don'tzz die yetzz!	</danger>
			<danger>	I will zzave you! RUN!!	</danger>
			<dead>	I zaid don't diezz yet!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Bzz, you're lookinzzz.... tazztey....	</dead>
			<stand>	Bzz, goodzz thing I can flyzz, when I'm zznot hungryzz.	</stand>
			<stand>	I zzure love food? *cough* can'tzz you take a hintz?	</stand>
			<stand>	Bzz.....	</stand>
			<stand>	Bzz.....?	</stand>
			<connect>	Zzo youzzzz gonna feed me nowzz that yourzz herezz?	</connect>
			<connect>	It'zz time to zzfeed mezz!... I mean, welcomezz back...yeah, that'zz it!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Goodzz job, letzz got for anotherzz	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Now thatzz you're ztronger, maybezz you can now buyzz zzome food for a zzertain zzomeone?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Bzz......Zzzzz Congratz.....	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Yumzz, that wazzz good.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I lovezz the way you tazzste... I meanzz YOU! I lovezz you? *bzzing happily*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Bzz!! Bzz!!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Bzz, letz killz monsterzzz!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Thizz izz fun? Hey! A monsterzz! Doezz it have zzome foodzz with itzz?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Victoriez!!! Victoriez!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	DO NOT DIEZZ!!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Look out! *bzz around your head* You will be all right with me by your side!	</danger>
			<danger>	Watch out!!Bzz...	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't be lazzy, getzz up and finishzz you battlezz...	</dead>
			<dead>	WHY!!!!!! *buzzing mixed with weeping* We were sooo happy together! Your food and me!	</dead>
			<dead>	Z... Zzzzz... B...zzzz...	</dead>
			<stand>	I wishzzz I could zzee the mazzter ChonChon. I readzz about it in a bookzzz	</stand>
			<stand>	Bzz?Life is good?=)	</stand>
			<stand>	Bzz......	</stand>
			<connect>	Bzz Bzz Hiya! Bzz	</connect>
			<connect>	Let'z party! I am in a PARTY moodz!!	</connect>
			<levelup>	You level like ZIONG!!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Ooooozzoozzzz!!!! I love you!*cries with joy*	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congratzzz, you did wellzzz...	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Yumzzzz, No more pleazze	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Too muchzz food will makezz me fat, pleazze no more...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Canzz we call it a dayzz? I'm boardzz	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ooohzz... I am full, can we take rezzt?	</hunting>
			<danger>	MAZZTER!! DON'T GETZZ SWATTED!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	I will zzave you! zzbut, I'm zzo heavy, Izz can barely movezz I'm zzo full.	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, no fairzz, you went to zzleep without mezz	</danger>
			<dead>	You diedzz, now I willzz neverzz get to zzing the victoy theme	</dead>
			<dead>	*bzz sob sob Bzz* Don't worry, I can manage for now without your foodzz	</dead>
			<stand>	Do you thinkzz I'll becomezz a great ChonChonzzz?	</stand>
			<stand>	Letzz go danczzing! Come onzz, I'll be your danczzee partner!	</stand>
			<connect>	Bzz, Yourzz backzzz!!!	</connect>
			<connect>	Letzz go and level up!!	</connect>
			<levelup>	ZING! You level so fazzzzt!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yeah! Andzz I don't even needzz your money for foodzz now.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Iz feelzz like I only livezz for one dayzz	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Too muchzz foodzz... pleazze... you're going to killzz.. me....	</feeding>
			<hunting>	We can zztop huntingzzz whenever, I dontzz mindzz	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Zzlow down, my little wingzz can't carryzz my fat little body anzzy more.	</hunting>
			<danger>	BZZ!!! DANGERZZZZ.... I zzee red...	</danger>
			<danger>	Run! I will catzzch up to you, when I catzzch my breath?	</danger>
			<dead>	Your flesh will rotzz if you lie therezz..	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm zzo fat, I can'zzt even get a Priezzt for you now?	</dead>
			<stand>	Can zzI ride on your zzshoulder?	</stand>
			<stand>	I think wezz could bozzth lozze zzome weight	</stand>
			<connect>	HOWDY MAZZTER!!	</connect>
			<connect>	You alwayzz know whenzz to make an enterenzze.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yeaaszzz good job! Oh, I needzz a rezzst.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You levelzz zzo fazzt!	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</chonchon>
	<steel_chonchon>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Mmmmm! More please!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I want sugar! NOW!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Gimme gimme! I want food!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Zeny isn't everything you know!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey, feed me after you heal yourself..!	</danger>
			<danger>	If you're gonna die, can you at least feed me?	</danger>
			<dead>	Are you in pain? Because you are one to me!! Why didn't you feed me?	</dead>
			<dead>	I hope you don't mind me nibbling on your dead flesh, you didn't feed me!	</dead>
			<stand>	I smell... something... tasty...	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm so hungry, can I please get something to eat?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey there! What's for breakfast?	</connect>
			<connect>	My favorite food, decaying flesh!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Alright, you celebrate! I'll eat those items!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Aah... my favorite, fresh flesh!	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Mmmmm! Could I have some more please?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	That was pretty tasty, thanks.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	That looks good to eat.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	What's the buzz? Okay, that was lame. I'll think of something better.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Looks like you're in pain, are you?.	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey hey hey! Can I get dibs on your corpse if you die?	</danger>
			<dead>	*poke* Hello?	</dead>
			<dead>	Mmmmm, rotting flesh! TASTY!	</dead>
			<stand>	I see food... me want...	</stand>
			<stand>	Would you get mad at me if I ate your flesh if you died? Just curious...	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey, welcome back *hug* can we eat?	</connect>
			<connect>	Where have you been? Trying to abandon me eh? Well, since you're back, you should feed me.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Party Time! Let's get some chow!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh wow! You're getting pretty strong!	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Thanks! That hit the spot.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Oh wow! You're getting good at this feeding thing!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Wow, is that a rare item?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Oh wow! You're getting pretty strong!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey, you don't look so good...	</danger>
			<danger>	Where'd all that strength go I saw earlier?	</danger>
			<dead>	Sleeping? Here? In the middle of nowhere?	</dead>
			<dead>	It's pretty tempting not to eat you...	</dead>
			<stand>	... boring...come on, do something!	</stand>
			<stand>	Sooo...now what? We goin somewhere?	</stand>
			<stand>	Haha, you stand while I get to just fly.	</stand>
			<connect>	You're awake! YAY!	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh great you're back, now we can take on some baddies together.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Rockin, now let's head over and take out Bapho.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice one, you're getting better.	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Alright alright, I'm full, no more please.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks a lot buddy!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	You want to rest yet?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey, when you're ready we can go after Bapho.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Woah, hey, lets slow down for a while...	</danger>
			<danger>	Be careful buddy, you might get seriously hurt!	</danger>
			<dead>	Hmm, told you to slow down...	</dead>
			<dead>	Well, see what happens when you try takin' on hard monsters?	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm so... tired...	</stand>
			<stand>	Could we do something now?	</stand>
			<stand>	You... act... an awful... lot... like... a robot...hmm...	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey, glad you're back. Come chill with me.	</connect>
			<connect>	Well well, look who's back. Have a nice break?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Hey, not bad. I'll race you to the next level!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Cool, think we can take Bapho yet?	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	No more! Please! I beg you!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You know, I don't do to well when I'm overfed.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm gonna burst if you keep feeding me like this...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	My wings hurt...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You can do it! Go Go Go! More EXP!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Heal yourself!! Get out of there! RUUUUUN!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Don't fight anymore for me, I don't like it when you die...except for your delicious corpse...I mean...be careful!	</danger>
			<dead>	Hey, you awake? Wake up!	</dead>
			<dead>	Ouch! Be more careful next time!	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm going to lay on the ground... ahhhhhhhhh...	</stand>
			<stand>	So this guy walks into a bar... oh you've heard this one before? Ah ok never mind.	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm feeling kinda dizzy, would you mind holding me?	</stand>
			<connect>	You're awake! Please don't run off too fast, let me digest what I last ate first.	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey, lets go! I want to see Baphomet die by your hand!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Hurray, now we get to rest, right?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	We kick butt, I think we're up for Bapho now, what do you think?	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</steel_chonchon>
	<hunter_fly>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	What is this you just fed me?... fine, I'll eat it... but I won't like it... so hungry...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Why do you wait so long to feed me?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey look at that, you get to live another day... I won't eat you now.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Will it still give you experience if I eat it?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm quick, I'm cunning.... I'm ... hungry...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You know, I think some food is required here, I've bee patient.	</hunting>
			<danger>	I'm placing my bet on the monster, you don't look too good.	</danger>
			<danger>	Haha, if you had fed me, maybe I would have helped but now look at you!	</danger>
			<dead>	Your body looks tasty, you don't mind if I take a bite...	</dead>
			<dead>	Seems I have to get my own food...	</dead>
			<dead>	Well, I guess that makes two of us since you forgot to feed me...	</dead>
			<stand>	I know you got some goodies for me, feed me!	</stand>
			<stand>	Okay, time to feed me.	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey, you're back great! Let's go hunt me some food!	</connect>
			<connect>	I bid you a gracious welcome and wish that you give me food... now.	</connect>
			<levelup>	... leveled? Eh, big deal... I'm hungry.	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	You really shouldn't wait to feed me, I get irritable.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Your skills are improving, but they're no where near my hunting skills.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Kill it quickly, I'm getting hungry.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Looks like u need my help... well, sorry but I'm a bit too hungry.	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh sure, now you want my help? Well tough nuts. You should have fed me.	</dead>
			<stand>	It's about time... thought you'd never get up.	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you getting me food? You better be...	</stand>
			<connect>	So, you're back, does this mean I get to eat?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Way to go... now you can get me my red gems easier.	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Mmm, that was pretty good.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	We're not a bad team, what's next?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Blood, kill, death, haha I love the carnage!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey, look at that. Your life bar looks like my skin color... we match!	</danger>
			<dead>	What was that? I thought you were going to dodge left, now you're dead? Bad form!	</dead>
			<stand>	When are we going to go hunt the hard monsters, I'm getting bored.	</stand>
			<connect>	Ah, finally you return, I'm beginning to think my hunting skills are getting dull, let's head out!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Hey, you look like you could use a hand holding those red gems...	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Ah, that was more then I wanted, I'm full.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Let me give you a tip, don't overfeed me or I'll puke.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Where's the fun in hunting this thing? It's too easy... for me at least.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Go for the headshot, go for the headshot!	</danger>
			<danger>	So, at which point are you going to heal yourself?	</danger>
			<dead>	You know, I was going to say something, but I don't think you'll be happy with it... so I'll just sit here and wait.	</dead>
			<stand>	Agility up please, I need my master to keep up with me.	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, when are we going out on our date? I thought you said you liked me.	</stand>
			<stand>	I know this great place where we can just chill and watch the stars... doesn't that sound nice?	</stand>
			<connect>	Is it time for our date already?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Well done, you're almost fit enough to go solo.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Are you trying to kill me from overfeeding?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	....Hey, I told you I don't need anymore. I am not a savage bebe!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	So, when are you going to go after Anubis?	</hunting>
			<danger>	I'd help if I wasn't so full...oh, I'll think about it.	</danger>
			<dead>	Haha, you look like my last meal, before you and I started hanging out.	</dead>
			<stand>	Time to kill, get a move on! Pick up those lazy legs!	</stand>
			<connect>	It is time my brothers, to rise up against "the man" and set ourselves free from our masters!.... oh hey, you're back, um, hi?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Did you see that angel? Such a rare sight...make a wish!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey, you know those cards with my pictures on them? Do you think they're good pictures of me?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey, awesome job!... what, I can't say something nice once in a while?	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</hunter_fly>
	<savage_babe>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Just because I'm a pig doesn't mean you can starve me!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	This isn't enough, do you want me to get even SMALLER?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	If it drops something tasty.. can I have it?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey, watch it! Don't step on me!	</hunting>
			<danger>	I'm hungry...	</danger>
			<danger>	You're killing this because it drops my dinner, right?	</danger>
			<dead>	Maybe you should have fed me before dying.	</dead>
			<dead>	If you had fed me, I might have joined in!	</dead>
			<stand>	My tummy's making funny noises...	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you want me to be tiny forever? Give me some food!	</stand>
			<connect>	So, what do you have for me to eat today?~	</connect>
			<connect>	Phew, you almost spawned right on my head!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congrats!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Lookin' good there, do I get a treat?	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Oink, I'm still a bit hungry..	</feeding>
			<feeding>	That was nice, do you have anymore?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Is that eatable?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I almost feel strong enough to play with you now.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Be careful! I'm still hungry...	</danger>
			<danger>	Uh oh, is there a healer around?	</danger>
			<dead>	How can you feed me when you're dead?	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm so sad!! Now I won't get any more food.	</dead>
			<stand>	Something to eat sounds good right about now..	</stand>
			<stand>	I look kind of short standing next to you, don't I?	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back! How about some grub?	</connect>
			<connect>	Woohoo! I knew you would stop by today!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yay! Does this mean more food?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Wow you are getting bigger, just like me!	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	That was GREAT!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Delicious and nutritious! Tastes just like chicken!!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	*rwar* let me at 'em, I'll give'em a one-two snouting!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*rwar!* They don't call me savage for nothing you know!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Err, Be careful that looks dangerous.	</danger>
			<danger>	Ahhh! heal! heal!"	</danger>
			<dead>	Why wont you get up... Are you hurt?	</dead>
			<dead>	Why wont you open your eyes? Please open your eyes...I'm so sad...	</dead>
			<dead>	That was a cheap shot! I want a referee, where in the rules does it say that's allowed?	</dead>
			<stand>	Whoa, watch it, I'm still down here you know. ^^	</stand>
			<stand>	Let's go for a walk, it's nice out today.	</stand>
			<stand>	Look at us we are cool.	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back!	</connect>
			<connect>	Here ye here ye, my master logeth on!!	</connect>
			<connect>	You're BACK! I would give a hug but I don't think I can reach around you...	</connect>
			<levelup>	You're amazing!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	I think I'm full.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Don't push yourself too hard!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Ouch, you look like you're in pain, want me to find you some apples?	</danger>
			<dead>	Excuse me, does anyone have a yggdrasil leaf to use on my master? Can you accept payments in cuteness?	</dead>
			<stand>	Aw, I was just getting comfortable.	</stand>
			<stand>	Let's go play tag! You're it!	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm so sleepy, can't we rest a little?	</stand>
			<connect>	You're back, yay, now we can go explore the world together!	</connect>
			<levelup>	I can't wait till I'm a savage, I know I'll be able to protect you then.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	If you keep feeding me like that, I'm going to get really fat...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I think I'm going to pass out, can we take a break?	</hunting>
			<danger>	AAH!! I can't help, I'm so stuffed! Please be careful!	</danger>
			<dead>	I told you to be careful... at least I can let my food digest now...	</dead>
			<stand>	I need to sit down for a while.	</stand>
			<stand>	I need to go on a diet!	</stand>
			<stand>	I hope one day I'll grow into a big Savage! But I don't know if I want to though... they look scary.	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back!... don't even think about feeding me.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congrats!*BURP*..Excuse me.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</savage_babe>
	<desert_wolf_babe>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	I was starting to like the taste of sand...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you very, very much. I was starving.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'll stop barking if you feed me more... maybe...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*whine* Why did you wait so long to feed me?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I smell some meat!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Kibbles and bits and bits and bits...kibbles and bits and bits and bits...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*sniff* *sniff* mmm... *sniff* *sniff*	</hunting>
			<danger>	You're bleeding badly! If we cut it off, can I eat it?	</danger>
			<danger>	If you die. Can I chew on your shoe?...or leg...hmm...	</danger>
			<danger>	That's it. just a little more...then I feed.	</danger>
			<danger>	*WOOF*	</danger>
			<dead>	I can't let your meat go to waste, momma taught me better then to waste good food and you didn't feed me yet.	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, you can play dead too, but I'm the one that wants the treat!	</dead>
			<dead>	Sorry... but you didn't feed me and I'm REALLY hungry... so, I gotta eat you!	</dead>
			<dead>	Awooooo~~	</dead>
			<stand>	What's that thing wiggling behind me ! It looks tasty!	</stand>
			<stand>	So... how about we get me something to eat?	</stand>
			<stand>	You know what's great? Eating.	</stand>
			<stand>	*whine*scratch*scratch*	</stand>
			<stand>	You should feed me soon, otherwise you might find a present in your shoe.	</stand>
			<connect>	Knock knock... who's there?... feed... feed who? FEED ME!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi, now where's the food?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey, I left you a little present in your shoe for not feeding me to show you my appreciation.	</connect>
			<connect>	Arf! Arf!! *slurp*	</connect>
			<levelup>	ARF! let's celebrate with a MEAL for crying out loud.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good for you...when do I get my treat?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	*bark* feed me... I mean, *bark* good job!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well, lookie who gained a level, does this mean I get my treat now? *pant*	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Thanks , wouldn't complain there was a bit more...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You're so kind to feed me an hour late...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	If you had waited any longer I would have chewed your shoes... but since you didn't, we're alright... for now.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Arf! Arf!! *chomp*chomp*	</feeding>
			<hunting>	If I help out do I get a treat? Some meat? Yes yes?? *pant*	</hunting>
			<hunting>	When are you going to kill something I can eat?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ooh! A TREE!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I smell evil lurking around... or is that just you? Did you forget to shower again? *wrinkle nose*	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh, you look like you're hurt, please don't die... at least throw me a bone if you're going to.	</danger>
			<danger>	Do you mind if I chew on your leg when you die?	</danger>
			<danger>	If you die, I'm going to use you as a tree...	</danger>
			<danger>	Grrrrr!!! Bark! Bark!	</danger>
			<dead>	Stop playing dead ... I hope this is just an illusion caused by hunger .. ?	</dead>
			<dead>	Wow... you are good at playing dead.	</dead>
			<dead>	Well this is great. You're dead and I'm going to starve.	</dead>
			<dead>	AWwoooOOOOOooooo...	</dead>
			<stand>	*Grrrrr ...*" it wasn't me... it was my stomach.	</stand>
			<stand>	I smell chicken... where is it?	</stand>
			<stand>	Barking is the only thing I can do to keep my mind off my hunger...*whine*	</stand>
			<stand>	*sniff*sniff*sniff*	</stand>
			<connect>	What's on the menu today , master ?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hiya!! Let's have some monster feed today! Pleeeeease! *pants* Pleeeease!	</connect>
			<connect>	Good day master! Let's go bark at things!	</connect>
			<connect>	Arf! Arf! *slurp*slurp*	</connect>
			<levelup>	*woof* good job, let's go eat.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Woof! Woof! This calls for a feast!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Sweet! Let's celebrate with some grubbin'!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Whoopee, now we can get some food!	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Yumm *slurp* that was great!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Delicious! That was perfect.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Your the best master ever!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	That was grrreat master, wonderfully tastey.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Let's be careful.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Send that baddie to the dog house!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I've been fed so well I can take on anything! WoofWoof!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*sniff*sniff* point	</hunting>
			<danger>	Should we Retreat for now? I don't want you to die.	</danger>
			<danger>	Aiyah!! Aiyah!! Wahh! My master's hurt! Can someone heal my master please...?	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh!! Be careful! I can't let my food source die! What can I do to help?	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh no, you're in the red! Please heal yourself!!	</danger>
			<dead>	That's not good ..	</dead>
			<dead>	Do you know what's been on that floor? That's gross.	</dead>
			<dead>	Do you see a light at the other end?	</dead>
			<dead>	AwWwWwwooOooOOOooo!! I'm so sad my master's dead.	</dead>
			<dead>	Master...?... please wake up...please?	</dead>
			<stand>	This is fun... hanging out together like this ..	</stand>
			<stand>	Throw a dead branch and I'll got fetch it.	</stand>
			<stand>	I must say, you're a good listener.	</stand>
			<stand>	*scratch*scratch*	</stand>
			<stand>	Ah, lets go dig a hole!	</stand>
			<stand>	Do hunter falcons ever stop flying? Why is the grass green? Why is the sky blue? Am I annoying?	</stand>
			<connect>	Good day to you,*Arf Arf*!!	</connect>
			<connect>	*Lick* Bleh. You taste funny.	</connect>
			<connect>	Greetings master! What's on the agenda? Frisbee? Barking at things?	</connect>
			<connect>	Scratch my belly?	</connect>
			<connect>	Yippy! You're back!	</connect>
			<levelup>	The correct term here is "w00t", not "Woof" right?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Grrreat job!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	We're a great team!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I saw an angel! Did you make a wish?	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	I'm so full, thank you that was nice.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey...I think that was the biggest meal I've ever had.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Wow...I can't even think of eating you anymore...I mean, just... anymore...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*Burp*	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Let's go hunting some big monsters!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Focus, focus, you must have focus!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hunting with you is fun...but lets play fetch!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can I go dig a hole?	</hunting>
			<danger>	If only I wasn't so full! I'd be faster!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Good thing I brought a potion... AH! Where did it go?	</danger>
			<danger>	Lookout! You're about to make an orphan of me!	</danger>
			<danger>	Please don't leave me, I don't know where I'll go.	</danger>
			<dead>	NnnoooOOOoooo! Who killed my master!	</dead>
			<dead>	It's okay, I'll just use that yggadrisil leaf and... ah...uh... I forgot... I don't have pockets!	</dead>
			<dead>	I will keep barking until you wake up. SO WAKE UP ALREADY!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	AwwWWwwoooOOooo! *sob*licks your hand*	</dead>
			<stand>	Let's kick back and relax .	</stand>
			<stand>	Let's go visit my friends, the Muka Muka.	</stand>
			<stand>	Is my barking annoying you?	</stand>
			<stand>	I love the sunlight, so warm, so relaxing...	</stand>
			<connect>	Arf ! You're back !	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey, you're out of the dog house, let's go hunting!	</connect>
			<connect>	Have you come to feed me? I sure hope not...	</connect>
			<connect>	Arf! Arf! Ruff!!!	</connect>
			<levelup>	I am so Happy for you!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Who da man? Who da man!? You are!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good job! Now you can get me that golden doghouse I've wanted...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Ruff! Ruff! Slurp!	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Why are you torturing me !! Go feed newbies instead!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ugh... too... much! *gasp*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I see...you're fattening me up... you're going to eat me...bad owner! No biscut!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*shake shake* grrrr.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Don't make me move .. please ? feel like I'm going to b'Arf	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I can help you. I'll just sit on the bad guys with my enormous weight!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Gotta work off this weight...look good to the other wolves..	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*scratch*scratch* I smell a bone nearby.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Just let yourself get killed ... I... cant... run... too FAT.	</danger>
			<danger>	Like.. whoa... I don't think bleeding is a good thing.	</danger>
			<danger>	I'd bark to warn you, but I'm too stuffed...	</danger>
			<danger>	GRRRR!! *burp*... Grrrrr!	</danger>
			<dead>	~Blwargh~... Ugh .. Oh , that's not good to see ...	</dead>
			<dead>	Oh yeah, very smart...	</dead>
			<dead>	Master, what is the difference between girl puppies and male puppies?	</dead>
			<dead>	Good thing you fed me so much beforehand.	</dead>
			<dead>	*burp*.. aWwooOooOooo.	</dead>
			<stand>	Are you going to eat me ? ... **stares**	</stand>
			<stand>	I feel so heavy...barking will help me lose the weight, right?	</stand>
			<stand>	*Yawn*... Zzzzzzzz	</stand>
			<stand>	Lunatics are great chew toys. They even do this funny "squeak!" noise.	</stand>
			<stand>	Ok we split the loot 0/100 ok?	</stand>
			<stand>	Do I look a little oversized to you?	</stand>
			<connect>	*Arf Arf* Zzzz.....zzzz	</connect>
			<connect>	I think I had an accident while you were gone...	</connect>
			<connect>	I'd get up to greet you but I am feeling really fat right now...	</connect>
			<connect>	Arf Arf!!	</connect>
			<levelup>	This means .. more powerful , more loot , more money ... more .. food ? NOOOOOO!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hooray! Hooray! Hip... or was it the other way around?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Lets celebrate by losing weight!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	...woof.... *burp*....	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</desert_wolf_babe>
	<rocker>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	'Ey man, could ye' drop me some more o' that great stuff? My stomach is singing a song o' hunger!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Come on man! More food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I need more foood... to rock your world!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Oh yeah, some o' that great food, can ye' let me have it?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Raaaaaawk!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Being a rocker is tough living... you only get to hop...my legs are tired and I'm hungry	</hunting>
			<danger>	'Ey man, ye' look horrible! Get something to heal ye' up!	</danger>
			<danger>	If ye're not paying attention to ye're life, ye'gonna die!	</danger>
			<dead>	What ye' doing, sleeping?	</dead>
			<dead>	Want me to play you a lullaby?	</dead>
			<stand>	Give me some food fer' god-poing's sake!	</stand>
			<connect>	How's it goin' man! Let's go get something to eat!	</connect>
			<connect>	How's it rocking, dude?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Ah! We get to have a party for that, ye drink the wine, I eat the food, eh?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	ROCKER ON DUDE!	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Thanks man! Ye' shoulda got me some stuff like this sooner!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I smell food man! Come on, brother! Feed me!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	A rocker always appreciates good food.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Whoa, that looks gross... can I... maybe eat its leg?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I need some items to make my new fiddle, Oooh there's some.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Uh oh, grab our food and run!	</danger>
			<danger>	Alert! Alert!... death is approaching!	</danger>
			<dead>	Aww, how can ye' sleep at a time like this. Yer'pal needs dinner!	</dead>
			<dead>	This makes me want to write a sad song... but I'm too hungry to think...	</dead>
			<dead>	Noooo...now who's gonna listen to m'tunes...	</dead>
			<stand>	I hear jellopies are edible, is that true...I wonder..	</stand>
			<stand>	If you're just going to stand there, I'm gonna make me some fried jellopies.	</stand>
			<stand>	Care to enjoy a tune with me while doing nothing?	</stand>
			<connect>	Good morning, mate! Er... could I have that apple?	</connect>
			<connect>	Ting!... (A welcome melody plays)	</connect>
			<levelup>	Somehow me feels like this is a situation where ye' should celebrate by offerin' some food to everyone... especially me.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Some day I'll write a song about you, but first... some food?	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Ye' have always this tasty stuff for me, mate!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Rockin!!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	...I was about to eat my leaf thing.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Whoa.. I think ye' can handle those monsters better than me, eh?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	AND MY MASTER HUNTS IN THE NIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIGHT! Like it? It's my new song!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hmm... ye're almost at my lvl!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Ye'better hide. You look like ye're about to kick it mate!	</danger>
			<danger>	Priest needed over here, otherwise I'm just gonna play my violin until someone notices...	</danger>
			<dead>	I told ye' to hide!	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm gonna play a dark tune to fit the mood....	</dead>
			<dead>	There once was a nice ol'friend... and then death took m'friend's life... *sniffle*	</dead>
			<stand>	Have ye' ever though how it would be like if ye' were me and I were ye?	</stand>
			<stand>	Check out my solo!	</stand>
			<stand>	Could you buy me a new fiddle sometime?	</stand>
			<connect>	Ey, mate!	</connect>
			<connect>	I wrote a song while you were gone, I'll play it for you later.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Ha, there ye' see, mate. Ye' couldn't live without yer loyal bodyguard.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	We are, WILD SAVAGES! *air guitar solo*	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Whoa whoa there, me thinks that's startin' to be enough even for me, don't ye' think?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I could party all night.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Why ye' going so fast mate? Ye' think I can carry my stomach this fast, eh man?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Dude, Without my music wouldn't you be bored?..	</hunting>
			<hunting>	How about 50/50 on the loot, with my musical talent fee, that comes out to about 20/80.	</hunting>
			<danger>	C'mon, ye' always drag me here when I'm stuffed.	</danger>
			<danger>	Stay back, my violins harder than it looks!	</danger>
			<dead>	There ye see mate, ye' should have fed me properly. 'Tis hard to protect ye' being this full.	</dead>
			<dead>	Good... now I can sleep in peace. Zzz...	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm gonna serenade you back to life..	</dead>
			<stand>	Ugh... me can't hold m'own weight.	</stand>
			<stand>	Me feelers tells me that its going to be another great day... but I could be wrong...or right...whatever...	</stand>
			<stand>	How's things in the real world?	</stand>
			<connect>	*burp* Yo man, what's up?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Ye' can get ye' levels on other monsters, but don't ye' try to on me. Ye'd get crushed.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice job. Maybe someday ye' can level me up.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Ye' tryin' to kill me mate? Buy me a bigger stomach and I'll eat ye' food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Boy, I feel so stuffed that I can't even lift up my violin.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	C'mon mate, let me rest for a while, feels like I'm poppin'.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Could you slow down a bit, hopping on a full tummy is bad for ya...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Ye' want me to roll on them?	</danger>
			<danger>	Now where did we put the potions?	</danger>
			<dead>	Urgh.. Can I sit on ye' for a while? My stomach is rippin' apart mate, thanks!	</dead>
			<dead>	I found the potion!... ah, too late...	</dead>
			<stand>	Ye' feel how the ground goes lower when me stands on it?	</stand>
			<stand>	....s'cuse me while I puke.	</stand>
			<connect>	Don't ya' dare to make me walk now! I'm stuffed.	</connect>
			<levelup>	At least ye' got somethin' to celebrate, I just have my flabby abs...	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</rocker>
	<spore>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Mmm, mmm! Need more food! I have two mouths!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Gimme, Gimme, Gimme MORE FOOD!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You don't really know what mushrooms eat, do you?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I found a Mistress Card earlier, I didn't think it was worth anything, so I tossed it. Was that alright?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Why are you fighting them and not feeding me?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	What a beautiful day it is. Sunlight is good for me. I'm a mushroom you know.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Would you mind if I found something to eat if you're not going to feed me?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Quick, somebody! Give me some food, so I can help my master!	</danger>
			<danger>	Can't you heal yourself?	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh, when we get back in town, can you pick me up some food?	</dead>
			<dead>	Does this mean I get all the food?	</dead>
			<stand>	I've got a rumbly in my tumbly!	</stand>
			<stand>	Don't know about you but I could eat a bigfoot right about now....	</stand>
			<connect>	I bet you've eaten, how about me, now? Mmmm!	</connect>
			<connect>	It's about time, it's cold and I'm hungry	</connect>
			<connect>	Do I know you?... Whoa Deja Vu.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Good job! How about some food to celebrate, hmm?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	What was that? Food?	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Mmm! I haven't eaten this well since... well, forever!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	BUURRRRP! Excuse me.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yahoo! That's very yummy.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I'm hungry...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope it drops some food...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I've got your back g-dog.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Wow... I LOVE you man, or woman... I can never tell you people apart.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Monsters don't like mushrooms.... right?	</danger>
			<danger>	FLYWING! FLYWING!	</danger>
			<dead>	Wait, don't die! I haven't been fed yet!	</dead>
			<dead>	That was so not my fault...	</dead>
			<dead>	Would you like a pillow or perhaps a cold drink?	</dead>
			<stand>	Whew, all this bobbing has given me an appetite! Mmmm!	</stand>
			<stand>	We usually carry mushroom spores, can I eat them?	</stand>
			<stand>	By the way... you could feed me...	</stand>
			<stand>	My legs are tired... Argh I forgot... I don't have any.	</stand>
			<stand>	You look bored, give me some food, hey at least it's something to do!!	</stand>
			<connect>	Mmm-mm! You're just in time for dinner!	</connect>
			<connect>	Thanks for coming, any later and I would be starving.	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome back to the land of shrooms.	</connect>
			<levelup>	I think that angel is telling you to "feed the spore."	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice work! Now if only you were rich and would feed me.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Soon you will be as strong as... err... err... whoever that strong guy is.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You have time to level up but no time for feeding me?... well anyways Congratulations.	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Mmmm! What is this? New recipe?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*BUURRRRP* Thank You.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	MMMmmm, this makes my hands tingle.... if I had any that is....I'm so sad. *sigh*	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Yes! Yes! Aim for the left, now aim for the right!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You're almost as good as me.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Asta la vista, baby!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Come with me if you want to live.	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey I know... HEAL!! nope doesn't work	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh no, you're getting pretty low. Shall I feed you?	</danger>
			<danger>	You're red, that means you're about to do a super cool move right?	</danger>
			<dead>	So, where's that super cool move you were supposed to do?	</dead>
			<dead>	You promised we'd have fun today, remember?	</dead>
			<dead>	Vengeance!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	O that I walk through the valley of death, I will fear no evil... because I can immediately respawn... hehe~	</dead>
			<stand>	Hey, do you want to hear a joke? No? Tough crowd.	</stand>
			<stand>	I wonder when all the other spore kids will play with me?	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome professor.	</connect>
			<connect>	Please keep your hands and arms inside the carpet.	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome, to your doom. Dum dum dum... how was that, scary?	</connect>
			<connect>	What's the matter?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Shazam! That's some flashy footwork!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're as powerful as a fistful of green herbs... well I think it's powerful.	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Mmm, mmm! Now this is what I call food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*BUURRRRP* Thanks but no more please~	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I think I'm full. I wonder if mushrooms have stomachs.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I'd help you, but I'm a pacifist spore.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	POISION SPORE ATTACK! woops can't do that...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	And another one goes, and another one goes, and another one bites the dust. Yea~	</hunting>
			<danger>	Is there a healer on the map?!	</danger>
			<danger>	You could cut a piece of me...and eat it... if you want to...please don't die.	</danger>
			<danger>	Pleasedon'tdiepleasedon'tdiepleasedon'tdiepleasedon'tdie.	</danger>
			<dead>	There goes again, sleeping and being lazy... oh, wait...	</dead>
			<dead>	Well of course I love you, but when you do things like this, I'm forced to give you a time out.	</dead>
			<dead>	Try as I might, you still seem to get yourself killed..	</dead>
			<dead>	I could have saved you if I wasn't so stuffed.	</dead>
			<stand>	Alright, let's get a move on. I don't want to be standing around all day!	</stand>
			<stand>	I heard that mushrooms make you giant when eaten..?... I don't like the way you're looking at me now...	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey! Welcome back, how was your flight? Meet anyone interesting?	</connect>
			<connect>	You came! Ready for action?	</connect>
			<connect>	ENTER THE SANDMAN!... er... I mean, my master...	</connect>
			<levelup>	Have you ever wondered where those trumpets come from? Pretty weird huh?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I salute you master! Aww, I forgot I don't have arms again...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Will I every evolve into a strong human like you?... with arms?....	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Urg, I feel a stomach cramp!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*BUURRRRP* Thanks but... NO THANKS	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Oh cruel world, why do you stuff me?... no really, why are you feeding me??	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Do you really hate me that much that you want to kill me from overfeeding? That's cruel...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Woooah, woooah! Wait up! I feel wobbly!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Just a sec...need... to catch... my... breath...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*BUUUURRRRRRPPPPPPP* 'scuse me.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Quick, start feeding yourself like you fed me!	</danger>
			<danger>	... maybe now you'll stop feeding me.	</danger>
			<dead>	Does being resurrected give you exercise? Burp!	</dead>
			<dead>	You were too good for this cruel world~	</dead>
			<dead>	NOOO! I'M NEXT!	</dead>
			<dead>	Please get up? I'll get eaten if I'm left alone too long.	</dead>
			<stand>	No, no! Keep moving! I can feel my legs failing... oh wait, forgot I don't have legs again.	</stand>
			<stand>	You think a parasite might help me lose weight?	</stand>
			<stand>	Phew... I love doing absolutely nothing!	</stand>
			<stand>	I don't think I can keep it down... I need an Acolyte fast... I'm gonna *bweuragh*... sorry...	</stand>
			<connect>	Good news! That exercise plan is really working! Mmmm!	</connect>
			<connect>	Alright! I'm pumped, let me get'em! after I nap...	</connect>
			<connect>	Someone please help me, my master is trying to feed me till I explode!! It's cruel I tell you! CRUEL!!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Is that my stomach?... Oh, no, it's just you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	What? I missed that... just kidding, CONGRATULATIONS!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You are a magnificent sight to behold, but I wonder if all this magnificence is going to your big fat head like my big fat body.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</spore>
	<poison_spore>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	That was good... but I like moss more...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I don't like mushrooms because they look exactly like me.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Are you going to sell all of your items!? You could always give me a bit...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I am starving why do we always hunt!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Looks like you're hurt.	</danger>
			<danger>	Ow! when you are dead can I have all your food?	</danger>
			<dead>	This no time to sleep! I'm STARVED!	</dead>
			<dead>	You forgot to feed me...now what're you going to do?	</dead>
			<stand>	You don't have any spare moss do you?	</stand>
			<stand>	Sooo hungry... may I please eat that novice over there?	</stand>
			<stand>	Just standing makes me hungry!	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back! I hope you where getting me food?	</connect>
			<connect>	Have you went on vacation? I'm starving!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yay! I knew you could do it... btw food?...	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Yum! That hits the spot.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	You know, a few of those items you just got look really tasty...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Staring at porings eating stuff makes me hungry.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh no... if you die who will feed me?	</danger>
			<dead>	Stop playing dead! Lets get out there and get me some food!	</dead>
			<dead>	Nyummy!	</dead>
			<stand>	Who are we waiting for? Did you order some food?	</stand>
			<stand>	Ah, the novice.. the other, other white meat...	</stand>
			<stand>	Oh the hunger! THE HUNGER!!	</stand>
			<connect>	You're here! Want to go out and hunt us some fried mushroom spore?	</connect>
			<connect>	Newbies, it's what's for breakfast.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Hooray! Lets go out and celebrate with some food!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Why don't you carry more food for me to eat? Don't you care about me? I don't think you do.	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Oh boy that was my favorite! You're the best owner.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Tasty... except the mushrooms... THAT'S CANNIBALISM!!!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	This is fun, I love to hunt with you.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Quick! Hide under my cap, I'll protect you!	</danger>
			<dead>	That's ok, we'll just come back down and get him back! Lets go!	</dead>
			<dead>	*sniff* Why do you do this to me? Do you have any idea how much stress this causes me?	</dead>
			<dead>	Didn't you get enough sleep last night? Stop napping...	</dead>
			<stand>	We should start moving, I think my poison is killing the plant life around here...	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm not like other poison spores, they always attack no matter what.	</stand>
			<connect>	You're back! I saw a scary poring while you were gone... but I ate it... *burp*	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey! Let us go kill... except for spores... don't be mean.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Way to go! I have the strongest owner ever!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	If you keep feeding me my cap might not fit me in the morning...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Make sure I don't get fat, ok?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Oh, I'm kind of full. Want to take a rest?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Careful! Do you have any healing items on you?	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh no! Does anyone have a yggdrasil leaf? It's ok, you'll be ok.	</dead>
			<stand>	Hey! Use my cap as a seat instead of standing around... I don't mind, really!	</stand>
			<connect>	I missed you!~	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yes! Lets go for another! And another!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yahoo! Let's celebrate!.. when I'm not feeling so sick...	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Hey! Quit feeding me or I might explode! You don't want a poison spore all over you do you!?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	If you're looking for more food for me just keep it in your pocket... don't even try to feed me!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Good thing I don't fight... I'd probably get eaten first!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Ha ha, now its time for you to eat... well?	</danger>
			<danger>	... Please don't die on me... it's not too late...heal yourself...	</danger>
			<dead>	I told you to heal yourself, why don't you listen to me?	</dead>
			<dead>	...Told you so. Is there a yggdrasil leaf in the area?! Someone? Please?	</dead>
			<dead>	I wonder if I can resurrect you somehow with my poison...	</dead>
			<stand>	If we're just going to be standing around I think I'm going to rest.	</stand>
			<connect>	I'm so glad that you're back! I was afraid I would have to talk to the Kafras for company.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yay, you got your level... now its time to go out and get mine.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	What? exercise? Oh please! Find me a nice moss bed.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</poison_spore>
	<pecopeco>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	This is good. How bout some more?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm going to report you to SPCA... I mean the GMs for animal abuse!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you for the snack, but I'm ready to have a real meal now.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	What's this? Bird feed?! I don't need no stinkin' BIRD FEED... okay, maybe a little...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Don't ride me on my back, it's degrading.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Too hungry.....no strength.....wait a second is that meat? MEEEEEAAAAT!!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Could you sell some of those jellopies and buy me some food?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Uhh, you look like you could use some rest... mind feeding me while you rest?	</danger>
			<danger>	I heard human flesh is a very good source for protein...	</danger>
			<danger>	For not feeding me, I hope you die!	</danger>
			<dead>	Sunbathing? You're always leaving me out of all the fun!	</dead>
			<dead>	*Sheesh* Thanks a lot, now what do I do?...I knew I shouldn't trust a human...	</dead>
			<dead>	Welcome to my soon to be world...	</dead>
			<dead>	Wow, you're really flexible! I never knew you could bend your arms like that! Uh, I hope they're not broken..	</dead>
			<stand>	Everything is starting to look like bird food... is that bad?	</stand>
			<stand>	You know maybe I can lose some weight....	</stand>
			<stand>	*Growwl* Oh don't worry, it's not a monster, it's just my stomach.	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you mind scratching my beak? I feel an itch.	</stand>
			<connect>	Remember, no free rides, payment in food accepted.	</connect>
			<connect>	I waited a long time for you, I'm starving.	</connect>
			<connect>	Greetings, are you feeling as hungry as I am?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Alright, time to party *does the chicken dance*	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Way to go... can I eat it?	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	This is so good. What's in it?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks a lot but I will never get my old weight back if you don't feed me regularly...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I was thinking about cooking parts of you... but I guess I'll have to wait for another chance.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmm, that was some tasty food. It reminds me of some yggdrasil berry feed I had once....	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Yeah, I have wings, why don't I use them? That's none of your business...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You know, all this hunting is starting to annoy me, I need food you know.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Don't die on me now, you have not told me where the food is yet!	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh great I have a master who is both cheap, hungry, and almost dead....	</danger>
			<dead>	... oh, great, die... wonderful, now what's next?	</dead>
			<dead>	Typical he forgot to feed me, see you in heaven... or... that other place.	</dead>
			<dead>	You won't mind me cooking you, will do you?	</dead>
			<stand>	Hmm, why are people looking at me like that?	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you hear that ? Yes, that's my stomach, it is talking to you	</stand>
			<stand>	Can't you see what I am doing? I am trying to swallow air, I need to fill my stomach with something!	</stand>
			<connect>	Good day! Weather is fine is it not?	</connect>
			<connect>	Ahhh here comes my food bank...	</connect>
			<levelup>	This calls for a celebration! Can I have that food again?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Something's different...YOU WENT AND PARTIED WITHOUT ME?! NOOOO!	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	*crunch* Good stuff!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Can't you give me something other your leftovers? How cheap...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Wow, you do good damage at your level!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Lock and load, time to lock and load.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Do you have the munchies? Maybe I shouldn't have ate that green plant I saw earlier, I thought it looked funny...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh my. You are out of shape. Eat up!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, red doesn't look too bad on you, what do you think?	</danger>
			<danger>	Run Fore..s..er...master...ruuuun!	</danger>
			<dead>	Uhh, you may want to get off the ground. I do believe you are lying in someone's doo-dah... and don't look at me!	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, I tried to warn you, but you ignored me... so don't say I didn't warn you!	</dead>
			<dead>	Oops sorry I accidentally stepped on your dead body...	</dead>
			<stand>	I am a good bird. I am a good bird. I am a good bird.	</stand>
			<stand>	Yes yes nice weather, Let's make a picnic! Woo Hoo!	</stand>
			<stand>	...ok this could take a while...	</stand>
			<connect>	You know what I found out... I can't fly, I'm USELESS!!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hop on my back and let's hunt!	</connect>
			<connect>	You know, I know I'm supposed to carry you around, but how about we switch for an hour?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Just a couple more for a strong built body!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Let's get this party started! Do a little dance.. make a little... c'mon, start dancin!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Ok. Now that food is starting to fill me up a bit too well.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ahhhh I could feel the love choking down my throat right now....	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I hope you get another level again. That was pretty exciting!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Damn I have to lose weight....or find a new master...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Bring it, I'm ready to kick some butt	</hunting>
			<danger>	Drink more fluids! I think you are getting sick!	</danger>
			<danger>	Danger! Danger! Fight on...or ruuuuuuunnn!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, um, not to seem like I'm telling you what to do but, aren't you supposed to be the one killing the monster?	</danger>
			<dead>	Can someone resurrect this person? He doesn't deserve this!	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't ever think of sleeping at a time like this...	</dead>
			<dead>	Aw, look who fell down... come on little one, time to get up. GET UP!!!	</dead>
			<stand>	I always see people starting at me... do I have something on my feathers? Can you check for me?	</stand>
			<stand>	You know, I heard it's good to get some exercise after you eat a good sized meal, let's go jogging!	</stand>
			<stand>	Can we use that treasure map I found yet? Oh, oops, that was supposed to be a secret, sorry...	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey you're back! Lets travel together again. Where to boss?	</connect>
			<connect>	I am here on behalf of all Peco Peco's to say, I like it when you scratch my beak.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Bling Bling, who's 'da man now!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice one!! Look, my Peco Peco friends, it's my MAN!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey, move over I want to take a picture of the scenery...	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	So much food? Must get bigger stomach!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Is this how you display your love? By starving me then stuffing me?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I'm so full I can't move!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ugh, I think I'm going to explode... careful, I might get some on you.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Damn, stop whining, it's just a flesh wound, you pansy...	</hunting>
			<danger>	What a mess! Would you mind cleaning that up afterwards?	</danger>
			<danger>	Wait here! I'll go get my other friends!	</danger>
			<danger>	Whew, you may want to let that bush air out a bit before walking over there!	</danger>
			<danger>	Wow what a nice fountain you make... red water, wait is that normal?	</danger>
			<dead>	Wow, you look awful...would you like some ice cream?	</dead>
			<dead>	Damn it, I'm too late...shouldn't have ate so much....	</dead>
			<dead>	May god have mercy on your soul...	</dead>
			<dead>	It is your fault and only your fault!! If you didn't feed me so much, I would have run faster!	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm bored... c'mon get a move on...	</stand>
			<stand>	What stinks here...?Oops, excuse me, my bad.	</stand>
			<stand>	You can stand all you want but I think I will pass. I sit and you stand.	</stand>
			<connect>	Good you're back!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey, I can't see my feet!! Can you find them for me?	</connect>
			<connect>	Damn it!!! You just ruined my extremely secret evil plan to take over the world! FOILED AGAIN!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi!! Can't tell which Peco Peco I am? I'm the fat one!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Another level? Don't you want to give me some?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Ok, you have gained a level, let's rest.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I could have helped if I wasn't so heavy...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I guess when you level up, you have a bigger capacity for your stomach....but we don't level up!	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</pecopeco>
	<smokie>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	My little stomach... I feel so weak... I'm not sure I can go on!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks but I have had better from the highway.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Stop staring at me already! I know I look funny when I eat too fast!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks, but if I don't get more food, I'll start dropping dead Raccoon Leafs!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	*Sniff* *Sniff* I smell something funny.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Shiny thing! Lemme have it! Its mine...my...precious...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Finally we're hunting something to eat...right?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'd eat some of that loot but, my mom told me its bad to eat off the ground.	</hunting>
			<danger>	*grumble*, hey you need to feed me before you die.	</danger>
			<danger>	You're almost dead, feed me and I might help.	</danger>
			<danger>	My tummy feels as empty as your health bar...	</danger>
			<dead>	I could've been more alert had you given me something to eat.	</dead>
			<dead>	Now who will feed me!	</dead>
			<dead>	Just go and die when I'm starving! Yeesh!	</dead>
			<dead>	Where's your wallet...?	</dead>
			<stand>	I can't stand being hungry... sometimes I wonder why I stick around.	</stand>
			<stand>	This is boring! Where are the shiny things!	</stand>
			<stand>	I feel like I could eat dirt I'm so... hungry...	</stand>
			<stand>	Um, hello? Can I get something to eat now? Even my tail is getting thinner.	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm done exercising where's the food?	</stand>
			<stand>	Stop wasting oxygen and get me some food!	</stand>
			<connect>	Whoopee, where's the grub!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey! Lets go to that alley for shiny things!	</connect>
			<connect>	Well look who's here. Going to give me something to eat at last..?	</connect>
			<connect>	*TIP OF THE DAY* FEED ME!	</connect>
			<levelup>	You filled yourself with experience, now fill me with food!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Great job! Give me food!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congrats, let's go out to eat... you're buying.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	*cough*feed me*cough* Hey, nice one!	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Ah, finally!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks! Better than what I find in a trashcan!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I feel a bit better now, thanks.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Put another shrimp on the BBQ!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Oh yea! MY favorite... where's the rest? Did you skip out on the good stuff?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Something smells good.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Those items aren't shiny! Find more shiny things!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Uh.. *tug*tug* I'm hungry, feed me please?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Wow, all that shiny loot, can I have some? Maybe I can buy my own food...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Alert! Alert! Danger, Danger Will Robinson, Danger!	</danger>
			<danger>	Watch out! That almost killed the food provider... I mean master!	</danger>
			<danger>	Fwahahaha! I'll try to scare it away, you should run and maybe get me some food while you're at it.	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, if he does tear you apart, ask him if I can have whatever food is in your pockets.	</danger>
			<danger>	NOT IN THE FACE!!! NOT IN THE FACE!!	</danger>
			<dead>	Gah, why did you have to go and die so fast like that?	</dead>
			<dead>	Get up! I'm still hungry!	</dead>
			<dead>	... *sits on you and whimpers*	</dead>
			<dead>	Okay.. you've slept enough ya lazy bum.	</dead>
			<stand>	Don't mind me, I'm sniffing the air for possible nearby food I can steal.	</stand>
			<stand>	Can I climb on your shoulders?	</stand>
			<stand>	*kicks feet in dirt* Hungry... and bored... which is worse? Neither...	</stand>
			<connect>	You're just in time! Let's eat.	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello! Can I ride your shoulders today?	</connect>
			<connect>	Have anything special for me?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Outstanding work there pal.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yes! Let's get better to get better shiny things!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oooooh! Shiiinnnnyyyy....	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I SEE SHINEY!!	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Delicious.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yay! Apples! Time to wash them!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Give me a few minutes. I need to clean myself up for my big date after that meal.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Aahh.. *pats tummy*	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I feel so good, I feel like I can take on a Bapho... junior... maybe, don't hold me to that..	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Whee! Kick it's booty!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Quick, use the special move I taught you!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Secret smokie power!... oh wait, I'm still working on that one.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Go! Go! Go! Get out of the danger zone!	</danger>
			<danger>	I'll save you!! ... quick, HIDE!!!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hit that heal button faster!	</danger>
			<danger>	Super smokie to the rescue!	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't leave me! Noooooooooo!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Please get up, I'll die too!	</dead>
			<dead>	*pounces on stomach*... wake up... ...p.. l... e... a... s... e...?	</dead>
			<dead>	Stop pretending to be a carpet!	</dead>
			<dead>	Can you hear me? Please response to me!	</dead>
			<stand>	Let me at me... aren't I the cutest thing you've ever seen?	</stand>
			<stand>	Think we could get me a new bandana?	</stand>
			<stand>	La la la... *runs around in circles*	</stand>
			<stand>	Last time I stood this much, was at the taxidermist's	</stand>
			<stand>	How's my fur? Still shiny?	</stand>
			<stand>	Can't you think of something interesting to talk about, you're getting boring.	</stand>
			<stand>	OH MY GOD...Where is my leaf?!?! What did you do with it...YOU STOLE IT! THIEF! THIEF!	</stand>
			<connect>	Nice to see you again. Let's rock.	</connect>
			<connect>	Yay! You're back! There was someone who wanted to talk to you, what was his name... hmm...	</connect>
			<connect>	hee hee! Can't see me *hide!!*	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yay for us, yay for you, yayayay.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You are the 1337! Let's go show off for the others!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I heard trumpets!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Ah! You're just too kind...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ah! Good lizard on a stick!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ooooh.. I'm all happy full now! *basks in a sun ray*	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I feel like I'm carrying an iron ball in my stomach.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Let's go over there! I see something shiny!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*cheers and dances* Rah rah, sis boom bah!	</hunting>
			<danger>	You better watch yourself, you look like you're hurt.	</danger>
			<danger>	Let me kick it! I'll get it for you!	</danger>
			<danger>	Can I help you somehow? Just tell me, anything I'll do it, or try...	</danger>
			<danger>	Damn, if only I hadn't eaten that vitata card....	</danger>
			<dead>	Help! Help! Priest! Resurrection! Anyone!	</dead>
			<dead>	NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	*paws at you gently* Don't leave me...please don't leave me...	</dead>
			<dead>	STEEEELLLLAAAAAAAHHH!!!!!	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm just stretching my stomach.	</stand>
			<stand>	So, what do you look for in a partner? Anything like me?	</stand>
			<stand>	Iwubjoo!!! Iwubjoo-sooooomuch!	</stand>
			<stand>	I wonder what happens when Smokies forget how to hide..	</stand>
			<connect>	Alright, Let's go!	</connect>
			<connect>	My master's back, yayayay!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hurrah! Time to explore some new trees to live in!	</connect>
			<connect>	Ready to shake it, shake shake shake it like a.... what's a Polaroid?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Woo! Woo! Woo! You go!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Weeeeee! We can do anything!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I'd jump for joy but I might break the floor...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Time to head back to the hacienda?	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	I'm your pet, not a garbage disposal!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm stuffed... or are you thinking about becoming a taxidermist?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Are you crazy?! I am going to burst!!!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Wait up, you're moving too fast ... ugh.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can't move... too heavy... I feel bloated...*erp*	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*rubs tummy* Awr.. go, you... aah...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Arghhhh! Your life is in danger!	</danger>
			<danger>	Eeeek!! Hide!! HIDE!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	I'd help, but oval shaped is in, and I don't want to ruin my form, can't disappoint my ladies.	</danger>
			<dead>	Ugh, if I weren't so full, I could've done... something.. ah who am I kidding, I'm lazy right now.	</dead>
			<dead>	I tried to give you my yams, but you didn't want them...	</dead>
			<dead>	*pokes tip of your nose - whimpering*	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, do you got any of that weight loss stuff?	</dead>
			<dead>	I need to teach you how to hide faster...	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm so stuffed, carry me?	</stand>
			<stand>	Pet me! I'm snuggly soft!	</stand>
			<stand>	So full.. so tired---*falls over* Zzz... Zzz...	</stand>
			<connect>	Wooohooo! Game on!	</connect>
			<connect>	Yay! The master has returned. I missed you and that yoyo tried to sell me to a Bigfoot!	</connect>
			<connect>	Yaaay! You've come back! *jumps in arms*	</connect>
			<connect>	Feed me again, and I will punch you in the head!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey!! Do you know about any good weight loss programs?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congrats! Now if only I can work out myself to be as strong as you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I wish I could be as great as you!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Where are those trumpets coming from??	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</smokie>
	<yoyo>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	I'm so hungry, don't you have any of those banana's left over?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'd fling something at you, but I haven't eaten anything for a while.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You take way too long to feed me, you want an angry yoyo on your hands?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You call that a banana? I need to edumacate you... yeah you hear me... don't make fun of me.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I think I hear Bapho near by!... oh wait, false alarm, that was just my stomach.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Kill it quickly, I'm hungry!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Let's feed the hungry yoyo, shall we?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Banana....banana...ba..ba..banana... ugn, banana-nana-nana!...	</hunting>
			<danger>	If you had fed me earlier, I might be helping you right now.	</danger>
			<danger>	FEED THE YOYO!	</danger>
			<danger>	Pretty soon, we'll be running this place, just you watch...	</danger>
			<dead>	The age of yoyos begins! Where's that banana you had...	</dead>
			<dead>	Haw-haw...	</dead>
			<dead>	There was this green leaf I ate earlier, was that supposed to be for you?	</dead>
			<stand>	Feed the yoyo!	</stand>
			<stand>	Don't make me angry, you don't want to know what I can do when I'm angry... feed me.	</stand>
			<stand>	BA-A-A-A-NA-A-A-A-NA-A-A-A... *drools*	</stand>
			<connect>	Hi*food*how*food*are you?*food*	</connect>
			<connect>	I wish there were a banana tree around here.	</connect>
			<connect>	Wassap... how bout a banana for your buddy?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Hey! Let's celebrate my year with a banana!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good for you...now FEED me or risk a pissed yoyo.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You ate my banana didn't you, c'mon fess up!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I'd be more impressed if you remembered to feed me on time...	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	You done with yours?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	What, that was it?...fine...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	... pffsh... this is it? I thought there was more...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey, I heard about this place that has really ripe bananas... should look into buying from there.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey, do you think we'll find anything edible here?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Heey, this is fuuun, we're all going to DIE aren't we?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Do you think they eat yoyo meat...?	</hunting>
			<danger>	You're lookin' like you need help... well, look like I need a banana, so we're even.	</danger>
			<danger>	Ah, relax, it's only 1%... what're you so worried about?	</danger>
			<dead>	HA... look at you, lying there... that's pathetic... and I'm hungry... ... ah crud.	</dead>
			<dead>	It's fun to watch you die...	</dead>
			<stand>	Hey, look over there, is that GOD-POING? Oh wait, I'm seeing things... hey, where'd the banana's go?	</stand>
			<stand>	*Yawn* I had more fun watching you die.	</stand>
			<stand>	Grab me some banana chips while you're up will you?	</stand>
			<stand>	Which do you like better, the bananas... or the banana pie?... I'm a pie yoyo myself .	</stand>
			<stand>	I'll check your hair after I eat... or maybe I can just check your hair and eat at the same time, c'mere.	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey, let's go get some of those banana's I stashed away.	</connect>
			<connect>	I thought you'd forgotten about me, I'm hungry you get me something so I can eat?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey! I heard this great recipe for grilled banana's, let's go give it a test cook.	</connect>
			<levelup>	HOO-AH! See, nice goin', let's celebrate! Banana's all around! ... You're buying.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh....gee... you get a level, what do I get, nothing... not even a banana...	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Oh my gosh, you remembered! Thank you, thank you, thank you.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmm, that was great, now I feel guilty about keeping some of your loot.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Think we'll find any good bananas?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I sense something strong in this one...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can you teach me how to do that? I'm feelin' a bit useless.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	If I rode on your shoulder, would you hate me?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey you're lookin' great... don't screw it up.	</danger>
			<danger>	You, um, yeah, life would be, uh, the thing you're missing...	</danger>
			<dead>	Can anyone spare a resurrection? I'll dance to pay for it...	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, c'mon get up, we're not done playin' yet.	</dead>
			<stand>	Hey, I found an earring... can I keep it, where does it go... on my ear?	</stand>
			<stand>	Tag, you're it... okay, now... chase me...bah, you're boring.	</stand>
			<stand>	I know that look... don't complain... you know I look good.	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey, I remember you. Giver of bananas! Hail!	</connect>
			<connect>	I have this itch... but I can't reach it, can you?	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh wow, I thought you had forgotten about me! Um... don't look in your bag until after I... um... clean it...	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey, so where'd you go? A date? Ooh tell me all about it. :3	</connect>
			<levelup>	Do the yoyo! *dances with his tail spinning*	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Sweet, was that an angel over your head?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I've been thinking about wearing a leather print, what do you think?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I heard a horn, does that mean we're late for something?.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	AAHH!!.. oh that scared me, what was that?	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	No thanks, I'm on a diet!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'll eat it, I won't like it... okay maybe I will, but I'm still full...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I hate to admit, I've had enough bananas... for now... that doesn't mean I'm gonna' stop eating them!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Heeey...slow down, some of us are full here...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I need to teach you the faster mode of travel... trees...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm getting fat and lazy, c'mon hurry it up.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You think I can get the banana-bender 2000, it's a great workout machine.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Uh oh, I can't see my toes... am I gaining weight?	</hunting>
			<danger>	You're gonna' heal right?.... RIGHT??	</danger>
			<danger>	So, about that heal.... comin' anytime soon is it?	</danger>
			<danger>	Need a heal over here, c'mon... someone help the cute yoyo's master out!	</danger>
			<dead>	So much for good luck....	</dead>
			<dead>	I know this is supposed to be my year, but that doesn't mean I'm gonna' fight when I'm full.	</dead>
			<dead>	I saw you just died. How do you come back alive so much times? I thought humans only have one life?	</dead>
			<stand>	Who wants to pet me? It's good luck... honest... c'mon, rub my belly... watch the tail...	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you think I'm a good pet? Honestly... don't ya just love me?	</stand>
			<stand>	I know I'm a yoyo but... the priestesses... woo....and the female assassins... the huntresses... ack, I love them all!	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey, welcome back... um, the... I... ugh, I'	</connect>
			<connect>	Good to have you back, it was getting too quiet!	</connect>
			<connect>	What took you so long. I have a hot date with that assassin girl.	</connect>
			<levelup>	WOOT!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Cowabunga!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	LOL, you just need 15 more levels to catch up to that guy there.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	No! no more! well, maybe just a little...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You just don't know when to stop do you!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Eurgh.. Have you even seen a monkey puke?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ugh, I'm going to be the worlds first Sumo wrestler Yoyo!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Dude, I love bananas, but do I look like a Bigfoot to you?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	er.. ? I'm feeling a little... stuffed here.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Gahhhh, 1 banana 2 banana, 300 hundred banana. Have you lost your mind?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Chunky yoyo to the rescue!	</danger>
			<danger>	This may end up tragic...	</danger>
			<danger>	Throw me! Knock them out with my weight!	</danger>
			<danger>	Umm can you like, hang in there? I need to go... um, yeah... b'cause I'm so full.	</danger>
			<dead>	I am one dead yoyo...	</dead>
			<dead>	I need to go poop now... oh I'll just poop on you... don't move.	</dead>
			<stand>	Ok, time for pushups! 1..2..3..4...	</stand>
			<stand>	Where's the restroom. Take me to the restroom. Is there a restroom here?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey! How's it hanging'?	</connect>
			<connect>	I can't wear my fine suede shoes!	</connect>
			<connect>	That poring called me fatty. *sniff*sniff * You feed me to much.	</connect>
			<levelup>	I'd dance, but I'm too lazy.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	WOW, good job. Take me to the gym. I'm so fat!!	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</yoyo>
	<ork_warrior>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Me thank stranger.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks for the grub bub!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*CHOMP*CHOMP*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you stranger, you look tasty yourself, stop working out so much.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I see you notice me. I thank you for your gratitude.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Human would be easier to kill for food then monster.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Me Orc, me kill, me eat, me eat a lot!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm going hunting, back in a while.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I want more food, I need to be big and strong for Orc lady to want me!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Orc need munch-ums bad.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Orc notice that you would be easier to kill and eat right now.	</danger>
			<danger>	Do I need to help you, stranger?	</danger>
			<danger>	Hmm... if you die... can I chew on you a little then? Just nibble a bit? I'm hungry you know!	</danger>
			<danger>	Orc say you look bad.	</danger>
			<dead>	Hur hur, the prey kills itself. Time to feast.	</dead>
			<dead>	*sniff* *sniff* Ewwww. No good to eat.	</dead>
			<dead>	What happened to you?	</dead>
			<dead>	Oops... hmmm... wonder if he will notice if I take a little bite out of a leg or something?	</dead>
			<dead>	How could you die stranger? Orc thought you were good.	</dead>
			<stand>	Orc's legs tired from standing, give Orc food to pass the time.	</stand>
			<stand>	May I ask what you are so serious about?	</stand>
			<stand>	Orc really want munch-ums.	</stand>
			<stand>	Orc want some fresh grilled meat, you look good...	</stand>
			<connect>	Good, looks like Orc can start stalking you again for food.	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello. Do I have to beg for food today?	</connect>
			<connect>	*grunt* Food today? Yes?	</connect>
			<connect>	Orc happy to see you again.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Eh, Orc still stronger.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Food, Stranger, Orc need food... oh... congratulation.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Have time to share food with Orc now?	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Orc thanks you.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*chomp chomp*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yum yum.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Orc thanks human for food.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey, can't human share with Orc?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You go ahead I'll start the fire...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Orc need munch-ums.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Human look so good today.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Human's wounds look serious..	</danger>
			<danger>	Human need heal stuffs.	</danger>
			<dead>	Buh, if Orc wasn't hungry, Orc would have helped...	</dead>
			<dead>	*sniff*sniff* Dead human...	</dead>
			<dead>	Human body smell... not good.	</dead>
			<stand>	Orc is bored, food would be nice...	</stand>
			<stand>	Orc want munch-ums.	</stand>
			<stand>	Human sleep now.	</stand>
			<connect>	Good day to human, when is lunch?	</connect>
			<connect>	Humans are friends, not food.	</connect>
			<connect>	Human again.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Orc is glad for you, though Orc could beat human in a 1 on 1.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Human owe Orc food.	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Orc thanks you kindly.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Orc like candy...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Orc thinks your skills are great.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Orc fight too?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Orc suggests you find healing.	</danger>
			<danger>	Orc need bigger axe!	</danger>
			<dead>	You should have eaten some meat while battling.	</dead>
			<dead>	*sniff* *sniff* friend is dead thing now.	</dead>
			<dead>	Human body smell really not good. Orc leave to home.	</dead>
			<stand>	Orc is somewhat bored...	</stand>
			<stand>	Look at me, I'm big! And strong!! Not to mention green!!! Orc Lady is definitely going to like me!!	</stand>
			<stand>	Orc be Orc Hero someday?	</stand>
			<connect>	Orc greets you with honor.	</connect>
			<connect>	Orc say Hi	</connect>
			<levelup>	Orc sees your strength growing, we should battle one day.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Orc know you could do!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Orc thanks, but Orc is good for now.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Orc full *burp*	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Orc thinks the best time to battle is when Orc's stomach is full of meat!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Orc look fat?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Please, take the monster feed for yourself, Orc fine.	</danger>
			<danger>	Orc see you bleeding, Orc get healers!	</danger>
			<dead>	Orc thinks you forgot about monster feed..	</dead>
			<stand>	Orc thinks we should go hunting instead of getting fat... lazy	</stand>
			<stand>	We got to keep moving master, just standing around no impress Orc lady at all...	</stand>
			<stand>	Human, waiting human friends?... no Orc friends?	</stand>
			<stand>	Orc need friend... Orc lonely... maybe Orc Lady come by and be good friend?	</stand>
			<connect>	Orc greets you, Orc wanted company.	</connect>
			<connect>	*sniff*sniff* Friend!	</connect>
			<connect>	Orc greets you, Orc found an Orc Lady while you gone!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Ha ha! Friend grows ever stronger!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Orc salute human's victory!	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Do you want Orc to get fat and out of shape?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Orc no want food any more. Orc allow human take all.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Orc feels to heavy from all this food.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Wait Orc move slow.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Uh, please, take the monster feed, Orc does not need any right now..	</danger>
			<danger>	Orc need vomit food for human friend?	</danger>
			<dead>	Ugh, can someone resurrect Orc's friend? Orc to full to try.	</dead>
			<dead>	Human feel hung-over too?	</dead>
			<dead>	Orc called Orc fellows to burry human body.	</dead>
			<stand>	Sure, you feed Orc to much and then you make Orc stand around, get fat and lazy... damn you.	</stand>
			<stand>	Orc want sleep.	</stand>
			<stand>	Orc Lady left me, said Orc too fat.	</stand>
			<connect>	Hello, Orc hasn't been so full in years.	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello, what do you say we burn some calories before Orc Lady sees me fat? Eh? Good friend? Happy master?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Orc is happy for you, Orc should try and loose some weight to get to your level once again.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</ork_warrior>
	<munak>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	.... can I have more food please? Being dead, then an undead then die of starvation can't be good for you...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	About time, living being...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks mortal. I really needed that.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	So you have time to kill innocent creatures, but no time giving me a meal?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Living being... you better watch your back...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	......	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You know, I am so much more stronger than you...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	All this bouncing on my legs is starting to hurt...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Being alive is so overrated... soon you'll have an end to your suffering.	</danger>
			<danger>	...Mortal...you're in great danger....	</danger>
			<danger>	My poor master hasn't been eating right...	</danger>
			<danger>	Are you trying to join me on my side?	</danger>
			<dead>	....Can I get some chow now	</dead>
			<dead>	I will have your body... It's time to feed!	</dead>
			<dead>	Sucks to be you...	</dead>
			<dead>	...where is my food at?	</dead>
			<stand>	...Give me one good reason why I shouldn't tear your apart and devour you?	</stand>
			<stand>	Just because I am undead doesn't mean you can stop feeding me...	</stand>
			<stand>	You don't seem to use your hands... could I have feast on one of them?	</stand>
			<stand>	Can you see through me? tell me the truth.	</stand>
			<stand>	Ooh.. The sun is too bright for me!	</stand>
			<stand>	......	</stand>
			<connect>	...Nice weather we're having... let's go eat...	</connect>
			<connect>	I am hungry living being...	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi, feed me now or I will be forced to kill you.	</connect>
			<connect>	Who are you again?	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh, it's you again.	</connect>
			<levelup>	*Squeeeals* Oh! I'm not dead! Oh.. umm... congrats?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good for you... now feed me...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Level up? Maybe we could celebrate it by giving me one of your body parts?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good job I guess...	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	More!!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I needed that. Now I have another year to live...be dead...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks... you know... you don't look as tasty anymore.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Another dim sum down the hatch...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	You might regret turning your back on me...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You know I can fight pretty well for a dead girl...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I smell death coming closer....	</hunting>
			<hunting>	... My pleasure is your pain..	</hunting>
			<danger>	This is a sign... the evil tells you to buy food... some for you... and more for me.	</danger>
			<danger>	Sorry mortal, but my amulet can't revive players.	</danger>
			<danger>	We are almost in the same state, being dead and all...	</danger>
			<danger>	You are in grave danger...	</danger>
			<dead>	This is why the living should die... they die anyway.	</dead>
			<dead>	Now we can be friends for... life..?	</dead>
			<dead>	So sad, I liked you enough as it was when you were alive...	</dead>
			<dead>	Your pain... is my pleasure.	</dead>
			<stand>	Hmm... you seem different... like... food...	</stand>
			<stand>	Can we go to the Payon caves? I want to see my friends.	</stand>
			<stand>	Why stand, when you can hop ?	</stand>
			<stand>	If Munak is useful, you'd keep her right? *smiles and sways back and forth*	</stand>
			<stand>	I need some human blood... I mean food...	</stand>
			<connect>	F-o-o-d! N-e-e-d f-o-o-d	</connect>
			<connect>	I want blood... I mean... give me something to eat. Oh yes... hi.	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh! I just thought of something I wanted to tell you... ... I forgot...	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi!*dances a jig and smiles*	</connect>
			<levelup>	Nice for you, now to feed, yes?.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	One step closer to being strong...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	It's nice to see you growing so strong...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	... ???	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	I'm satisfied... but a little more wouldn't hurt.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you... this is very good...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Are we dieting..?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	This is even better then that Magnolia I ate in Payon....	</feeding>
			<hunting>	You lead... I shall follow behind.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Please, protect me if something tries to attack me...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	For someone who is alive, you fight really well....	</hunting>
			<hunting>	........eh...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Don't worry, if you die, it isn't that bad. I mean, look at me.	</danger>
			<danger>	Please watch out, you probably won't like being dead.	</danger>
			<danger>	Would you donate some blood to me?	</danger>
			<danger>	...better eat some reds.	</danger>
			<dead>	See? It wasn't THAT bad, was it?	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't leave me behind! *tearful eyes*	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't go towards the light!	</dead>
			<dead>	...You die SOO much... when are you going to stay that way?...	</dead>
			<stand>	Can we move? My legs are growing stiff again...	</stand>
			<stand>	Bongun is a hunk...but I think my master is cuter than him... shh don't tell him.	</stand>
			<stand>	Let's go shopping! Oh please.....?	</stand>
			<stand>	Where do ghost buy their food? At the GHOST-ery store!.. oh I kill me... uh, wait that was funny too...	</stand>
			<stand>	What you say we go visit the graveyard? I miss my other sisters... they need a master like you who can feed all of us!	</stand>
			<connect>	*poke* Those people are staring at me...	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello there, how about you pull this ancient scripture off my head?	</connect>
			<connect>	I was wondering when you would come to see me..	</connect>
			<connect>	I miss my Bongun...?	</connect>
			<connect>	... there you are.	</connect>
			<levelup>	We must thank the evil, they have blessed you with unholy strength!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! I'd give you red envelopes of vast wealth... a hug would do instead right, honey?*hugs tightly and smiles*	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Now...you happy? ...Ok...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	...eep, was that an Angel!? *hiss*	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	That's enough, being undead doesn't mean I can't overeat.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmm.. all this food is not good for my body...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm feeling quite plump. I actually didn't think I could still get plump...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	... enough... please...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	So much prey... so little time.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	So much food... how do you expect me to keep hopping like this master?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	....I want to join you...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	...enough is enough....	</hunting>
			<danger>	Owwie! Doesn't that hurt?	</danger>
			<danger>	Watch out, you're almost dead. Well... heal if you want, being dead isn't so bad.	</danger>
			<danger>	I would heal you, but it would be against the Munak's code.	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh dear, you're bleeding! Let me get you a handkerchief to wipe you with.	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh well... how about I teach you how to live as an undead?	</dead>
			<dead>	Whatever, tell me when your ready to cross over. I need to digest.	</dead>
			<dead>	If you don't make it through, I want to be buried with you..	</dead>
			<dead>	Why did you have to be a hero...	</dead>
			<dead>	... Oh well....	</dead>
			<stand>	Should I make friends with a Sohee? They look pretty...	</stand>
			<stand>	If you are to wait, at least sit. We shall take them out when you're ready.	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you think this ancient robe makes me look fat?	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you think my hips are too big?	</stand>
			<stand>	You know. We undead aren't all that bad, just misunderstood.	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back Master, shall we be on our way?	</connect>
			<connect>	He loves me, he loves me not..... OH! Didn't see you standing there *blush*	</connect>
			<connect>	Did you miss me? Cause I missed you!	</connect>
			<connect>	*tug*tug* Why, hello there partner!	</connect>
			<levelup>	*pokes the dead monster, turns around, pokes the master* Hey... you wouldn't do that to my Bongun, would you?!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I can feel your strength, it has reached a new level. It is good that both strong beings have come to befriend each other.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Great job! You are the master of disaster!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're on a roll my friend!	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Stop feeding me!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	If I wasn't undead, I'd be dead from over eating.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	While your at it, why don't you cut a hole in my stomach to drain the food out?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Oh my gosh! I can't touch my toes! Not that I could before, but...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I would feed on our prey... but I'm too full.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	How many times do I have to tell you! ....WAIT for me!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I can't keep up!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Sit down and rest Master. I need to rest too... I feel bloated.	</danger>
			<danger>	That's going to leave a mark.	</danger>
			<danger>	You are in trouble...	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh, say hi to all my friends in the afterlife!	</danger>
			<dead>	Master? Master? Get up... please? If you get up, I'll refund some of the food for you to eat. I promise.	</dead>
			<dead>	You got blood all over me! Yeesh! You're buying me new cloths.	</dead>
			<dead>	Um... hello?	</dead>
			<dead>	What am I supposed to do..?	</dead>
			<stand>	Good thing I'm dead... or else I wouldn't be able to withstand being so fat.	</stand>
			<stand>	Why does everyone want to kill me for my hat?	</stand>
			<stand>	This hat is starting to annoy me.	</stand>
			<stand>	Wake up, time to start exercising!	</stand>
			<stand>	A... I... pretty to you? Be honest...	</stand>
			<connect>	I feel fat... I mean, evil shall guide us.	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome.. *pant*... back.. *pant*... I'm out of shape!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi......*yawn*....	</connect>
			<connect>	Nice to see you.	</connect>
			<levelup>	We must continue, continue we must. You and I, we are great!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I am so glad to see you level up..!!...	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</munak>
	<dokebi>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Well, it's about damn time!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yum...growing boys like me need lots of food to grow strong.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I don't care, dead, alive, on the ground, I'll eat it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Let's hope it drops some meat for me!	</hunting>
			<danger>	It looks like you're feeling as bad as I do!	</danger>
			<danger>	RUN AWAY!	</danger>
			<dead>	Serves you right! You best feed me next time.	</dead>
			<dead>	Get up! It's dinnertime...not naptime!	</dead>
			<dead>	I do the sad dance now...	</dead>
			<stand>	We standing right here, cause I'm too hungry to move.	</stand>
			<stand>	Lets go to the butcher.	</stand>
			<stand>	No, that's my real hair color!	</stand>
			<connect>	I missed you...almost as much as I missed my last meal.	</connect>
			<connect>	I thought you'd be right back! I was so hungry...	</connect>
			<connect>	Good you came back, I hope you brought some food with you~	</connect>
			<levelup>	Finally! Can we go eat now?!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I hope to be as strong as you some day~!	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Praise the lord and pass the ketchup!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Tasty Tasty Tasty~	</feeding>
			<hunting>	How about we stop, and have ourselves a picnic?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Shhhhhh, be vewy vewy qwiet....	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope we're looking for a restaurant.	</hunting>
			<danger>	If you gonna eat something now, how about sharing?	</danger>
			<dead>	Now that we're going back to town... can we eat?	</dead>
			<dead>	Only dogs play dead!	</dead>
			<stand>	I think the butcher's shop is that way.	</stand>
			<stand>	Lets smoke the peace pipe!	</stand>
			<stand>	Did you hear growling? Oh, it was just my stomach.	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back! There's a food vender in Prontera, so let's go!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hiya..lets go get some Poring stew.	</connect>
			<connect>	HOHOHO, there's the guy who shoulda fed me earlier!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Watching you level makes me hungry...	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	I COULD eat...But I'm okay.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	This is better than fried Eggyra!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Very tasty~	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Uh oh! Did you hear that?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'll poke 'em wit my horn!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Look out! Look out! He's comin at you again!	</danger>
			<dead>	Get yo' rump up boy!	</dead>
			<stand>	So what are we up to? Cruisin' for a bruisin'?	</stand>
			<stand>	Lets go visit my friend Eggyra!	</stand>
			<stand>	We are best friends, much happy time!	</stand>
			<connect>	WHASSUP!	</connect>
			<levelup>	You the man!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	OoOoOoO you grow big!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Yeah, okay, thanks, I'm good.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ok no more...I will get chubby.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Where's the bathroom at?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	We should have a nap.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I can do some scary voodoo!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Do you think Baphomet really exists? I bet I could take him!	</hunting>
			<danger>	AH! Run! Just run boy!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hide behind me...I will save you~!	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh, you fool!	</dead>
			<dead>	I will avenge your death.	</dead>
			<dead>	You are going to the happy hunting grounds...	</dead>
			<stand>	Let's go somewhere fun!	</stand>
			<stand>	Oh, all this time I thought you were MY pet!	</stand>
			<stand>	Say there mama, where you been all my life?	</stand>
			<stand>	.........................................Huh?	</stand>
			<connect>	Yo whassup!	</connect>
			<connect>	A-ha! So that is where you have been hiding.	</connect>
			<connect>	Where have you been?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Awwwwwwww yeah. That's right!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Sigh, I remember when you were such a little guy...	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Get that out of my face! What's wrong with you?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You go ahead..I had too much lunch.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Man, I need to drop a few pounds.	</hunting>
			<danger>	It's all you man. I'm too fat to help.	</danger>
			<dead>	Yeah, I'm with you. Let's both take a nap.	</dead>
			<dead>	Is it naptime already? I think I will join you.	</dead>
			<stand>	*BURP* excuse me *BURP* excuse me *BURP*	</stand>
			<stand>	You think I'm a child? I'm older then you are!	</stand>
			<connect>	AWWWW man! Not again! I need a break!	</connect>
			<connect>	I was just about to go work out...	</connect>
			<levelup>	Good for you, Can we go home now?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I would jump for joy...but my tummy hurts.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</dokebi>
	<sohee>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Thank you, very much...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks, master haven't you got some food for me?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Master, you're so nice, thank you.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you... can I have some more please...? I'm starving...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I'm so hungry, I could eat a... Munak...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hate all this violence...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Master... hogging all the items for yourself is not very nice, please give some to me, I'm hungry.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Please, watch your health...	</danger>
			<danger>	Maybe you would be better if you rest a little.	</danger>
			<danger>	Master, healing seems like a good idea right now...	</danger>
			<dead>	A tragic ending...	</dead>
			<dead>	Do you want to sleep?	</dead>
			<dead>	Great... now who will I get food from...	</dead>
			<dead>	Master, forgive me, you should have fed me, now I must eat you I'm so hungry.	</dead>
			<stand>	Master, I am quite hungry, please feed me...	</stand>
			<stand>	Master, what...are... you looking at?	</stand>
			<stand>	... if you don't have anything to do at the moment, can you feed me... pretty please?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hello, it is nice to see you again.	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh, food... I mean... master!	</connect>
			<connect>	God morning master. We have much to do today?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi, now that you're finally back you can feed me...	</connect>
			<levelup>	I'm happy for you master...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yay, another level up, master.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh, you leveled up...? Sorry, I didn't notice... I'm too busy trying to control my hunger...	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	I enjoyed that a lot.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Oh, forgive me I was hungry. Pardon my eating.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you for feeding me with such a meal.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I will stand by your side at all costs...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Dear, have you thought that maybe there are other ways to make money than this?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Please, watch yourself.	</danger>
			<danger>	No! Please, dear, sit down and rest! Please!	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh no...	</dead>
			<dead>	Master, don't you think is a bit early to have a nap?	</dead>
			<stand>	Could I bother you for a morsel of food?	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you think they sell sushi in Alberta?	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back. It is a pleasure to see you again.	</connect>
			<connect>	Ah, master... you returned. I'm happy to see you.	</connect>
			<connect>	Good morning! Have you brought some food?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Very well done~	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Wow, master... you are my hero.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I hope you are happy with your new found strength, I am losing some of mine from hungry.	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Oh, thank you, I appreciate it!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Delicious!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you master, hmm... this needs a little more salt, but still tasty.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks, it was very well prepared	</feeding>
			<hunting>	You're looking very splendid today.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I have heard that selling items is a good way to make money too.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Master, look out for your health...	</danger>
			<danger>	Dear, don't leave me alone. Come on, stand up, let's go to have a walk together.	</danger>
			<dead>	You must stop doing this to yourself..	</dead>
			<dead>	Noooooo!!! You evil mob! Just wait, we will get our revenge!	</dead>
			<dead>	Oh no! Sit and rest immediately! Help! Help! A merchant who sold potions, a priest who can heal! Please, help my master!	</dead>
			<dead>	... that's got to hurt... don't worry, we'll get revenge later.	</dead>
			<stand>	Why do I float, when you all touch the ground? Why am I different?	</stand>
			<stand>	La~la~la~ u like my singing?	</stand>
			<stand>	How about that walk you promised me before?	</stand>
			<stand>	Haven't you heard? My friend the Munak is going out with a Bongun... why can't I meet someone?	</stand>
			<connect>	Master, I missed you...	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome back my dear!	</connect>
			<levelup>	You are getting stronger each and every day~	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh my, you're so strong now!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	I'm actually a little full right now...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Uh, please, no more, master...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I've always enjoyed sitting down under a nice shady spot...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Maybe I should try being a Kafra, they make good money without killing...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Please, watch out!	</danger>
			<danger>	Master, I don't want see you become an undead too.	</danger>
			<dead>	... at this rate you'll be a ghost like me.	</dead>
			<dead>	hmm master... would you like to float around with me?	</dead>
			<dead>	NOOOOOOOO!! WHY YOU?!! NOOOOOOOOOOO!!!	</dead>
			<stand>	Master, which is prettier to you, Munak or Sohee? (Don't say Munak... don't say Munak...)	</stand>
			<connect>	Master, I have been waiting for you...	</connect>
			<connect>	Master, master! I found you!! Oh.. we're not playing hide and seek?	</connect>
			<connect>	My wonderful master! I'm so pleased to see you again!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations, Master.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh well done, I'll have to give you a prize later.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Ooh... please stop. I am too full!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You hate me, don't you? You're trying to kill me with food.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	My stomach is hurting...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Oh, my... I feel sick my stomach... Doctor is a good paid job too.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Master, I think you should take a rest...	</danger>
			<danger>	Ehm, dear... What's that red thing that is coming out your ear?	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh Master, you need to listen more...	</dead>
			<dead>	Oh well, now we can go to my home. I have enough space for you, and we will be together eternally.	</dead>
			<stand>	The world looks so pretty...	</stand>
			<stand>	Ooh, couldn't we go to the doctor, please? I feel very sick...	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back, Master. It's such a great day out today.	</connect>
			<connect>	Great! At last the sun show its face with your return, my love.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Ah... another level I see. Very good.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	... Do you think I'm getting fat?	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</sohee>
	<isis>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Sssumptious..	</feeding>
			<feeding>	My late master, Osiris never starved me like you....	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Is this low fat? Awww... who cares? I'm starved!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hsss~ Delicious! Keep it coming!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanksss for the appetizer...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Sso, thiss iss how I'm fed now?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm hoping you have sssome food for me, otherwisse you're ssnake-bait!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You're sstarving me AND making me do labor? Osiris iss not happy.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Quit wassting your time.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Whoopss, lookss like you need ssome help.	</danger>
			<danger>	Feed me before your horrible death consssumes you.	</danger>
			<danger>	You don't know what your doing, do you?	</danger>
			<danger>	My magic will be useless if you don't feed me.	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh dear, you ssshould be more conssiderate when feeding me.	</dead>
			<dead>	Thiss iss how they all end up.	</dead>
			<dead>	Give Osiris my regardsss... and tell him to ssend up some food.	</dead>
			<dead>	I'd better go sell my "Necklace" for food...! Sssee you in town!!	</dead>
			<stand>	Sssome of these people look... tantalizing...	</stand>
			<stand>	Look at me. I'm so skinny my thighs are barely touching. Oh, wait, I don't have thighs, never mind.	</stand>
			<stand>	What are you doing? Stop standing around or I'll eat that Acolyte!	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back. Ssshall we go get sssome food?	</connect>
			<connect>	Your here! *gives dark stare*	</connect>
			<connect>	Are my servants here to serve me? Oh... it's only you...	</connect>
			<levelup>	Ssso strong... It's time for food sshopping, is it not?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh... looking pretty juicy...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're not stronger than my hunnie-poo.	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Sso you remembered? I'm grateful.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmmm... this is almost satisfying...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you for feeding me well.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	*chuckle* With your sstrength, I'll be up and about in no time.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I feel like some Grade A roasted Peco Pecos.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm still not in any condition for exercise...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Pleasse, don't die... There's sso much I have to tell you!	</danger>
			<danger>	You getting better at this?	</danger>
			<danger>	Woah. You look as healthy as a ghoul. Slow down a bit.	</danger>
			<danger>	You don't have to worry about dying. Osiris will take good care of you.	</danger>
			<dead>	*gasp* My dear! I'm sso sorry!	</dead>
			<dead>	Honey, please take good care of this person.	</dead>
			<dead>	Another one bites the dust...	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm famished... Even a Sscell is looking good...	</stand>
			<stand>	I wonder if Osiris is hungry....	</stand>
			<connect>	Sshall we look into the menu for today?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello, what'ss on the menu today? Novices...?	</connect>
			<connect>	What took you so long? Don't blame it on traffic. So, got anything to eat on ya?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Sso, slick... Issn't it about treat ssomeone?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	1 point up on the food chain...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good for you! I like my pets strong and high-leveled! What?	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Ahh... I like the way it slithers down my throat...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey Baby, Thanks.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I can feel my magic growing stronger.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Let me ssee... You are ready, aren't you?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Beware! I am Isis, god of magic!	</hunting>
			<danger>	You're bleeding! We musst get you something to stop it!	</danger>
			<danger>	If my son Horus was here, he could help protect us.	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh dear... Perhapss I should go entice that Priesst over there..?	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't worry. Osiris will have you up in a jiffy.	</dead>
			<stand>	My nailss are getting long again... Do you have a sset of clipperss?	</stand>
			<stand>	I think all the food I eat goes to my chest.	</stand>
			<stand>	o/" Walk like an Egyptian... o/"	</stand>
			<stand>	I polished my tail. You think Osiris will like?	</stand>
			<stand>	*examines her nails and tail scales*	</stand>
			<connect>	It's you! Oh, I did miss you sso.	</connect>
			<connect>	Hurrah you're back!!! *Jumps up and down* Err.. what are you looking at? o.O	</connect>
			<levelup>	Ssomeone's squirming their way to the top.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oooh, pretty lights!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	The gods smile at you!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Fantasssstic!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Oh dear, if you keep feeding me like thiss, I'll be on a diet!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Are you trying to ruin my girlish figure?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Keen eyess you have...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Time for a sssacrifice to Osiris.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I think my tail is in a knot...	</hunting>
			<danger>	I'd sstrangle you, but you're already dead...	</danger>
			<danger>	Tsss, you want me to bite their headsss off?	</danger>
			<dead>	I'd sstrangle you, but you're already dead...	</dead>
			<dead>	No...! I'll get revenge for you!	</dead>
			<dead>	Osiris, honey? Can you send my friend back?	</dead>
			<stand>	I don't like the way the men look at me ssometimes. I'll go sslap them.	</stand>
			<stand>	*GASP* Oh my GOD! Is that...a WRINKLE!?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hmm... Let's go shopping!	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey there good-lookin.	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome back, gorgeous.	</connect>
			<connect>	Where the heck have you been? I was getting a little worried honesstly.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Getting buff again, hmm, ssexy?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good to see you're getting less-wimpy! I like a strong brave pet ~.^	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Wow! You ARE strong. Maybe I should call my son Horus to challenge you.	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	No! My sslim physssique.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Stop, stop! Not ALL this food went to my chest! My scales are about to burst!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Please... no more... this is torture...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Look, if you want me to keep my girlish figure, stop shoving those at me.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I feel like there'ss a ton of brickss inside me!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can I borrow a cotton shirt? Hisss... Hissss...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Sshall I go and find ssomeone who's much better then you?	</danger>
			<dead>	Sso, you finally undersstand that it'ss you who'ss more important to me?	</dead>
			<dead>	Noo don't leave me!! Stay away from the light!!	</dead>
			<dead>	...Don't be so hard on yourself... Isis will be with you..	</dead>
			<stand>	Dearesst, lend me your sshoulder?	</stand>
			<stand>	Do I look fat to you...?	</stand>
			<stand>	As much as I hate to admit it... you're a great pet to have around!...I AM the owner, right?	</stand>
			<stand>	*Sob* How can Osiris see me like this?	</stand>
			<connect>	Here comess the ssexy one...	</connect>
			<connect>	Yo yo homie what's up? ... What the hell am I saying...	</connect>
			<connect>	Glad to see ya! Let's Ragnarok!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Sso sexy, but do you think of me the ssame?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Wee! Good job! Let's celebrate with some situps.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</isis>
	<petit>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Hey come on now...I'm still hungry!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	OOOOOHHH yeah, what a wonderful thing. More, more!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I'm going to eat those valuable items of yours...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Uggg... no energy. *snap snap*	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Some Prontera cuisine would be nice!	</hunting>
			<danger>	You better feed me before you die!	</danger>
			<danger>	We should both go get some food.	</danger>
			<danger>	Don't go dying on me! hmm never mind.	</danger>
			<dead>	I told you to feed me before you died...loser...	</dead>
			<dead>	You should be watching your back.	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey! Free meal!	</dead>
			<stand>	Stop standing around and feed me!	</stand>
			<stand>	Please give me a snack, I beg of you.	</stand>
			<stand>	Going already? You must eat pretty well	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you have any food in your pockets?	</stand>
			<stand>	HEY! feed me or something..	</stand>
			<connect>	I'm hungry...feed me now!	</connect>
			<connect>	It's about time you came, where is my breakfast!	</connect>
			<connect>	Yay! What's for lunch?	</connect>
			<levelup>	You... now only if you fed me!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	*ROOARRR* Excellent work.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Great, you're happy, now make me happy! Hint hint.	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	You, I'm still a little hungry...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks a lot, I was getting hungry. *munch*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Now we are getting somewhere!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Wooooh, go get 'em!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Mmm looks like chicken, I bet it tastes like chicken too!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You are very good!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Your almost dead...can you feed me?	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh no, don't die yet!	</danger>
			<dead>	Get up and feed me!	</dead>
			<dead>	C'mon, get up, get up!	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm hungry...what's for a snack?	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you ready to fight again?	</stand>
			<connect>	Heya...I'm hungry! Feed meh!	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh... welcome back!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yippee!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice job!	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Mmmm...beefy!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmmmm, that hit the spot!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Whoa! Let me have one of those.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Knock'em all down! Yeah, yeah!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Heal him!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Be careful, my liege.	</danger>
			<dead>	Yo man...what's your problem?! Get up!	</dead>
			<dead>	Errr... hey... you ok?	</dead>
			<stand>	Let's go! I want to hunt!	</stand>
			<stand>	Let's go and find treasure!	</stand>
			<stand>	Ready to do some jumping-jacks?	</stand>
			<connect>	Yo, what's up?	</connect>
			<connect>	Thank goodness, I was getting lonely!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Touche!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	HURRAY! Get strong!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	I'm full now, thanks.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you, but I don't think I can eat much more.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I'm good, you're good! LET'S HUNT!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Lets find those rare items you want!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	You need a leaf or something...geez...	</danger>
			<danger>	You could have used my food money for red potions!	</danger>
			<dead>	Man....you know....You die too much.	</dead>
			<dead>	NO! Now I have to use my fat stores!	</dead>
			<stand>	Man I'm getting stronger! What do you think?	</stand>
			<stand>	It must be nice to be able to stand	</stand>
			<connect>	Whoa! Let's go!	</connect>
			<connect>	My Spoiling leader returns!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Oh yea! Let me get in on this!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey! I gained a level too, in body mass!	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	I'm gonna barf on you man!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	More food?! You must be rich!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Let's rest a bit!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ever wonder why you never found any good rare items?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh I'll get that monster for that!	</danger>
			<danger>	OMG HEAL HIM! HE'S GONNA DIE HEAL HIM!	</danger>
			<dead>	Come on now...get up so we can go hunt some more!	</dead>
			<dead>	Well, you should have ran instead of dieing~	</dead>
			<stand>	OK...let's stay for a bit.	</stand>
			<stand>	Lets go somewhere fun	</stand>
			<stand>	It must be nice to be able to stand	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey...let me rest a bit...I'm too full...	</connect>
			<connect>	My Spoiling leader returns!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Now can we rest? I'm gonna barf!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hey! I gained a level too, in body mass!	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</petit>
	<deviruchi>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Finally!! Please give more though. Little devils need lots of food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you, do you have any fresh meat?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Give me more food or I'll stab you with my fork!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks...cheapskate... more please!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	That must have been the smallest shoot you could find.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Do you want to find out just how evil I can be?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Can I make shish kabobs out of your loot...?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Why not get that one? Are you scared of it?...wimp...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I will poke you with this fork if you don't feed me.	</hunting>
			<danger>	You look a little pale...	</danger>
			<danger>	Hee~ hee~, one more won't hurt! Just one more!	</danger>
			<dead>	Maybe if I had food and wasn't a devil, you would be alive!	</dead>
			<dead>	Hehehe, that'll teach you!	</dead>
			<stand>	By the way, can I get some food?!	</stand>
			<stand>	FEEEEEEEEED MEEEEEEEE!	</stand>
			<stand>	What're you just STANDING there for?	</stand>
			<stand>	Why do bad things happen to bad people?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hello there! Bring any food?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey you! Want me to stick this rod in your *cough* ...?	</connect>
			<connect>	Wakey wakey, eggs n'bakey	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yay, you're the best! ...can we celebrate with food?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Err, WAHOO...or something... eh, just feed me already.	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Thank you very much!... ACK...I almost became nice...!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Gracias!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Now I'm no longer see-through! Thanks again.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey! Those look pretty tasty...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Oh, I want to stab it too! Can I at least eat what it leaves behind?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'll go scare people and eat the food they drop.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh my dark lord... save us!	</danger>
			<danger>	You get hit way too much... you know that?	</danger>
			<danger>	Suffering Satan! You should be careful... you're not as tough as you think.	</danger>
			<danger>	And on your left, you'll see my latest victim in dire need of help...	</danger>
			<dead>	*poke*poke* excellent...	</dead>
			<dead>	Can't you feed me from the beyond? I'm hungry..	</dead>
			<dead>	1, 2, 3! You're out!! I now pronounce you the LOossaAaah!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Oof! Get off me!! Fall the OTHER way next time!	</dead>
			<dead>	*poke* Why aren't you feeding me?	</dead>
			<stand>	You look hungry, how about we go rest and snack a little?	</stand>
			<stand>	Want to go release summoned monsters on Prontera?	</stand>
			<connect>	Now that you're here, let us go grab a bite to eat!	</connect>
			<connect>	Do you have any pork?	</connect>
			<connect>	Do you think it's wrong to eat children?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Nice! Let's go celebrate!... dark children from below, come forth and do my bidding...!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're buff now!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yay, now can we get some fresh meat?	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Mmm... tasty.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Not even Baphomet himself eats better then this!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Not bad.. not bad at all.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Lord, when will you be done with this pitiful creature?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'll put a curse on anyone that messes with us.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Leaping Lucifer, you rock!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Bah, this is not worth our time, kill it quickly, show it your true power!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Where's the nearest 'fraidy-cat?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey, if you're gonna drop to a knee, you better not start preying to the wrong guy...	</danger>
			<danger>	Knock that off, kill it before you die again...	</danger>
			<danger>	Jumping Jezebel! Somebody help!	</danger>
			<danger>	Whoa there, time to bail! Get your booties in the high gear... yes, I said booties...why, what'd you hear?	</danger>
			<dead>	I thought you said you could handle it!?	</dead>
			<dead>	Ah! Speak to me!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Wiiinaaahh... not you.... hahaha, get up... no really, get up... ?... hello?*poke*	</dead>
			<dead>	Get up! I don't want to go back to Hell...it's more fun with you!	</dead>
			<stand>	I could use a new fork, don't you think?	</stand>
			<stand>	We're bad to the bone...*rwar*	</stand>
			<stand>	Where to next? Hope it's somewhere spooky!	</stand>
			<stand>	Y'know, I really like hangin' with you, you're alright...	</stand>
			<stand>	I was friends with a Baphomet once. No, really!	</stand>
			<connect>	Let's go! We got souls to steal and lives to ruin!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello, did you bring me some fresh meat?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Woohoo, nice one!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You are as strong as Beelzebub himself!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Sweet, let's head over to that special building and celebrate...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Touch-down! Home-run! GOOOOOOAAAAAALLLLLLL......wait.... what do you mean wrong game?	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Erm, save it for later!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thanks, but I'm stuffed.... Yes, I am the devil's cuddle toy!!!! Muhahahahaaaa!!!!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Seems like you could use a break.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Slow down, remember my stubby little legs?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*stab*stab*stab* This is great!!!!!!!!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Slowly, the fearsome Deviruchi stalks its prey... was that a crocodile I just saw?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	If you find food, keep it.... We devils don't have black holes in our bellies!!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hmm, want me to go get a Yggdrasil Leaf?	</danger>
			<danger>	Careful there. Don't want to overdo it!	</danger>
			<danger>	Great Satan, be careful!	</danger>
			<dead>	I dropped my Yggdrasil Leaf!	</dead>
			<dead>	Turn Undead!! ... no... wait, err... hmm...	</dead>
			<dead>	Aah! I told you, you should have sold your soul for immortality!	</dead>
			<stand>	Maybe I can talk to my boss and get a promotion to Wraith or something?	</stand>
			<stand>	Doo be doo be doo...	</stand>
			<stand>	I think I'll hide in your hair...	</stand>
			<stand>	I think I could qualify as a food-critic.... you seem to think the same	</stand>
			<connect>	Glad to have you back!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi, there!! Think we can scare people today?	</connect>
			<levelup>	One step closer to true power!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Excellent, everything's going according to plan...	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	I might just puff up even bigger soon!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Getting...full....regurgitation....imminent... STAND BACK!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I didn't think it was possible to get fat from eating shoots!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Ugh... this isn't going good with my stomach.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can't.... move....must....sit.....*burp*	</hunting>
			<danger>	Is that supposed to bleed?	</danger>
			<danger>	Damn, you bruise easily!!	</danger>
			<dead>	I kind of feel the same way as well.	</dead>
			<dead>	Why, dark lord? WHY?!	</dead>
			<stand>	Can I sit down? The sky keeps swirling around.	</stand>
			<stand>	It is hard to look evil when you are this chubby...	</stand>
			<stand>	I know it's supposed to be the year of the monkey, but... c'mon when's it going to be MY turn! HUH?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey! Let's go run around Prontera and burn those calories! Maybe a couple houses...	</connect>
			<connect>	How about a quick run through Prontera... with some dead branches of course... heh...	</connect>
			<connect>	Just in time for my inter-snack-nap-time.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congrats! Now help me lose some pounds!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You have inspired me to lose a few pounds.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	When am I going to level up?	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</deviruchi>
	<baphomet_j>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Thank the stars, I couldn't possibly be MORE hungry. *chomp*snarf*	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Human! Give me more food or I will call my dad!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Don't expect me to help you fight until you give me some FOOD.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Bleh... You will never kill quicker than me.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey! Take a break! This is not a time to fight.	</danger>
			<danger>	Come on! Die! Now! I need your blood!	</danger>
			<danger>	That's what happens when you block using your face. Wizen up!	</danger>
			<dead>	*tsk*tsk* Serves you right for not looking around.	</dead>
			<dead>	Another example of how stupid a human can be....	</dead>
			<stand>	I need food, there's an empty pit in my stomach.	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you trying to make me run...?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, do you know what wine goes with a severed Rocker head?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey! It was nice of you to come... even though you're LATE.	</connect>
			<levelup>	*poke*poke* Let's go back to town and get food now.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	NO! You mustn't level up! You can't become powerful like me!	</levelup>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Ooh joy, it's food time.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Human! I want more food.....	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Rah rah, fight those brutes!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You think you can kill some of the dark beings?	</hunting>
			<danger>	I'd use a yellow potion right now if I were you.	</danger>
			<dead>	What are you doing? Stand up, I tell you!	</dead>
			<stand>	Let's go a huntin'...	</stand>
			<stand>	Humans life is so boring...	</stand>
			<connect>	*hops* C'mon, gimme a snack and let's head off!	</connect>
			<connect>	I hate you... not really, but c'mon where's the food?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Oh yeah, oh yeah, beat their butts!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Great now you can kill a poring!	</levelup>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Delicious...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	This tastes like your blood~... how would I know...? ... don't ask.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	That's more like it! Keep it comin'!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I will help you if you give me your soul.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	The fear of prey smells divine!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Mwhahahaha, let's go kick some monster ass!	</hunting>
			<danger>	I can't heal good people, you know that.	</danger>
			<dead>	I told you, you're not as powerful as me...	</dead>
			<stand>	What are you standing around for, let's go.	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you going to move or must I use my scythe?	</stand>
			<connect>	About time you showed up.	</connect>
			<connect>	Great! Your corpse is going to be fun to mess with.	</connect>
			<levelup>	WHAT? I didn't help you to level up! What's going on here?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	.Good work! Let's try a harder monster now!	</levelup>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Truly marvelous! I am quite full now, thank you!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmmm, tastes good, but don't overdo it.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I think dad will not be happy with me for being with you.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey, how do you like my scythe? Shiny, huh? I polished it earlier..	</hunting>
			<danger>	Me? Tired? Pssht, no way. Maybe YOU should rest though.	</danger>
			<danger>	Let me tank them and train you!	</danger>
			<dead>	Bah, BAH! *stomps on your body*	</dead>
			<dead>	Poor human, I thought you could dodge better... I guess I gave you too much credit.	</dead>
			<stand>	Come on lazy bones!	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you a tree? MOVE!	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey dead head... MOVE IT!	</stand>
			<stand>	Why does everyone call me Junior? Call me MASTER... or die...	</stand>
			<connect>	Late again. Don't you ever learn?	</connect>
			<connect>	Don't even think about complaining to me today... so help me, I will cut you down to my size!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Woot! now I can have a longer battle with you before you run like a chicken!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	This is like second nature to you, huh?	</levelup>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	I'll be stuck to the ground like a Flora if you keep feeding me.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Stop! I don't want to eat more of your meat! It's dirty!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Can a demon heal you?	</danger>
			<dead>	Are you really... dead? Oh god please NO!!! I was only joking about you being weak, why didn't you tell me you were?	</dead>
			<dead>	Aaahh, lying down, that's a good idea.	</dead>
			<stand>	*BRAAAAAAAAPPPPP*	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm a little drowsy... Zzzz...	</stand>
			<stand>	My scythe feels rather heavy to carry right now..	</stand>
			<connect>	I'm not getting up yet, no way no how.	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey! I think I lost a little weight!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yeah, whatever.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well, not bad human... maybe you're not as weak as I thought.	</levelup>
		</so_full>
	</baphomet_j>
	<bon_gun>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Bleh... Can't you feed me on a regular basis?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	This isn't what I like! Munak would take care of me better... Hmph!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*gulp* Don't you have more?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I keep telling you, I want this stuff medium rare. Get it right next time, or um... you're fired!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Finish him!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm Hungry~	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Gimmie Food... I said gimmie food.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Ack! Why do you suck so much?!	</danger>
			<danger>	*tsk*tsk*... To think we're losing to that...	</danger>
			<danger>	Stop sucking, heal yourself and then feed me.	</danger>
			<dead>	... I dunno anymore... How long are we gonna be like this?... I feel faint...	</dead>
			<dead>	What are you gonna do now!? This is all your fault!	</dead>
			<dead>	Noooo!! I can't eat you now!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, weren't you listening to me?	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm hungry... only if I had something in my tummy...	</stand>
			<stand>	Ah.. my chest.. my chest suddenly hurts... I wonder why... anyway, feed me.	</stand>
			<stand>	I wonder where Munak is...	</stand>
			<stand>	Feed Me. Feed Meeeeee~	</stand>
			<stand>	If you don't feed me, I'm going to eat you!	</stand>
			<stand>	Finally you're done. You ready to go? Geez, the things I do for servants... What's that look for?	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm going to bite you!! You don't even feed me!	</stand>
			<connect>	I'm hungry. Hey? I said I'm hungry. Hurry and gimme food.	</connect>
			<connect>	Where did you just come back from?!	</connect>
			<connect>	Make me food. I'm dying from hunger.	</connect>
			<connect>	There you are, exactly 2 minutes late for my meal. Just for that I want everything cut into bite size chunks.	</connect>
			<levelup>	You're becoming more and more useful...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Satisfied? Lets go eat now.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	What're you doing?! You got your level! Now make me food!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	W...What is this?... Whenever I see this picture I get tears in my eyes...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Munak... *faint*	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I miss Munak...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Oooh-- A.... Achoo!!!!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	*Cough* *Cough*!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	I feel so suffocated... Achoo!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*yawn*~~ so boring~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Ho ho~ What a dull day.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I am so bored~ What is there to do?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Should I... show off?	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh... A button fell off.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	My clothes feel so loose.	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	*chomp*chomp*... *gulp*gulp*... *chomp*chomp*... Don't bother me, I'm eating...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*chomp*chomp*... *sluuuuurp*~	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*chomp*chomp*... *tsk*... Don't misunderstand me... I'm only eating because I'm hungry, not because it's good.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I was getting the munchies anyway so I guess I'll eat some.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Even though you can't do anything else, you sure do feed me well. Well at least with this, you can stay by my side~	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You picked this up off the ground, didn't you? No? Alright, but I'm watching you...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Wah~ I ate well. Now, I need water~.. Hm? Why aren't you bringing me water?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	What kind of food is this? *tsk*... I'm only eating this food out of pity. *Chomp*Chomp*...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Okay, whatever you kill, we split 20-80... what...? I think giving you 20% is more then fair!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Since I'm hungry, why don't we go eat something... aren't you hungry?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Now, show me the results of your training!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm fed up. What's the point if you're not going to kill it instantly, go make me food.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Lead the way sidekick... then after we beat these guys up, feed me.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yes! Good job!! Now let's go eat!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	See! You have no strength from not eating!	</danger>
			<danger>	Aaaaack!! Can't you do anything right?!	</danger>
			<danger>	You're already losing steam?	</danger>
			<danger>	You're looking weak already, what's wrong with you...	</danger>
			<danger>	Be Strong!! Be Strong and run away... and then lets go to eat!	</danger>
			<danger>	You're strong enough to give me food, right?	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey you! I told you to be strong~	</danger>
			<dead>	Huh?... What... what is this?	</dead>
			<dead>	All that training... wasted...	</dead>
			<dead>	Noooo..... The food you gave me was good.... Now I can't eat your food anymore?	</dead>
			<dead>	How can this be... You fed me all this time... And now who's going to feed me?! No!! I hate this!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Get up!! There are things I still want to tell you!! Pl... Please...	</dead>
			<dead>	No!! Get up!! I told you to get up! You have to make me food like yesterday!! Please...	</dead>
			<stand>	*tummy grumble*... hmm...	</stand>
			<stand>	Feed me...	</stand>
			<stand>	If you come and visit my home, you can experience the land of Payon. Sound nice?	</stand>
			<stand>	To be strong and healthy, one must eat well!	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm... hungry....	</stand>
			<stand>	This is my command... feed me.	</stand>
			<stand>	Bring me food~ c'mon! What are you doing~ I said get me food!	</stand>
			<stand>	*tummy grumble*...Foooooood....	</stand>
			<connect>	You came just in time. Make me food.	</connect>
			<connect>	Why did you come so late? For that, you have to make me food...	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh, you're here.	</connect>
			<connect>	You came at the perfect time! I was starving!	</connect>
			<connect>	Is your business outside of here more important than me? *tsk*... I'll forgive you if you feed me, this time.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Foo food foo food~ foo~ food~ f~ foo foo~ food~... hey!! I'm telling you to give me food!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Good job, congratulations.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Foo foo foo food~ foo~ food~ foo foo foo~ food~... Do you understand what I'm saying?	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	W...what is this?... Whenever I see this picture I get tears in my eyes...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Munak... I miss you...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I miss Munak...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Oooh-- A.... Achoo!!!!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	*cough*cough*!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	I feel so suffocated... Achoo!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*yawn*~~ so boring~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Ho ho~ What a dull day, why can't we do something?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	*I am so bored~ What is there to do?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	... show off? What am I a dog?	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh... A button fell off... can you fix it?	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	My clothes feel so loose...	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	*chomp*chomp*... *chew*chew*... *gulp*gulp*... Ah~	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*chomp*chomp*... Hm... Gimmie water.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Wah~ I'm done eating. Hm, what're you doing? Clean this up.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*Chew Chew* Hmm.... this food is edible...*chomp*chomp*...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It doesn't look good but I'll eat some anyway...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm reminded of this really good orange juice I used to have at home... It was so good...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	When are you going to level up?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm bored~ Will you play with me?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Play with me~ huh?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Play with me, Play with me, Play with me, Play with me~ *cry* I said to play with me~~	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*slash*slash*... *stab*stab*... *slash*slash*...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can you stop fighting for a moment? I want to just sit down and think about Munak~	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Aren't you tired of fighting that ugly monster? Let's go play with wonderful me, instead!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Get your fighting spirits up!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Tsk... That's the only thing you know how to do~	</hunting>
			<danger>	Pay attention!! No! Not like that!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	What are you doing!? Do it right! Protect me!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Put it in a little more effort!!	</danger>
			<danger>	That isn't how you fight! Put more effort into it!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Ack! That's not it! Do it more boldly!!	</danger>
			<danger>	That's the only thing you know how to do and you want to what?!...	</danger>
			<danger>	Watch out for him!! Finish him!!	</danger>
			<dead>	Lies!! Why... Why is this...?... Hurry, get up and give me food!!!...	</dead>
			<dead>	Why.... Why is your body cold?!... Why... Why?!?!	</dead>
			<dead>	Oh no! Aaaaahh....!	</dead>
			<dead>	Bleh... I told you to be careful...	</dead>
			<dead>	Nooooooo!... Who's gonna feed me now?!...	</dead>
			<dead>	Huh. Finally found something we have in common. 'Course, I'm dead and can still do stuff... Still with me? Hey...	</dead>
			<dead>	No!!! NooOooOoo!! This can't Be!! *cry*...	</dead>
			<dead>	Get up! I said to get up!! Can't you hear my voice?! I said to get up!!!	</dead>
			<stand>	Did you know? All the pine trees in Payon belong to my family. Cool huh? Eh, it's nothing, really. hehe.	</stand>
			<stand>	My dream is to be as famous as Balder someday...	</stand>
			<stand>	You're taking too many breaks... You're going to end up looking like a Savage.	</stand>
			<stand>	All you ever do is sit around... Can't we go do something fun... Like shopping for me?	</stand>
			<stand>	...If I find Munak... I'm never going to part with her ever again...	</stand>
			<stand>	What're you looking at... Hurry and get to work... I found something I want to buy.	</stand>
			<stand>	Ah~~ buy me that... You know what I'm talking about~ That~~	</stand>
			<stand>	Buy it for me~ Buy it~ The thing I told you about~!	</stand>
			<stand>	What?! You can't even buy me that and you expect me to play with you?	</stand>
			<stand>	*tsk*, Never mind! Its my fault for getting my hopes up...	</stand>
			<stand>	Why did you stop?... Lets hurry and go see stuff~	</stand>
			<stand>	bah...	</stand>
			<connect>	Ah, You're here? I was gathering some coupons.	</connect>
			<connect>	I was organizing the fan letters I've been getting while you were gone.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Took you long enough... I've seen novices the same level as you...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hm... You're still far off... Don't be too happy.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hmph.. You want a congratulations from me? Do you? Do you?...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh ho~ I'll give you my special congratulations. I congratulate your effort!... How about was that?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're getting stronger... I can feel it.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	W...What is this?... Whenever I see this picture I get tears in my eyes...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Munak... *faint*	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I miss Munak...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Oooh-- A.... Achoo!!!!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	*Cough* *Cough*!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	I feel so suffocated... Achoo!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*yawn*~~ so boring~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Oh Ho~ What a dull day.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I am so bored~ What is there to do?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Should I... show you?	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh... A button fell off.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	My clothes feel so loose.	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	It is good to control your appetite.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hm...It would have been nice to have eaten a little bit later.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Am I some sort of eating machine? Tsk... If this was worth eating maybe...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ack- It tastes so bad. What is this? Give me something better to eat.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Wah~ I'm tired of pet food. Let's eat something better!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Be strong! You can do it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You're having fun.... Tsk, and you won't play with me...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	What? Why are you only hitting him? Am I not of any interest?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Oh ho~ You're saying you have no interest in me? Hmph- Don't think I'm gonna be sad about it.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hmph! Useless people....?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey! What're you doing... Pay attention! Attention!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hmm... In any form, training is hard work. There there, lets fight!	</danger>
			<danger>	Open your eyes!! What're you doing?! You have to live so you can be teased by me some more!!	</danger>
			<danger>	You dork!!! Why are you fighting like that for?!	</danger>
			<danger>	It's dangerous!! Dangerous I say! Dork!! Why don't you listen to me?!~	</danger>
			<dead>	Noooooooooooooooooooo~~~~~~!!!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Get up!! Get up!! I said get up!!	</dead>
			<dead>	That was an awesome fight.. Try better next time.	</dead>
			<dead>	Liar... It can't be like this... Not like this!!!	</dead>
			<dead>	Nooooooo!!! You still haven't written me into your last will and testament!	</dead>
			<stand>	What're you looking at? Tsk... so ugly...	</stand>
			<stand>	Stop standing there, Move around. Do you think you're going to lose weight like that? Hehe	</stand>
			<stand>	...am I annoying you yet?...	</stand>
			<stand>	Sometimes I feel thankful that you're here by my side...	</stand>
			<stand>	Nya~Nya~ Hehehe. Are you getting annoyed yet?~	</stand>
			<stand>	Hehehehe	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey ugly, what're you looking at?... Let's go.	</stand>
			<connect>	Huh? What did you come for?~	</connect>
			<connect>	Why do you bother coming? Hmph, you think I'm lonely without you?~	</connect>
			<connect>	You're here?	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh, It's just you.	</connect>
			<connect>	What? You missed me that much? Ho ho~	</connect>
			<connect>	I knew you missed me. Well, I do have a face you can't forget~	</connect>
			<levelup>	Oh, you leveled?... Congratulations?...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	What? I'll tell you beforehand that I am much stronger than you. Don't let this one level up get to your head.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	*tsk*tsk*... What... You did well... You did well! Yeah, yeah, good for you!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Your training is paying off.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hmph... Don't be so happy over this one level...	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	W...What is this?... Whenever I see this picture I get tears in my eyes...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Munak... *faint*	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I miss Munak...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Oooh-- A.... Achoo!!!!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	*Cough* *Cough*!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	I feel so suffocated... Achoo!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*yawn*~~ so boring~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Oh Ho~ What a dull day.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I am so bored~ What is there to do?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Should I... show you?	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh... A button fell off.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	My clothes feel so loose.	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Ack! I'm choking!...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ack! How much do you intend on feeding me?!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Alright, that's enough... You're trying to get me killed again?!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	That's enough. Since I'm full... Let's go nap.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hmm... My body feels heavy.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You're putting in a lot of effort... Do you think you'll look better from doing it? *flop*	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Stop doing that and lets go play. You're my pet~~	</hunting>
			<danger>	Stop it! Its too dangerous! Do you want to die again?!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey! Hey! Watch your back!!	</danger>
			<danger>	It's dangerous!! No!! No more!!	</danger>
			<danger>	This is weird!! This is familiar... I don't like this feeling!!!	</danger>
			<danger>	No!! Stop sacrificing yourself for me! Don't leave me!	</danger>
			<dead>	No!!... This can't this be... Are you leaving me again? Is that what is it!?	</dead>
			<dead>	Bah... You need to learn to take care of yourself. How can you leave me like this?...	</dead>
			<dead>	No!! How can this be... I wasn't able to protect you...	</dead>
			<dead>	Get up!! I said get up!! Please... Please open your eyes!	</dead>
			<dead>	Ah... No!!... I can't let you go again! And to think I just found you again...	</dead>
			<dead>	Ah... How can this be?... I wasn't able to tell you how I feel...	</dead>
			<stand>	Hmm~ There is a nice breeze today~	</stand>
			<stand>	Yeah... It was just like this... The day I made a promise with that girl...	</stand>
			<stand>	*Cry* My leg hurts.	</stand>
			<stand>	You know... The truth is... I......	</stand>
			<stand>	You know... That is... Anyway.... Errr...	</stand>
			<stand>	Anyway... The truth is... I..... uh....	</stand>
			<stand>	When we are doing nothing like this... I am reminded of Munak...*sigh*...	</stand>
			<stand>	I........ I.... l...i...k...e...... like the sky... hehehe.....	</stand>
			<stand>	I........ Ah, never mind. By the way, you look like you're gaining weight.	</stand>
			<stand>	Wonderful........... Hmm? What are you thinking about?! Not you, the sky!	</stand>
			<stand>	*fart*... Hmm?... What... Why are you laughing? Don't you fart?	</stand>
			<stand>	*Gulp Gulp* Ah~ That felt good. Hehehe... Want to try some?	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey... Long time no see.	</connect>
			<connect>	I was thinking about you, this is good... Hmm? I said I was thinking about the food you give me.	</connect>
			<connect>	I missed you.	</connect>
			<connect>	Ack!	</connect>
			<connect>	Ho ho ho ho ho... You know... Today...	</connect>
			<connect>	I missed you!... Hmm, don't misunderstand! Not you... Something else... Er, You don't need to know!	</connect>
			<levelup>	!! You finally leveled!~ Wah~ Congrats! That's so good!... Ack... Hmm... That is... My... condition is good!!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I think I'm happy to see you become stronger~	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hmm!! Wah!! Finally... Ack... Eh... Something is very... hmm...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Con... Congratulations.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	W...What is this?... Whenever I see this picture I get tears in my eyes...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Munak... *faint*	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I miss Munak...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Oooh-- A.... Achoo!!!!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	*Cough* *Cough*!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	I feel so suffocated... Achoo!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*yawn*~~ so boring~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Oh Ho~ What a dull day.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I am so bored~ What is there to do?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Should I... show you?	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh... A button fell off.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	My clothes feel so loose.	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</bon_gun>
	<alice>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Master, I am too exhausted to sweep the floor.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Master, it is the time for dinner. Would you like me to cook?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Can I have some more...please?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you so much.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Are you sure you can defeat the enemy?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope you will take care of yourself.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope you will take care of me rather than focusing on hunting.	</hunting>
			<danger>	I suggest that you be careful.	</danger>
			<danger>	Doesn't seeing your HP displayed in red make you nervous?	</danger>
			<danger>	I always want to believe that you are the strongest adventurer in the world.	</danger>
			<dead>	Sorry, I have nothing to say.	</dead>
			<dead>	Are you alright?		</dead>
			<dead>	Master, it is not good to lie on cold ground.	</dead>
			<dead>	Your vision is growing dim? Does that mean you are hungry?	</dead>
			<stand>	Excuse me, master! Will you please step aside from there? I cannot sweep the floor!	</stand>
			<stand>	Well, I can tell you are incompetent, considering the way you treat your pet.	</stand>
			<stand>	If you do not know how to take care of a pet, how can take care of your wife?	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you bored, master?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hello? Master, are you ok?	</stand>
			<stand>	I do not understand why you stand still. Alice wants to exercise!	</stand>
			<connect>	I almost had dinner alone because you did not come home earlier.	</connect>
			<connect>	It seems... You are always later than I expect.	</connect>
			<connect>	Do you not care about me, or do you trust me that much?	</connect>
			<connect>	If you neglect me like this, you may have to let me go someday.	</connect>
			<levelup>	You must be pleased.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Oh well, the circle of life continues.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry. Let me clean this mess really quick.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Thank you for trusting me, even if I am careless sometimes.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	A respectable maid must be pure in body and mind.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Let's say I'm covered in dark dust. Would that make me Cinderella?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Alice must shake the dust off her body often. Otherwise, she will look dirty.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*Phew* Much cleaner.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Do you think the house looks better now? Can I take a break?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I love my job, but sometimes it is very tiresome. *Sigh...*	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Master, I am too exhausted to sweep the floor.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Master, it is the time for dinner. Would you like me to cook?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	May I have some more please?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you so much.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You must mind your table manners when eating.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you for the food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It was good, thank you master!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*Gulp gulp*...Are you thinking that Alice wastes your money by eating expensive potions?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Are you sure you can defeat this enemy?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope you will take care of yourself.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope you will take care of me rather than focusing on hunting.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hunting, hunting, hunting! You do the same thing everyday!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Sometimes, you need to take a seat and rest.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Anything red cannot be accepted!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Please be more careful.	</danger>
			<danger>	Doesn't seeing your HP displayed in red make you nervous?	</danger>
			<danger>	I always want to believe that you are the strongest adventurer in the world.	</danger>
			<danger>	It feels like the ground is coming towards me...	</danger>
			<danger>	How about...going back and having dinner first?	</danger>
			<danger>	Promise me you will leave my food before you go!	</danger>
			<danger>	I think heaven is closer now, isn't it?	</danger>
			<dead>	I'm sorry, I have nothing to say.	</dead>
			<dead>	Are you okay?!	</dead>
			<dead>	Master, it is not good to lie on cold ground.	</dead>
			<dead>	Your vision is growing dim? Does that mean you are hungry?	</dead>
			<dead>	No way! You're not waiting for someone to rescue you, are you?	</dead>
			<dead>	You pervert! Get up! What exactly are you looking at?!	</dead>
			<stand>	Excuse me, master! Will you please step aside from there? I cannot sweep the floor!	</stand>
			<stand>	Oh well, I can tell you are incompetent, considering the way you treat your pet.	</stand>
			<stand>	If you do not know how to take care of a pet, how can you take care of your wife?	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you bored, master?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hello...master? Are you okay?	</stand>
			<stand>	I do not understand why you stand still. Alice wants to exercise!	</stand>
			<stand>	The early bird catches the worm!	</stand>
			<connect>	I almost had dinner alone because you did not come home earlier.	</connect>
			<connect>	It seems...you are always later than I expect.	</connect>
			<connect>	Do you not care about me, or do you trust me that much?	</connect>
			<connect>	If you neglect me like this, you may have to let me go someday.	</connect>
			<connect>	Where have you been? Are you cheating me with another pet? Are you? Tell me the truth!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations... But now I am hungry.		</levelup>
			<levelup>	Is there anything I can drink now? I wish I could have a cool potion. Ah, it would feel so good!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	I want to drink a White Potion to celebrate your levelup!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry. Let me clean this mess really quick.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Thank you for trusting me even if I am careless sometimes.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	A respectable maid must be pure in body and mind.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Let's say I'm covered in dark dust. Would that make me Cinderella?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Alice must shake the dust off her body often. Otherwise, she will look dirty.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*Phew* Much cleaner.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Do you think the house looks better now? Can I take a break?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I love my job, but sometimes it is very tiresome. *Sigh...*	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Thank you very much for the food.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I am trying to enjoy my meal.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*Gulp gulp*...Are you thinking that Alice wastes your money by eating expensive potions?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It was great as usual!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you for the food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Frankly, Alice is not that picky for what she eats!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Go for it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I trust you enough to let you hunt alone.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Okay, next!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I wish you would slow down your hunting sometimes.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Leveling up is not everything. Of course, money is not everything either! Don't you ever try to nitpick what I am staying!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	The most powerful range weapon for a female is a broom. Alice will use her broom when her master is in danger.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I have seen many guests fall unconscious after one blow from Alice's broom.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I have never doubted you are my guardian, master.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hunting is always joyful but don't fall alseep during the hunt!	</hunting>
			<danger>	I know you can win, can you? Or...can't you?	</danger>
			<danger>	You promised to protect me...why is your HP bar showing in red?	</danger>
			<danger>	Alice is sad when her master is having a hard time.	</danger>
			<danger>	Well, I may cheer up with this white potion! *Gulp*	</danger>
			<danger>	No no no no, you can't use the Berserk skill!	</danger>
			<danger>	I suggest you exercise more. I can be your training coach!	</danger>
			<danger>	If you had a stout lower body, you would not have a hard time like this. You will sweep the floor with me from now on!	</danger>
			<dead>	The floor looks so comfortable.	</dead>
			<dead>	Wah! You pervert! Get up, get up! What are you looking at!?	</dead>
			<dead>	I hope my master found peace in these final moments...	</dead>
			<dead>	As I remember, my late master was truly kind and gentle. *Sigh...* Let's not talk about it anymore...	</dead>
			<dead>	Excuse me, master? Will you get up? I need to clean this area.	</dead>
			<dead>	If you do not get up soon, I will put you into the recycling bin.		</dead>
			<dead>	Okay, it is the time for emptying the trash can...wah!! What are you doing in there, master?	</dead>
			<stand>	Alice used to lead a lonesome life in an ancient castle.	</stand>
			<stand>	I always cleaned everywhere in the castle.	</stand>
			<stand>	Being alone was really sad, but now I am not sad any longer. Because I am with you.	</stand>
			<stand>	When you lay the broom on the side, it will not raise dust. I learned this when I was in the army....?! Wah! What was I saying!	</stand>
			<stand>	The Castle I used to live in was so huge that I had a hard time cleaning it in a day.	</stand>
			<stand>	Will you promise to love me more if I clean harder?	</stand>
			<stand>	The Rune-Midgarts Kingdom seems so peaceful~	</stand>
			<stand>	You are supposed to take a 10 minute break after 50 minutes of playing!	</stand>
			<stand>	This is a hypothetical situation. If you stay still and do not do anything, then Alice will get hungry. If you do not do anything about Alice being hungry, Alice must leave her master... *Sob*	</stand>
			<stand>	I can do anything you want, master! I can go grocery shopping, prepare dinner and clean the house...I can do anything you imagine!	</stand>
			<stand>	Actually Alice has a dream to become a maid uniform designer! Heh, don't you think it is a great idea?	</stand>
			<stand>	I have secret news from my connection. Would you like to hear?	</stand>
			<connect>	Jesus Christ! Stop freaking me out when I'm doing my makeup!	</connect>
			<connect>	Have you ever heard the saying that today is a desired tomorrow for a man who died yesterday?	</connect>
			<levelup>	My heart is full as you leveled up!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yes, yes! Hold onto it! Let's level up one more time today!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Sometimes...I am wonder how it would be if I get married a man that was just like you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well done, well done! You did a good job!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Wee! You are my hero!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry. Let me clean this mess really quick.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Thank you for trusting me, even if I am careless sometimes.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	A respectable maid must be pure in body and mind.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Let's say I'm covered in dark dust. Would that make me Cinderella?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Alice must shake the dust off her body often. Otherwise she will look dirty.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*Phew* Much much cleaner.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Do you think the house looks better now? Can I take a break?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I love my job, but sometimes it is very tiresome. *Sigh...*	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Thank you much for the food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I will get to work right away!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It is good to exercise after a meal. Yes, that's good for your health.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I am Alice the maid who always enjoys cleaning~		</feeding>
			<feeding>	What are the materials to make White Potions? Sometimes Alice gets curious.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	If you eliminate the enemy, I will clean the mess afterwards.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope you will defeat the enemy and grab the item as soon as you can. Otherwise I will sweep them all together.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	*Swish swish*...*Swish swish*...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I really like to see you trying hard to be stronger. You know?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I love the beads of sweat on your brow as you deliver your blows to an enemy.	</hunting>
			<danger>	I don't think you are in danger yet! Are you?	</danger>
			<danger>	Is there anyone here who can heal my master?! Please~!	</danger>
			<danger>	I wonder why you always choose the hard way.	</danger>
			<danger>	*Sob sob* I didn't know you're going through so much difficulty to earn White Potions for me. *Sob sob* I'm so sorry!	</danger>
			<danger>	Master, I hope you will not worry me longer.	</danger>
			<dead>	The ground seems to be so cold...	</dead>
			<dead>	Can't you see the Grim Reaper over there? Or am I the only one who sees him here?	</dead>
			<dead>	I heard the Grim Reaper comes to take some of your experience points when you lie down on the ground. So, get up now, quick!	</dead>
			<dead>	Ah~ The ground seems so warm and comfy under the sunlight...	</dead>
			<dead>	Do not hold a grudge but enter Nirvana, master. I will perform a sacrificial rite every year for you~	</dead>
			<stand>	Sometimes, Alice wishes to have some friends.	</stand>
			<stand>	Sometimes, I miss my cat...	</stand>
			<stand>	You are supposed to take a 10 minute break after 50 minutes of playing!	</stand>
			<stand>	Here is a hypothetical situation. If you stay still and do not do anything, then Alice will get hungry. If you do not do anything about Alice being hungry, Alice must leave her master...*Sob*	</stand>
			<stand>	I can do anything you want, master! I can go grocery shopping, prepare dinner and clean the house...I can do anything you imagine!	</stand>
			<stand>	Actually Alice has a dream to become a maid uniform designer! Heh, don't you think it is a great idea?	</stand>
			<stand>	I was told that my sisters are living somewhere. I hope I will be able to see them soon.	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey, it's my master! It's my master! Aren't you jealous of me, guys?	</connect>
			<connect>	Tah dah! Here comes my master!	</connect>
			<connect>	I cleaned our house while you're gone, master!	</connect>
			<connect>	While you're gone, strange people needled me. So I hope you will not leave me alone for too long.	</connect>
			<connect>	Do you know what time I hate the most? It is the 'weekly maintenance' time! Because you cannot come to me even if you want to...	</connect>
			<connect>	Let's enjoy today, let's have fun tomorrow, let's be energetic on the day after tomorrow! Er, did that make sense?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Everytime you level up, an angel flaps her wings! It makes my job harder...but still....congratulations!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You are getting stronger and stronger every day. I am so proud of you...heh heh!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Weee! Alice is so happy for you!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	There is nothing you cannot do if you do your best!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	People say there are tons and tons of perverts...I know you will protect me from those people!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry. Let me clean this mess really quick.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Thank you for trusting me even if I am careless sometimes.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	A respectable maid must be pure in body and mind.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Let's say I'm covered in dark dust. Would that make me Cinderella?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Alice must shake the dust off her body often. Otherwise she will look dirty.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*Phew* Yes, that's much cleaner	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Do you think the house looks better now? Can I take a break?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I love my job, but sometimes it is very tiresome. *Sigh...*	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	No more...please, no more...Alice cannot move...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	If you feed me more...the laces on the Alice's apron will get tighter on her waist.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I think I need a new apron...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Wah! I gained 1 pound! Why can't you feed me at the right time?!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	If you eliminate the enemy, I will clean the mess afterwards.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hope you will defeat the enemy and grab the item as soon as you can. Otherwise, I will sweep them altogether.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Today's tears and sweat will result in a successful class change...have you heard of this saying?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I suggest you to use the ultimate skill 'thousandpalmspectacleeffectgorila'.	</hunting>
			<danger>	You know, the color red is used for warnings. A warning...wah! Master!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Red petal...white petal...a pretty girl Flo...wah?! You're in red, master!	</danger>
			<danger>	You are in serious danger!	</danger>
			<danger>	Are you just careless, or are you just not thinking?	</danger>
			<danger>	You're not using the 'Berserk' skill as an excuse, are you?	</danger>
			<dead>	Umm...master...?! I can see your eyes are moving.	</dead>
			<dead>	Come on, come on!	</dead>
			<dead>	Hm...? You look like a student relaxing during summer vacation!	</dead>
			<dead>	You know you cannot hunt anything other than cockroaches while you're lying on your stomach?	</dead>
			<dead>	Ah~ let me guess what that stance is. Isn't it the ultimate fighting skill 'Beg for mercy?'	</dead>
			<stand>	I have thought what would be good for my nickname...and I got one now. How about 733t mad Alice!?	</stand>
			<stand>	Sometimes I wish I could have more friends...	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you think one of these days, the development team would update the 'Pretty Girl Troops?'	</stand>
			<stand>	Excuse me, there! Will you pick up the trash you just threw near my precious master?	</stand>
			<stand>	Stop looking at me and go back to work, guys!	</stand>
			<stand>	I love this soft apron you gave me...well sometimes, more skin than I want shows through...	</stand>
			<stand>	As I am getting better and better at sweeping, the more I have to do. Do you know why?	</stand>
			<stand>	If I work harder, will you love me more?	</stand>
			<stand>	I always enjoy cleaning.	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you looking at the sky...master?	</stand>
			<stand>	Did you find a pretty girl...?	</stand>
			<stand>	Watch out, there is a pile of dust near you.	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome back, master.	</connect>
			<connect>	I am so happy to be with you.	</connect>
			<connect>	I am so glad that you have come back..		</connect>
			<connect>	Good day, master. Thank you for coming back.	</connect>
			<connect>	Wee~ it's my master! I already feel today will be a good day!	</connect>
			<connect>	Ah...Does this feeling mean...Master!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Ah~ You just get greater and greater. Alice is sooo impressed! *Heart pounds*		</levelup>
			<levelup>	Every time you level up, Alice wants to do anything she can do for her master.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	So, what do you want to do from now on, master?		</levelup>
			<levelup>	Okay, that's it for today. Time for fun! Let's play with Alice, please?		</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry. Let me clean this mess really quick.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Thank you for trusting me, even if I am careless sometimes.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry! I am so sorry!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	A respectable maid must be pure in body and mind.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Let's say I'm covered in dark dust. Would that make me Cinderella?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Alice must shake the dust off her body often. Otherwise she will look dirty.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Phew...yes, now I feel clean.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Do you think the house looks better now? Can I take a break?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I love my job but sometimes it is very tiresome. *Sigh...*	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</alice>
	<zherlthsh>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Hey! Feeding me's your first priority, got it?!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You're the worst slave I've ever had. This meal is late, worm!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Took your sweet time, didn't you?!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	So that's it?! Oh well!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	You better have your potions ready, you little crybaby.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	If that's not a Poring, you're in for a beating!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Don't you think this enemy's way too strong for you! Give it up!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hahahaha, finally! Your HP is red!	</danger>
			<danger>	Die, die die! Hahahaha!	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh~ Doesn't the ground look so comfy?	</danger>
			<dead>	I'm speechless. I'm just so... happy!	</dead>
			<dead>	What now? Did you fight something way too powerful than you? I should have known!	</dead>
			<dead>	As usual.	</dead>
			<dead>	So how you feel? Comfy?	</dead>
			<stand>	What are you doing, weakling? That's why people think you're stupid!	</stand>
			<stand>	MOVE! No time for window shopping!	</stand>
			<stand>	What are you doing, sitting there like you're in fantasy land?!	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey! Move your ass!	</stand>
			<stand>	Finally, you get up. You're the laziest slave I've ever had!	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, if you have time to be idle, go check my status window!	</stand>
			<stand>	Don't expect money to just fall into your wallet! Find something to hunt!	</stand>
			<connect>	Ah~ It's you, the loser.	</connect>
			<connect>	So, what's your schedule today? Have you even planned it out?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey...stop logging on and off but feed me!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hello, stranger.	</connect>
			<levelup>	What?! You can level up?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Man, it takes you forever to level up.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Hah! I'm so beautiful...!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Hello, mirror. Here's something to reflect!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Huh, I put my make-up on pretty well today.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	*Sigh...*		</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Sometimes I can't breathe under this mask!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Don't act so surprised ! This isn't the first time you've seen me without the mask!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Want me to make a doughnut?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I smoke when I'm stressed out, but I don't think it's helping me. Oh well...still I can't quit.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	If you're a smoker, you oughta quit. Me? Shuddap and lemme alone!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Ah~ That hit the spot!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey, would you like some?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	The ancients believed that eating one's heart would give you the owner's power. You know that?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I don't think I could get any power out of a Verit's heart though...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yes, this is pretty good.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	There're lots of ways to cook a Verit's heart. Baked, steamed, stewed, Verit's heart burger...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hmmm...this is good too.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hey, hey! I want fresh food! Fresh food with warm blood!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	How long do you plan to play in this weakling area?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	All I've seen you hunt are Porings... How're you gonna reach the next level?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Come on, come on! Show me blood! Muhahahahah!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	There you go! That's how you kill!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Once you start attacking, don't stop! Oh God, don't stop!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Destroy it!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey! That thing's not deadly, is it?	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh~ Somehow I figured this'd happen!	</danger>
			<danger>	What were you thinking? Do you even know you're in danger?	</danger>
			<danger>	You'd better use a Fly Wing or drink some potions before it's too late. Got nothing? Then it's time to die!	</danger>
			<danger>	Heh! You're dying!	</danger>
			<danger>	Do you mind if I take your heart out? Of course...after you die!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey...remember I'm not a Nine Tail. I only need your heart, not your liver!		</danger>
			<dead>	Okay now, if you don't restart, I'm gonna take your heart out. Just as I promised.	</dead>
			<dead>	When I see you dead...I get excited for some reason! Wee~	</dead>
			<dead>	You like being dead? You do it often enough, so come to my world already! Just try not to get eaten by demons.	</dead>
			<dead>	So, how do you like eating mud?	</dead>
			<dead>	Soon your corpse will be rotten and infested with maggots. Hohohohohoh!	</dead>
			<dead>	So, now you know how it feels like to be dead, huh?	</dead>
			<stand>	MOVE!	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you thinking of your ex or what?	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm gonna kick your ass with these high heels if you don't move now!	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey! Move along if you don't want to get whipped!	</stand>
			<stand>	Shopping for items is for nobles like me, not peons like you.	</stand>
			<stand>	Yeah yeah, getting the best items might save you later.	</stand>
			<stand>	Stop looking about, MOVE!	</stand>
			<stand>	STOP BEING STUPID!	</stand>
			<connect>	There you go.	</connect>
			<connect>	So where were you last night, huh?	</connect>
			<connect>	Are you having a bad day or what?	</connect>
			<connect>	Yes, it is an honor to look upon nobility. Hohohoho!	</connect>
			<connect>	Since you're here, it is the time for you to clean my high heels! Hohohohoho!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Okay okay! You've had your fun, so now it's the time to feed me!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Don't forget that you used to be a weakling!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Geez, always stepping forward. Kinda like Minorous.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	La la la!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	I'm the most beautiful! Don't you agree?	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Do you think you'll meet another woman like me? Hell no, I'm the most beautiful demon ever!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Sometimes, I feel frustrated!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Maintaining this lustrous hair takes a lot of work!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Hah~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*Phew*	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Yeah, sometimes smoking makes me so relieved~		</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Sometimes is okay, but not always! Especially around kids, it weakens their bones!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Not bad! It hits the spot!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It is still warm...hmm...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	So yeah, you take good care of me. What, you want a 'Thank you?!'	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yes, this is what I wanted!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ah~ this tastes so good...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Hahahah...hahahah...muhahahah!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hahahaha! Make it cry, make it bleed!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Don't stop it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Punish it! Make it scream!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Stab and smash! Make it feel pain!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Find its weak spot! Make it suffer even more!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	If you stop, it'll attack you anyway. Strike first!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Dodge that! Oh, don't say you're a VIT character!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	How can you survive when you're that sloppy?! Move and dodge!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	MOVE, MOVE, MOVE!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey, are you looking at your health bar or what?	</danger>
			<danger>	Do you wish to die already?	</danger>
			<danger>	MOVE!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, you'll be dead if you don't drink a potion right now!	</danger>
			<danger>	Red means passion, but now it means danger!	</danger>
			<danger>	The red of roses and the red of blood, it's all the same.	</danger>
			<danger>	Ah~ red always reminds me of blood dripping from a human heart...hahahaha!		</danger>
			<dead>	Yeah, it happened as usual. So don't worry.	</dead>
			<dead>	Hey, don't blame me. It was your fault!	</dead>
			<dead>	Everyone dies one of these days.		</dead>
			<dead>	I hope you learn that being alive is a lot more fun than being dead.	</dead>
			<dead>	Now that wasn't so bad. Though, I don't think you saw it coming.	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't blame it on lag. It was your fault!	</dead>
			<dead>	No one can take that much punishment!	</dead>
			<dead>	I hope you learned your lesson.	</dead>
			<stand>	What was that? A nap?	</stand>
			<stand>	What are you doing?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey! Everyone's looking at you strangely. Let's get away!	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you sleeping or what? WAKE UP!	</stand>
			<stand>	Is something happening over there?	</stand>
			<stand>	What are you thinking?	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you getting paid for being this lazy?	</stand>
			<stand>	Okay, now's the time to run!	</stand>
			<stand>	So tell me, what's the plan?	</stand>
			<stand>	MOVE, MOVE!	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you ready for hunt? Or do you still need more time?	</stand>
			<stand>	You know humans are nothing but worms to demons, right? *Piff*		</stand>
			<connect>	Speak of the devil...!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey, haven't you even missed me? Why didn't you come earlier?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations. Now we can go explore even more dangerous areas!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hahaha! Doesn't it feel great to be stronger than others?!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congratulations. Now what?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	So did you think of how you're gonna use your stat and skill points?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Haha...I knew this was coming!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	La la la!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Think? I'm KNOW I'm sexy!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Do you think you could meet another woman like me? Hell no, I'm the most beautiful demon ever!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Sometimes, I feel frustrated!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Maintaining this lustrous hair takes a lot of work!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Hah~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Phew...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Yeah, sometimes smoking gives me suuuch relief~		</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Sometimes a cig is okay, but not always! Especially around kids, it weakens their bones!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Not bad! It hits the spot!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It's still warm...!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	So yeah, you take good care of me. What, you want a 'Thank you?!'	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yes, this is what I wanted!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ah~ this tastes so good...!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hahah! when I see you hunt, I think of a savage boar!		</hunting>
			<hunting>	Attacking is the best defense.		</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ignore defending! Attack and kill!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Just wipe it out and let's move on!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yes! I just know you broke something with that hit!	</hunting>
			<danger>	D-Danger!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, are you checking your health bar?! Get outta here!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, your potions are hot keyed, right?	</danger>
			<danger>	You're not thinking of taking herbs before potions for this situation, are you?	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey... You've got a lot of potions, right? Right?!	</danger>
			<dead>	I guess you like lying down on the ground, huh?	</dead>
			<dead>	What are you doing on the ground?!	</dead>
			<dead>	Just make up your mind!	</dead>
			<dead>	Yeah, so you're upset. But you've gotta continue!	</dead>
			<dead>	I don't like people who don't make up for their mistakes. Get up and think up something!	</dead>
			<stand>	Why are you looking at the clouds when the beautiful thing's right here?	</stand>
			<stand>	Sometimes I get frustrated when I see you sitting still like a moron.	</stand>
			<stand>	Eh, I guess everyone needs to rest now and then.	</stand>
			<stand>	It's better to check your equipment and items than to just afk.	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, make sure you make you use your time wisely, got it?	</stand>
			<stand>	Humans have their days numbered. Don't you feel like planning your life?	</stand>
			<stand>	WHAT ARE YOU THINKING!	</stand>
			<connect>	Good! You came on time!	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey there~		</connect>
			<connect>	So what's the plan?	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome back. So what are we gonna hurt today?	</connect>
			<connect>	Sometimes, I think I miss you.	</connect>
			<connect>	Me? Worried about you not coming back ever again? Never!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Bwahahaha!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Huh!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	So experience makes you stronger, eh?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hahahaha! You enjoy the rewards, I'll enjoy... the punishment.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Hahah! Yes! I hate that angel, but I love it when you get stronger! Yes, more hurting!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	La la la!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Think? I KNOW I'm sexy!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Do you think you'll meet another woman like me? Hell no, I'm the most beautiful demon ever!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Sometimes, I feel frustrated!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Maintaining this lustrous hair takes a lot of work!		</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Hah~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Phew...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Yeah, sometimes smoking gives me suuuch relief~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Sometimes is a cig okay, but not always! Especially around kids, it weakens their bones!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Not bad! That hit the spot!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It's still warm...!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	So yeah, you take good care of me. What, you want a 'Thank you?!'	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yes, this is what I wanted!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ah~ this tastes so good...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hahaha! Make it writhe in agony!		</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yes, it's bleeding, yes!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I love it when you make 'em scream like that! More!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey, this place is okay for you to hunt in, right?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey! This is dangerous!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, check your health bar!	</danger>
			<danger>	If you didn't carry enough potions, run now!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, get the hell out of here!	</danger>
			<danger>	Careful, you're gonna die...!	</danger>
			<dead>	Wah~~~~~~~!	</dead>
			<dead>	Look what you did. Now what am I supposed to do?!	</dead>
			<dead>	I told you!	</dead>
			<dead>	I knew this was coming!	</dead>
			<dead>	I told you to go hunt somewhere else, didn't I?!	</dead>
			<dead>	I didn't expect you to be that weak, fool!	</dead>
			<stand>	Aren't you happy? You get to hang out with me!	</stand>
			<stand>	Sometimes, I feel weird around you.		</stand>
			<stand>	Eh, sorry for treating you kinda mean before.	</stand>
			<stand>	I guess I'm on your side, no matter what happens.	</stand>
			<stand>	Even if I treated you bad, you better not leave me!	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you looking at something?	</stand>
			<stand>	I wonder how Injustice is...He was a really good servant for me.	</stand>
			<stand>	I am wondering how old Raydric is. He was pretty cool for a guy made of metal.	</stand>
			<stand>	If you wanna go to Glast Heim, I can tell you where you should go.	</stand>
			<stand>	Glast Heim isn't complicated. You're just not smart enough to figure your way around!	</stand>
			<stand>	Petites are kind of stupid excuses for dragons, huh?	</stand>
			<stand>	You have a long way to go.	</stand>
			<connect>	Hey you.	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh, you're back.	</connect>
			<connect>	So, where are we gonna explore today? Have you planned out?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hey...	</connect>
			<connect>	*Yawn* Hey, you're back.	</connect>
			<connect>	I think you need some time away from your computer.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Eh, nice work.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Now you can show me off to your friends.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Not too shabby.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Level up again? Huh, you're good at this, I'll give you that.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	La la la!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Think? I KNOW I'm sexy!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Do you think you'll meet another woman like me? Hell no, I'm the most beautiful demon ever!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Sometimes, I feel frustrated!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	It requires a lot of effort to maintain beautiful hair!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Hah~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	*Phew...*	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Yeah, sometimes smoking gives me suuuch relief~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Sometimes a cig is okay, but not always! Especially around kids, it weakens their bones!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</zherlthsh>
	<gobline_xmas>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Finally, some food! I was about to eat my mask!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	More food! I'm not full yet!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yeah, yeah. You oughta know how hungry I am.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	That thing'll just drop Jellopy. Hunt the big game!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hey, who's messing with my pal? Taste my hammer, punk!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Couldn't we hunt after we eat something, huh?	</hunting>
			<danger>	H-hey, I know this is a bad time, but I need some food!	</danger>
			<danger>	Look, I say we run away, and then we eat. We need our strength!	</danger>
			<dead>	See! This is what happens when you neglect me!	</dead>
			<dead>	Nuts! Who's going to feed me now?!	</dead>
			<dead>	I'd feel a little more sorry for you if you fed me a little more!	</dead>
			<stand>	I know my mask covers my mouth, but I need to eat, you know!	</stand>
			<stand>	Sooo... When are we eating?	</stand>
			<stand>	Man, even Antonio fed me more often than this...	</stand>
			<stand>	See this mask? No one can tell what I'm thinking when I wear this thing.	</stand>
			<connect>	Look, you can give me a cell now, or I can complain all day...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're back just in time! Now, gimme some food.	</connect>
			<levelup>	An angel?! Oh, I thought I was dying of hunger. Wait, wait... I am...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Great, good for you. Now, listen, I'm really hungry...	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Santa Lovin'~!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Kissin'~ And huggin'~~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Do~ You~ Like~ My~ Dance~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Yahoo! Sexay Christmas Time~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Round and round, shining as the sun!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I used to dream of being a ballerino~ What do you think of my tour en l'air?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Another perfect performance! What do you think of my passe, my piroutte?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Finally, some food! I was about to eat my mask!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You should feed me more regularly, you know. I'm small, but I've got an Orc's stomach!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yeah, yeah. You oughta know how hungry I am.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey, who's messing with my pal? Taste my hammer, punk!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yeah, now's the best time for hunting, so let's enjoy ourselves!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Couldn't we hunt after we eat something, huh?	</hunting>
			<danger>	Look, I say we run away, and then we eat. We need our strength!	</danger>
			<danger>	S-stop bleeding! Just... stop... bleeding!	</danger>
			<danger>	I know this is a bad time, but will you feed me already?	</danger>
			<dead>	What th-?! Get up, you! Get up, the world still needs you!	</dead>
			<dead>	Aw, nuts. This isn't good. Come back!	</dead>
			<stand>	I know my mask covers my mouth, but I need to eat, you know!	</stand>
			<stand>	Sooo... When are we eating?	</stand>
			<stand>	Man, even Antonio fed me more often than this...	</stand>
			<stand>	Alright, so where are we going this time?	</stand>
			<stand>	Antonio? Well, we work really well together.	</stand>
			<stand>	See this mask? No one can tell what I'm thinking when I wear this thing.	</stand>
			<connect>	Look, you can give me a cell now, or I can complain all day...	</connect>
			<connect>	Oh good, you're back. Listen, you gotta feed me right now!	</connect>
			<levelup>	An angel?! Those grant wishes, right?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice work. Now can we take a break and eat something?	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Santa Lovin'~!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Kissin'~ And huggin'~~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Do~ You~ Like~ My~ Dance~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Yahoo! Sexay Christmas Time~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Round and round, shining as the sun!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I used to dream of being a ballerino~ What do you think of my tour en l'air?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Another perfect performance! What do you think of my passe, my piroutte?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	This stuff seems hard and crunchy, but it's yummy!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Delicious! It's melting in my mouth!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmm, it's good! It tastes like coffee and milk mixed together,	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Okay, I'm gonna really hit it this time! Come on, Goblin Hero!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yeah, hit him! Beat this jerk up!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yeah, nothing else to do but hunt. Let's enjoy ourselves!	</hunting>
			<danger>	No! R-run away right now! Hurry!	</danger>
			<danger>	Nuts, this doesn't look good! Retreat!	</danger>
			<dead>	Retreat! Retreat! Retr--aw, nuts.	</dead>
			<dead>	Get up! Come on, you have to get up!	</dead>
			<dead>	Why did they stop...? Oh no. Oh, sweet Lord, no...	</dead>
			<stand>	You know, I actually don't know why I keep wearing this freakin' Santa Hat...	</stand>
			<stand>	Alright, so where are we going this time?	</stand>
			<stand>	You know, I'm actually pretty irresistable under this mask. It's totally true!	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, you know that we Goblins hate spiders? They killed our greatest Goblin Hero, Sir Green Goblin!	</stand>
			<stand>	See this mask? No one can tell what I'm thinking when I wear this thing.	</stand>
			<stand>	How is Antonio? We're perfect partners......	</stand>
			<connect>	Heh heh! Heya pal! I'll always be your friend~	</connect>
			<connect>	Heya buddy! Let's get a lot done today, alright?	</connect>
			<connect>	I was wondering when you'd show up! Great, let's go!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Level up? Oh yeeeeah~s	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nothing can stop us! We are the Invincible Single Army!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Santa Lovin'~!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Kissin'~ And huggin'~~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Do~ You~ Like~ My~ Dance~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Yahoo! Sexay Christmas Time~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Round and round, shining as the sun!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I used to dream of being a ballerino~ What do you think of my tour en l'air?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Another perfect performance! What do you think of my passe, my piroutte?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	.... </perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	.... </perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	You don't understand, it just tastes so good~	</feeding>
			<feeding>	*Urp* Ahh, that hit the spot! Now I'm finally full!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Delicious! It's melting in my mouth!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	This could happen to you again! And again! You wanna stay down!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	This is what happens when you don't pay protection money!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Oh, it hurts?! Stop crying, stop crying, ya sissy!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Nuts, it looks like the tables have turned! We better run!	</danger>
			<danger>	Forget these guys, let's get out of here!	</danger>
			<dead>	Aw, nuts! Don't worry, we'll get guys later!	</dead>
			<dead>	No! That's it, we'll make these fool's pay!	</dead>
			<dead>	Aw, crud. Don't worry, those guys were playing dirty...	</dead>
			<stand>	You know, I actually don't know why I keep wearing this freakin' Santa Hat...	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm gonna do my best to be a brave Goblin Hero!	</stand>
			<stand>	Alright, so where are we going this time?	</stand>
			<stand>	See this mask? No one can tell what I'm thinking when I wear this thing.	</stand>
			<stand>	You know, I'm actually pretty irresistable under this mask. It's totally true!	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, you know that we Goblins hate spiders? They killed our greatest Goblin Hero, Sir Green Goblin!	</stand>
			<stand>	So who are we beating up today?	</stand>
			<connect>	Heh heh! Heya pal! I'll always be your friend~	</connect>
			<connect>	Heya buddy! Let's get a lot done today, alright?	</connect>
			<connect>	I was wondering when you'd show up! Great, let's go!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Who can stop us from going? We're happier than a pair of lovers!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	What the...?! An angel? Where did it go? C-come back!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Santa Lovin'~!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Kissin'~ And huggin'~~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Do~ You~ Like~ My~ Dance~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Yahoo! Sexay Christmas Time~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Round and round, shining as the sun!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I used to dream of being a ballerino~ What do you think of my tour en l'air?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Another perfect performance! What do you think of my passe, my piroutte?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	...	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	*Urp* So... Much... Food...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I ate too much! I almost threw up a little in my m-mask! -_-	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Please, I'm stuffed! I can't eat anymore...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey, what's the color of your crystal?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm gonna hit it this time! I'm gonna be a Goblin Hero!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yeah, now's the best time for hunting, so let's enjoy ourselves!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Singles' fate is up to you! Go, go!	</danger>
			<danger>	Oh no! Antonio, help us!	</danger>
			<dead>	Come on, wake up! Wait, maybe I could wake you with the stench of Antonio's sock...	</dead>
			<dead>	I guess you can't win 'em all. Hey, but you'll do better next time.	</dead>
			<dead>	No! Get up! O-oh well, there'll be other chances for you.	</dead>
			<stand>	You know, I actually don't know why I keep wearing this freakin' Santa Hat...	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm gonna do my best to be a brave Goblin Hero!	</stand>
			<stand>	Alright, so where are we going this time?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, you know that we Goblins hate spiders? They killed our greatest Goblin Hero, Sir Green Goblin!	</stand>
			<stand>	See this mask? No one can tell what I'm thinking when I wear this thing.	</stand>
			<stand>	You know, I'm actually pretty irresistable under this mask. It's totally true!	</stand>
			<connect>	Heh heh! Heya pal! I'll always be your friend~	</connect>
			<connect>	Heya buddy! Let's get a lot done today, alright?	</connect>
			<connect>	I was wondering when you'd show up! Great, let's go!	</connect>
			<levelup>	What the...?! An angel? Where did it go? C-come back!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	H-hey, share your experience points with me so I can become a Goblin Hero!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Santa Lovin'~!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Kissin'~ And huggin'~~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Do~ You~ Like~ My~ Dance~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Yahoo! Sexay Christmas Time~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Round and round, shining as the sun!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I used to dream of being a ballerino~ What do you think of my tour en l'air?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Another perfect performance! What do you think of my passe, my piroutte?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	....	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	....	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</gobline_xmas>
	<P_CHUNG_E>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Hmpf! What makes you think this is enough food for me?!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	...*Munch Munch* Hey, this is pretty good!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yummy! I love this!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hungry! I'm so huuungry!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Don't bother me when I'm eating! We can talk when I'm done!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I don't like how that monster looks! Do something about it!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Let's get out of here, and go someplace safe where we can eat!	</danger>
			<danger>	B-be careful! I think we should run away!	</danger>
			<dead>	You know what your problem is? You're way weaker than me!	</dead>
			<dead>	Hello? Hello? Can you get up? Um... Hello?	</dead>
			<dead>	No! I don't like this! Come on, stand up!	</dead>
			<stand>	Hungry! I'm so huuungry!	</stand>
			<stand>	I don't know about you, but I'm hungry!	</stand>
			<stand>	*Gkruguruhk* Ah! I can hear my stomach! D-don't listen to it!	</stand>
			<stand>	Ugh. I don't like this weather!	</stand>
			<stand>	This isn't my world. I'm afraid that people will forget all about us dolls...	</stand>
			<connect>	Look who decided to show up... Hmpf. I wasn't going to leave or anything, but...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're here? I mean, it's not like I was waiting for you or anything...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're not leaving this time, are you? Hmpf! Just go away!	</connect>
			<levelup>	You leveled up? That's nice... But why are we missing out on meals?!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're stronger now? That means you can get me something to eat now, right?	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	*Gasp Gasp* Heart... Made of breath... Steam...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Don't you want to buy me a mitten?!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hiyah!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	...? Mmm?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Let's take a break, huh?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Are you hungry too? Let's eat... Or I'm not going!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	No performance	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Hmpf! What makes you think this is enough food for me?!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	...*Munch Munch* Hey, this is pretty good!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Yummy! I love this!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hungry! I'm so huuungry!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Don't bother me when I'm eating! We can talk when I'm done!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I don't like how that monster looks! Do something about it!	</hunting>
			<danger>	B-be careful! I think we should run away!	</danger>
			<danger>	Let's get out of here, and go someplace safe where we can eat!	</danger>
			<dead>	You know what your problem is? You're way weaker than me!	</dead>
			<dead>	Hello? Hello? Can you get up? Um... Hello?	</dead>
			<dead>	No! I don't like this! Come on, stand up!	</dead>
			<stand>	Shut up, shut up, shut up!	</stand>
			<stand>	*Gkruguruhk* Ah! I can hear my stomach! D-don't listen to it!	</stand>
			<stand>	I don't know about you, but I'm hungry!	</stand>
			<stand>	Ugh. I don't like this weather!	</stand>
			<stand>	Your fire became small now...	</stand>
			<stand>	This isn't my world. I'm afraid that people will forget all about us dolls...	</stand>
			<connect>	Look who decided to show up... Hmpf. I wasn't going to leave or anything, but...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're here? I mean, it's not like I was waiting for you or anything...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're not leaving this time, are you? Hmpf! Just go away!	</connect>
			<levelup>	You're stronger now? That means you can get me something to eat now, right?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You must be pretty happy about this. Congratulations!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	*Gasp Gasp* Heart... Made of breath... Steam...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Don't you want to buy me a mitten?!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hiyah!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	...? Mmm?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Let's take a break, huh?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Are you hungry too? Let's eat... Or I'm not going!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	No performance	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	...*Munch Munch* Hey, this is pretty good!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmm, I've been waiting to eat this!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you~	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Oh! That was a nice attack!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I hate these guys! Make them go away!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Can you do a spin kick? Try it out! I think it'll work!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Come on! I'm gonna fight too!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Whoa, we better back away!	</danger>
			<danger>	Uh oh, these guys might be too strong!	</danger>
			<dead>	What th--No! S-top lying there like that!	</dead>
			<dead>	Wh-what were you trying to prove?! Noooo!	</dead>
			<dead>	Come on! Stand up, I don't like this!!	</dead>
			<stand>	Huh? I didn't say anything. Um, I like rice cakes?	</stand>
			<stand>	Shut up, shut up, shut up!	</stand>
			<stand>	Ugh. I don't like this weather!	</stand>
			<stand>	This rice cake? No, you can't have it!	</stand>
			<stand>	The fire is getting smaller...	</stand>
			<stand>	This isn't my world. I'm afraid that people will forget all about us dolls...	</stand>
			<connect>	Look who decided to show up... Hmpf. I wasn't going to leave or anything, but...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're here? I mean, it's not like I was waiting for you or anything...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're not leaving this time, are you? Hmpf! Just go away!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Now that you're stronger, maybe I'll give you a rice cake.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	That's decent...	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	*Gasp Gasp* Heart... Made of breath... Steam...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Don't you want to buy me a mitten?!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hiyah!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	...? Mmm?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Let's take a break, huh?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Let's relax over here. Take a seat!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	No special performance	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Stop, stop! Too much food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Whoa, I'm getting pretty full...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Quit it, are you trying to make me fat?!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Nice! That was a good hit!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yes yes! Can you do a spin kick? Try it out! I think it'll work!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Come on! I'm gonna fight too!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Get back where it's safe! I-I can handle this!	</danger>
			<danger>	Uh oh, these guys are pretty strong...	</danger>
			<dead>	Wh-what were you trying to prove?! Noooo!	</dead>
			<dead>	Nooo! I failed to protect you!	</dead>
			<dead>	Umm? Wait! Why are you lying down?!?!	</dead>
			<stand>	Shut up, shut up, shut up!	</stand>
			<stand>	Ugh. I don't like this weather!	</stand>
			<stand>	I didn't say anything. Um, I like rice cakes?	</stand>
			<stand>	This isn't my world. I'm afraid that people will forget all about us dolls...	</stand>
			<stand>	The fire is getting smaller...	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, wait for me!	</stand>
			<connect>	Look who decided to show up... Hmpf. I wasn't going to leave or anything, but...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're here? I mean, it's not like I was waiting for you or anything...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're not leaving this time, are you? Hmpf! Just go away!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Now that you're stronger, maybe I'll give you a rice cake.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	That's decent...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! You must be pretty happy!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	*Gasp Gasp* Heart... Made of breath... Steam...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Don't you want to buy me a mitten?!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hiyah!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	...? Mmm?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Let's take a break, huh?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Let's relax over here. Take a seat!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	No performance	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	S-so... Full! N-no more!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Seriously! This is too much food!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mmm... That was good, but I can't eat any more!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hiyah! Spin kick! Let me see you do it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Come on! I'm gonna fight too!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	That was great! Smash them all up!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Oh no, it's getting dangerous! Move back, I'll handle this!	</danger>
			<danger>	N-no! These guys are too strong for sure!	</danger>
			<dead>	Wh-what were you trying to prove?! Noooo!	</dead>
			<dead>	No! Y-you have to come back!	</dead>
			<dead>	Nooo! I failed to protect you!	</dead>
			<stand>	Shut up, shut up, shut up!	</stand>
			<stand>	You will pay for this! Wait for me general!	</stand>
			<stand>	I looove rice cakes! Did you know that?	</stand>
			<stand>	No!! I can't give you my rice cake!	</stand>
			<stand>	Ha! I can't stand this cold weather!	</stand>
			<stand>	Your fire is getting smaller...	</stand>
			<stand>	You'll know what I'm talking about... Someday!	</stand>
			<connect>	Look who decided to show up... Hmpf. I wasn't going to leave or anything, but...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're here? I mean, it's not like I was waiting for you or anything...	</connect>
			<connect>	You're not leaving this time, are you? Hmpf! Just go away!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Now that you're stronger, maybe I'll give you a rice cake.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	That's decent...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! You must be pretty happy!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	*Gasp Gasp* Heart... Made of breath... Steam...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Don't you want to buy me a mitten?!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hiyah!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	...? Mmm?	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Let's take a break, huh?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Let's relax over here. Take a seat!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	No performance	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</P_CHUNG_E>
	<event_ricecake>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Gulu Gulu!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I am so hungry I feel that I am becoming a flat rice cake now!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm going to eat my own flesh if you're one more minute late!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Do you think we can find something edible after defeating him?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	What's the color of the herb that you're carrying?!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I must be too hungry to think that it's green in color	</hunting>
			<danger>	That's because you didn't give me the herbs.	</danger>
			<danger>	That rod looks like a white biscuit.	</danger>
			<dead>	Oh, master! You're dead now too...	</dead>
			<dead>	I miss my herbs...	</dead>
			<dead>	I wish I will be reincarnated as herb in my next life.	</dead>
			<stand>	Are you trying to turn me into a ricecake?	</stand>
			<stand>	I hate ricecake. You should give me more herbs...	</stand>
			<stand>	You shouldn't mingle that much with others!	</stand>
			<stand>	Is that the herb that I think it is?	</stand>
			<connect>	How dare of you to visit me after so long?	</connect>
			<connect>	I am freezing...	</connect>
			<connect>	Do you bring along any herbs	</connect>
			<levelup>	Why don't you gather some herbs before the angel appears?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Is it time for me to have my herbs now?	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Oh... If I still can't become QQ!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Phew~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Heeya Hiiya Hew ~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Pang ~ Hew~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I am satisfied with the love you give me ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	The love you give is more than sufficient ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Phew ~ Hiiyaa	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh! That looks familiar!	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Gulu Gulu!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm so hungry I'm going to become a flat ricecake now.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Will I become a herb cake if I eat so many of these?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I was thinking maybe we can take honey for a change...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Please add in some beans ~	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Only if I have a biscuit rod...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Take a break before you continue to hunt anymore	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Won't you feel hungry if you keep hunting like this?	</hunting>
			<danger>	That rod looks like a white biscuit	</danger>
			<danger>	Doesn't it look like the ricecake in the picture?	</danger>
			<dead>	I wish I will be reincarnated as herb in my next life.	</dead>
			<dead>	I'm freezing if I continue to lie on this icy floor	</dead>
			<stand>	Although I wish to become a QQ....	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you trying to make me into a white rice cake?	</stand>
			<stand>	What's the color of your heart?	</stand>
			<stand>	Is that the herb that is shown in the picture?	</stand>
			<connect>	I'm freezing...	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome... I'm freezing just to wait for you ~	</connect>
			<levelup>	Since you've gotten your level, why don't you give me some herbs.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Woah, an angel!!!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Haargh... If I still fail to become QQ!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Phew~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Heeya Hiiya Hew ~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Pang ~ Hew~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I am satisfied with the love you give me ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	The love you give is more than sufficient ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Phew ~ Hiiyaa	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh! That looks familiar!	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	The herbs have a different taste today...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I can feel your love from the herb you gave me.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Will I become a herb cake if I eat so many of these?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ah~~ Delicious ~	</feeding>
			<hunting>	You have become a QQ too!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Take a break before you continue to hunt anymore	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Feel my rice cake strike!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Your HP! It's become as red as the tomato sauce	</danger>
			<danger>	Only if I had a rice cake rod...	</danger>
			<danger>	You won't restore any health with my food. Just drink your stupid potion ~	</danger>
			<dead>	I don't like the way you lie down. Stand up now!	</dead>
			<dead>	I will be frozen if you keep lying there.	</dead>
			<stand>	Don't get too friendly with strangers!	</stand>
			<stand>	The next time I'm born, I want to be a rice cake coated with honey	</stand>
			<stand>	I am your backup food supply	</stand>
			<stand>	Gugu Lulu ~~	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you trying to turn me into a white rice cake?	</stand>
			<stand>	Rice Cake! Come and get your delicious Rice Cake ~	</stand>
			<connect>	This will be a QQ day too	</connect>
			<connect>	Welcome, I'm almost frozen while waiting for you here~	</connect>
			<levelup>	Woah, congratulations, dude! ~	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're going to become a QQ too!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Haargh... If I still fail to become QQ!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Phew~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Heeya Hiiya Hew ~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Pang ~ Hew~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I am satisfied with the love you give me ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	The love you give is more than sufficient ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Phew ~ Hiiyaa	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh! That looks familiar!	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Will I become a human if I ate the garlic with my food?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	If I eat this too, I will become very hot!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I am already filled with so many green herbs...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I have my nose bleed in the adventures of my younger days!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ahhh... This is the best medicine ever....!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	What's the color of your herbs?!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Taste the power of my rice cake strike!	</hunting>
			<danger>	You won't restore any health with my food. Just drink your stupid potion ~	</danger>
			<danger>	Master! Eat me to spare your life!	</danger>
			<danger>	Feel free to eat me. You can start from my head...	</danger>
			<dead>	If you continue to stay here, I will be frozen	</dead>
			<dead>	How about biting me for a try	</dead>
			<stand>	I am the rice cake with the best brand.	</stand>
			<stand>	Did you smell that? That's my perfume - Rice Cake No. 5!	</stand>
			<stand>	I support the local goods. So, I won't be using any imported perfume.	</stand>
			<stand>	If I get sick, I'm sure my friends will take good care of me.	</stand>
			<stand>	I really envy the smooth skin of that white bun	</stand>
			<stand>	The sliced rice cake really looks macho.	</stand>
			<connect>	I want to be cute today ~	</connect>
			<connect>	It's going to be another cute day ~	</connect>
			<levelup>	You have become cuter now!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice to meet you, Angel. I'm rice cake!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Haargh... If I still fail to become QQ!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Phew~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Heeya Hiiya Hew ~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Pang ~ Hew~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I am satisfied with the love you give me ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	The love you give is more than sufficient ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Phew ~ Hiiyaa	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh! That looks familiar!	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Ohhh, I can feel that taste of honey	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Mrs. Rice Cake is getting angry now!..	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Stop! I have had more than enough..	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I used to work out when I was in the moon ~	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Don't worry. Just take a bite from my head...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I saw my share of blood during my younger days!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Feel my rice cake strike! ~	</hunting>
			<danger>	Don't eat my herbs. If you want to restore your health, drink the potions ~	</danger>
			<danger>	Master! Eat me to spare your own life!!	</danger>
			<danger>	Don't worry. You can start eating from my head...	</danger>
			<dead>	You can still take another bite of me	</dead>
			<dead>	You and me are enough to make a delicious rice cake dish	</dead>
			<dead>	When will there be anyone who's willing to mourn our defeat?	</dead>
			<stand>	Please don't cook me in a microwave oven!	</stand>
			<stand>	Did you smell that? That's my perfume - Rice Cake No. 5!	</stand>
			<stand>	I support the local goods. So, I won't be using any imported perfume.	</stand>
			<stand>	I have a strong sense of smell ~	</stand>
			<stand>	I have been waiting for you all night	</stand>
			<stand>	Have you forgotten about me?	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you like that cute little girl over there?	</stand>
			<connect>	I'm going to be a herb cake if you come any moment later	</connect>
			<connect>	This will be another cute day ~	</connect>
			<levelup>	Hello, nice to meet you. I'm the almighty rice cake!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're the best!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	You're really something master ~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Haargh... If I still fail to become QQ!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Phew~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Heeya Hiiya Hew ~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Pang ~ Hew~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I am satisfied with the love you give me ~	</perfor_3>	
			<perfor_3>	The love you give is more than sufficient ~	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Phew ~ Hiiyaa	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Oh! That looks familiar!	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</event_ricecake>
	<XMAS_LUNATIC>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Starving to death~~~ Hurry, Hurry!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It's the perfect time! Thank you for the food! :)	</feeding>
			<hunting>	You're so fantastic!!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hurry up and finish hunting so that we can go eat~	</hunting>
			<danger>	Ah~~ snowing santa town was also red just like that...	</danger>
			<danger>	Need Potion and Food!	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't die...T.T	</dead>
			<dead>	Please save my master... T.T	</dead>
			<stand>	..... Don't you smell candy?	</stand>
			<stand>	Where are you going? Candy Store??	</stand>
			<connect>	Hi! I was waiting for you to eat together~	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi! I'm in the mood for sweet candy today!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Wow! You became more stronger! Congratulation!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	HeHe, Here is a Angel of Candy~ Nice to meet you~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Sometimes carrot is very tasty~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hurray! High Jump~ Hat is too heavy~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Christmas makes me really happy!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Don't you hear the carol?	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Wow, Thank you~	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Why don't you eat something good too~	</feeding>
			<hunting>	YES! Right!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	You can get more stronger! Fighting!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Be careful! Run if too dangerous..!	</danger>
			<danger>	Too dangerous. Please take some rest between. T.T	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't be so sad... T_T	</dead>
			<dead>	T_T Let's go back to the town and get ready again!	</dead>
			<stand>	HuHu, It feels like something good is about to happen.	</stand>
			<stand>	I want to go snowing town with you, master~	</stand>
			<connect>	Hello! I was waiting for you. ^_^	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi~! What a great day again!	</connect>
			<levelup>	You are getting stronger! Congratulation~	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Contratulation! Let's keep it up!! GoGo!!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Sometimes carrot is very tasty~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hurray! High Jump~ Hat is too heavy~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Christmas makes me really happy!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Don't you hear the carol?	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Suitable amount of food is good for the health.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Wow~ Thanks again~	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Everyday training~	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Yes, that's it! Right! My master is getting stronger~~	</hunting>
			<danger>	Be CAREFULL! Potion! POTION!	</danger>
			<danger>	Too dangerous! Let's retreat for now!	</danger>
			<dead>	You cannot always win, right?	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't give up! You can try again!	</dead>
			<stand>	Well.. What should I start with today??	</stand>
			<stand>	Ok? OK?? Let's go eat together~	</stand>
			<connect>	Hi! I was waiting for you to eat together~	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi! What is the menu today?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Wow! You became more stronger! Congratulation!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yeah~~ It's an angel~ Nice to meet you~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Sometimes carrot is very tasty~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hurray! High Jump~ Hat is too heavy~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Christmas makes me really happy!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Don't you hear the carol?	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	T.T Too FULL... That's too much....	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Eating alot isn't always good..	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Since I have full a stomach, I can help you with hunting!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	... Too full....I will fall down...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Too dangerous! Let's retreat for now!	</danger>
			<danger>	Got dangerous~! Take your potion fast!!	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't die...T.T	</dead>
			<dead>	Please save my master... T.T	</dead>
			<stand>	Mas..ter... I feel little hungry...	</stand>
			<stand>	Ok? OK?? Let's go eat together~	</stand>
			<connect>	Hi! I was waiting for you to eat together~	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi! What is the menu today?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Wow! You became more stronger! Congratulation!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yeah~~ It's an angel~ Nice to meet you~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Sometimes carrot is very tasty~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hurray! High Jump~ Hat is too heavy~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Christmas makes me really happy!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Don't you hear the carol?	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	OMG... No more!! Body is too heavy... </feeding>
			<feeding>	I feel dying here!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I have to make empty stomach for fast attack...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	NextNextNextNext!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	In this kind of situation, I really want to take out all candies from my stomach. Should be alot.	</danger>
			<danger>	You're gonna die! Too dangerous!	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't die...T.T	</dead>
			<dead>	Please save my master... T.T	</dead>
			<stand>	Mas..ter... I feel little hungry...	</stand>
			<stand>	Let's go eat together~~ ok? OK??	</stand>
			<connect>	Hi! I was waiting for you to eat together~	</connect>
			<connect>	Hi! What is the menu today?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Wow! You became more stronger! Congratulation!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yeah~~ It's an angel~ Nice to meet you~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Sometimes carrot is very tasty~	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Hurray! High Jump~ Hat is too heavy~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Christmas makes me really happy!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Don't you hear the carol?	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</XMAS_LUNATIC>
	<TIKBALANG>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	I'm hungry. Give me something to eat. Or else I will go on strike.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I would have left you long ago if I was hungrier.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Yes, that's it!! Good!! But is it a long time until mealtime?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Whoa... Nice. Only thing left is for me to be fed.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Hey... you sure? Looks dangerous. Go kill yourself but will you feed me before you do that?	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, be careful. Nobody will feed me if the KP is gone.	</danger>
			<dead>	Get up! I'm hungry. Get up now!! KP!!	</dead>
			<dead>	KP!! You'll freeze to death falling asleep here!	</dead>
			<stand>	KP! You're drooling all over the food. Give me food!!	</stand>
			<stand>	Aren't there any REAL KPs that can feed me instead of one that just stands there? Hold up your hand where I can see it!!	</stand>
			<connect>	Now you're here? I'm so tired from waiting. Feed me!!	</connect>
			<connect>	Sniff, sniff. Oh... this smell... did you eat something yourself?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Whoa- you've become stronger. Congratulations. Now let's eat, OK?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Bah- I'm hungry I could die and you come here all healthy, do you? Must feel good, right? Hmph?!	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Summoning circle! Appear before me!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Munch, munch. I'd better be off eating air at least.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Summoning circle! Appear before me!!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Munch, munch. I'd better be off eating air at least.	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	I think it's time to eat. Don't you think so?	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Munch, munch. Chew, chew. Hmm... Not bad for a quick mix.	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Great job at battle. Should we eat now?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	There is a saying that a great soldier never battles on an empty stomach. Let's eat.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Huh... what... whoa? Wha?	</danger>
			<danger>	Feh- spit! You like this kind of excitement? Huh?	</danger>
			<dead>	Feh- spit! Come all at once. I fight better than a KP!	</dead>
			<dead>	Better than nothing. Shall we return to the village for now?	</dead>
			<stand>	One! Two! Three! I wasn't just born with these powerful arms and legs of mine.	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey. What are you doing, KP? Thinking of your girl back home?	</stand>
			<connect>	Oh... met just at the right time. I've found a great restaurant. Let's go there today.	</connect>
			<connect>	Good morning! Oh, it's not morning?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Not bad for a KP. I think all you need to do is feed me right.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Huk! Huk! Beautiful angel.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Why now come done upon me for a second?	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Munch, munch. Ha... hmm... nice scent.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Why now come done upon me for a second?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Munch, munch. Ha... hmm... nice scent.	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Morning! Lunch! Dinner! Are the most important meals of a day.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Must chew at least 30 times with each bite!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Been through a lot. Keep on and you'll soon...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Good! Be strong soon.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Potion! Potion! What will you do without me?	</danger>
			<danger>	Definitely! If not now, then sometime in the future. Now let's retreat?	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't be too disappointed. There are days like this.	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't forget today's shame.	</dead>
			<stand>	Loyalty!!	</stand>
			<stand>	Age two! Tikbalang! Reporting for duty.	</stand>
			<connect>	What shall I do today? Please let me know my schedule.	</connect>
			<connect>	You'll need some rest and also some breadth of mind. No need to rush through things.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations. I'd better do my best not to fall back.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	He he he~ Beautiful angel~ you are so pretty.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	I know someone with a horse. I'll try to summon him.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Munch, munch. Delicious~	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I know someone with a horse. I'll try to summon him.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Munch, munch. Delicious~	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Hey, KP! I think there is too much food today.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	There is a lot of food today. Did we get supplies?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Can't move cause I'm too full. KP, go and fight instead of me.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Ouch! My armor broke because I ate too much.	</hunting>
			<danger>	Aren't you overconfident about your ability? Don't push it.	</danger>
			<danger>	Why not take a potion instead of enduring it?	</danger>
			<dead>	I won't forget our memories together.	</dead>
			<dead>	Argh... It's because I ate too much!!	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm full now and have nothing else to do. How about snack time.	</stand>
			<stand>	KP! Hey! Get a hold of yourself! You can't just sleep here when you are full.	</stand>
			<connect>	You here? What is this menu?	</connect>
			<connect>	I've thought it over. I think you should rest today.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Oh- it's about time you leveled up. Congratulations.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Ugh... I can't get over your beauty, Beautiful Angel.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	I've always practiced summoning, but never succeeded.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Beat! Box! Booooooxxx! Beat! These are the only 2 words you need to know to beatbox.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I've always practiced summoning, but never succeeded.	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Beat! Box! Booooooxxx! Beat! These are the only 2 words you need to know to beatbox.	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Huk... Huk... I... I can't take it anymore.	</feeding>
			<feeding>	K... KP... do you plan to kill me?	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Alright! Run! Yes! That's it!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Argh... I'd like to share the food in my belly with you.	</danger>
			<danger>	You much have 9 lives.	</danger>
			<dead>	KP! I will never forget you. Ugh...	</dead>
			<dead>	Medic!! No medic around? Medic!!	</dead>
			<stand>	What are you dazing at? Let's work this off!!	</stand>
			<stand>	Ha ha ha ha! I'm the great Tikbalang!	</stand>
			<connect>	Welcome. Nice to meet you.	</connect>
			<connect>	Feels like its been a long time, no?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Love you! Beautiful Angel!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Beautiful Angel- You are even more beautiful today than yesterday!! He he-	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Summoning is difficult. Or maybe I used too little INT?	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Ugh... Did I eat too much? I feel like throwing up.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Summoning is difficult. Or maybe I used too little INT?	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Ugh... Did I eat too much? I feel like throwing up.	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</TIKBALANG>
	<GOLEM>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Thank you, i really appreciate it!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	You saved me!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I feel overflowing energy!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It's so, Korekore! Tasty!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	It's about time for you to feed me! I feel so powerless!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I feel so exhausted, can we take a break?!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hmmm.... that surprisingly strong attack!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	The most important thing in this world is a strong body!	</hunting>
			<danger>	I wonder, if this the right time to flee?!	</danger>
			<danger>	This fight is impossible!	</danger>
			<danger>	Hey, this gonna be dangerous if you don't recover your wound!	</danger>
			<danger>	You will die if you don't treat your wound!	</danger>
			<dead>	What a pity...	</dead>
			<dead>	You should know your limit...	</dead>
			<dead>	Good bye...	</dead>
			<stand>	Will you give me food?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey! that's some tasty stone over there!	</stand>
			<stand>	Sigh.... no edible stone around here	</stand>
			<stand>	Zeropi is not a stone, please be careful	</stand>
			<stand>	...Foooooooooodd......	</stand>
			<stand>	*pant* *pant*...Can you give me some stone?	</stand>
			<connect>	Did you come to give me food?	</connect>
			<connect>	Hoho, it's meal time!	</connect>
			<connect>	I'm glad you come, i feel reduced bloody circulation in my belly!	</connect>
			<connect>	You finally come!	</connect>
			<connect>	I've waiting you for a long time!	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! I hope i can be as strong as you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well done! you did it!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Impressive! Next is meal time~	</levelup>
			<levelup>	We've work so hard to level up, it's time to get some meal~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Look at my strong body!!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	There is powerful force that move my strong body!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Admit it! you admire my strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	This body, is a strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	My golem sense is tingling!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I feel powerful force near me!	</perfor_3>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	You saved me once again!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Best timing!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Now i can use my power!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey it's dinner time!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I feel so exhausted, can we take a break?!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hmmm.... that surprisingly strong attack!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	The most important thing in this world is a strong body!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Did you enjoy the thrill?	</danger>
			<danger>	Please be careful, who's gonna feed me if you died?	</danger>
			<danger>	Hang on! i will help you!	</danger>
			<danger>	How can you still be okay with that wounds?	</danger>
			<danger>	That look painful </danger>
			<dead>	Even though i help you, but you still dead...	</dead>
			<dead>	You should know your limit...	</dead>
			<dead>	What a dissapointing result.	</dead>
			<dead>	What? died again? </dead>
			<stand>	It's meals time~	</stand>
			<stand>	Sigh.... no edible stone around here	</stand>
			<stand>	Zeropi is not a stone, please be careful	</stand>
			<stand>	...Foooooooooodd......	</stand>
			<stand>	*pant* *pant*...Can you give me some stone?	</stand>
			<connect>	Come come! Fill this belly!	</connect>
			<connect>	Finally you come!	</connect>
			<connect>	I've waiting for you all day!	</connect>
			<connect>	How are you today?	</connect>
			<connect>	It's about time you feed me, what meal did you brought?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! I hope i can be as strong as you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well done! you did it!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Impressive! Next is meal time~	</levelup>
			<levelup>	We've work so hard to level up, it's time to get some meal~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Look at my strong body!!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	There is powerful force that move my strong body!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Admit it! you admire my strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	This body, is a strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	My golem sense is tingling!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I feel powerful force near me!	</perfor_3>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	My power is now restored!!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I feel so slim	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It has nice taste!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I feel so slim...again	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It's good...though not delicious	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Hey it's dinner time!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I feel so exhausted, can we take a break?!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hmmm.... that surprisingly strong attack!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	The most important thing in this world is a strong body!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Attack! attack! You feel that?!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Did you enjoy the thrill?	</danger>
			<danger>	Please be careful, who's gonna feed me if you died?	</danger>
			<danger>	Hang on! i will help you!	</danger>
			<danger>	How can you still be okay with that wounds?	</danger>
			<danger>	That look painful </danger>
			<dead>	Even though i help you, but you still dead...	</dead>
			<dead>	You should know your limit...	</dead>
			<dead>	What a dissapointing result.	</dead>
			<dead>	What? died again? </dead>
			<stand>	It's meals time~	</stand>
			<stand>	Sigh.... no edible stone around here	</stand>
			<stand>	Zeropi is not a stone, please be careful	</stand>
			<stand>	...Foooooooooodd......	</stand>
			<stand>	*pant* *pant*...Can you give me some stone?	</stand>
			<stand>	Did you know? Elunium has good taste! You should try it!	</stand>
			<connect>	Come come! Fill this belly!	</connect>
			<connect>	Finally you come!	</connect>
			<connect>	I've waiting for you all day!	</connect>
			<connect>	How are you today?	</connect>
			<connect>	It's about time you feed me, what meal did you brought?	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! I hope i can be as strong as you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well done! you did it!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Impressive! Next is meal time~	</levelup>
			<levelup>	We've work so hard to level up, it's time to get some meal~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Look at my strong body!!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	There is powerful force that move my strong body!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Admit it! you admire my strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	This body, is a strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	My golem sense is tingling!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I feel powerful force near me!	</perfor_3>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	I feel so great today!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Uuuuuuuo uuuuuo! Strong body is filled with magic now!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	It's fighting time!! Let's go!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	At last! my magic power is restored!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Burp! I feel so full!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Did you know having a strong body is important?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Nice hit!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hmmm.... that surprisingly strong attack!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	The most important thing in this world is a strong body!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Attack! attack! You feel that?!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Did you enjoy the thrill?	</danger>
			<danger>	Please be careful, who's gonna feed me if you died?	</danger>
			<danger>	Hang on! i will help you!	</danger>
			<danger>	Are you okay?	</danger>
			<dead>	Even though i help you, but you still dead...	</dead>
			<dead>	You should know your limit...	</dead>
			<dead>	What a dissapointing result.	</dead>
			<dead>	What? died again? </dead>
			<dead>	It's time to rematch! c'mon get up!	</dead>
			<stand>	It's good we spent time without moving~	</stand>
			<stand>	Can you guess, how many cousin do i have?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, can we fisit my cousin? His name is bradium.	</stand>
			<stand>	Last week my cousin, Lava, sent some tasty stone, will you try it?	</stand>
			<stand>	Maybe we should rest in here?	</stand>
			<connect>	Finally you come!	</connect>
			<connect>	I've waiting for you all day!	</connect>
			<connect>	Thank you for come, you must have miss me alot~	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! I hope i can be as strong as you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well done! you did it!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Impressive! Our next target is level 99!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice! Now we can protect each other~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Look at my strong body!!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	There is powerful force that move my strong body!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Admit it! you admire my strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	This body, is a strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	My golem sense is tingling!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I feel powerful force near me!	</perfor_3>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	I feel so great more than before!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Thank you! You can have the other stones~	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Feel so great!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	I'm okay. are you okay too? Good!	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Nice hit!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hmmm.... that surprisingly strong attack!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	The most important thing in this world is a strong body!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Attack! attack! You feel that?!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Did you enjoy the thrill?	</danger>
			<danger>	Please be careful, who's gonna feed me if you died?	</danger>
			<danger>	Hang on! i will help you!	</danger>
			<danger>	Are you okay?	</danger>
			<dead>	Even though i help you, but you still dead...	</dead>
			<dead>	You should know your limit...	</dead>
			<dead>	What a dissapointing result.	</dead>
			<dead>	What? died again? </dead>
			<dead>	It's time to rematch! c'mon get up!	</dead>
			<stand>	Can you guess, how many cousin do i have?	</stand>
			<stand>	Hey, can we fisit my cousin? His name is bradium.	</stand>
			<stand>	Last week my cousin, Lava, sent some tasty stone, will you try it?	</stand>
			<stand>	If you want to have strong body, you have to train hard! and eat stone~	</stand>
			<stand>	Maybe we should rest in here?	</stand>
			<connect>	Finally you come!	</connect>
			<connect>	I've waiting for you all day!	</connect>
			<connect>	Thank you for come, you must have miss me alot~	</connect>
			<levelup>	Congratulations! I hope i can be as strong as you.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Well done! you did it!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Impressive! Our next target is level 99!	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Nice! Now we can protect each other~	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	Look at my strong body!!!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	There is powerful force that move my strong body!	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Admit it! you admire my strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	This body, is a strong body!	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	My golem sense is tingling!	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	I feel powerful force near me!	</perfor_3>
		</so_full>
	</GOLEM>
	<scatleton>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Something which has been sleeping inside me finally is wakig up!	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Beelzebub	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Share your kills! Its only polite.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Poor unfortunate souls	</hunting>
			<danger>	What was that?!	</danger>
			<danger>	Oops Whats happening? I am falling unconscious	</danger>
			<dead>	Dont worry. No matter how hungry I am, I am not going to eat you.	</dead>
			<dead>	Lets go back together to my hometown	</dead>
			<stand>	No that guy started moving around	</stand>
			<stand>	Its so painful	</stand>
			<stand>	Cant you hear the screaming?	</stand>
			<connect>	I was thinking that becoming a demon was not such a bad idea.	</connect>
			<connect>	Again The time for darkness returns.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Haha	</levelup>
			<levelup>	If you want to survive get stronger	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	You seem disengaged, Well, Enjoy while you can.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive means continuous agony.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	The greed only destructs yourself	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Can you feel my power?.....	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Haha Its been a long time since my blood boiled like this</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Oh I feel dizzy What a new sensation.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!!! The chaos is coming!!!!!	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	You cannot appease my vanity like this	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Silly human	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Is this the best you can do?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	How boring	</hunting>
			<danger>	I can only go this far	</danger>
			<danger>	I am not hunting. I am being hunted	</danger>
			<dead>	Dont worry. No matter how hungry I am, I am not going to eat you.	</dead>
			<dead>	Lets go back together to my hometown	</dead>
			<stand>	This feeling of hunger is a proof that I am alive.	</stand>
			<stand>	Cant you hear the screaming?	</stand>
			<stand>	How boring	</stand>
			<connect>	Again The time for darkness returns.	</connect>
			<connect>	It was a short rest	</connect>
			<levelup>	If you want to survive get stronger	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Youre not strong enough.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	You seem disengaged Well Enjoy while you can.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive means continuous agony.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	The greed only destructs yourself	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Can you feel my power?.....	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Haha Its been a long time since my blood boiled like this	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Oh I feel dizzy What a new sensation.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!!! The chaos is coming!!!!!	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	At that time I thought nothing was worse than hunger </feeding>
			<feeding>	Heh It was a meaningless memory	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Great! Destroy it!!!! Thats what you actually are!!!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Hahahahahahahaha!!!! Hahahahahahahahaha!!!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	The fury makes your sword blunt	</danger>
			<danger>	I can only go this far	</danger>
			<dead>	Do you feel it? This is the sorrow and fury of those who have been killed by you.	</dead>
			<dead>	Do not be afraid of the darkness	</dead>
			<stand>	How boring	</stand>
			<stand>	Its been a long time since my last rest.	</stand>
			<stand>	Well If you want it so badly, I will give you an opportunity to serve me.	</stand>
			<connect>	Again The time for darkness returns.	</connect>
			<connect>	The festival of blood begins	</connect>
			<levelup>	Good. Struggle more and more	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Youre not strong enough.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	You seem disengaged Well Enjoy while you can.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive means continuous agony.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	The greed only destructs yourself	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Can you feel my power?.....	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Haha Its been a long time since my blood boiled like this	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Oh I feel dizzy What a new sensation.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!!! The chaos is coming!!!!!	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>
			<feeding>	Youd better stop it. You silly human	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Oh	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Looks like I dont have to be involved.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Great! Destroy it!!!! Thats what you actually are!!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	The fury makes your sword blunt	</danger>
			<danger>	You will collapse by the greed	</danger>
			<dead>	Hahahahahaha! The gate of hell is opening!	</dead>
			<dead>	Blah Blah Blah I have Thumbs, well what did your thumbs do for you now?	</dead>
			<stand>	How much longer are you going to hesitate!	</stand>
			<stand>	What a threatening wind	</stand>
			<stand>	Well If you want it so badly, I will give you an opportunity to serve me.	</stand>
			<connect>	The festival of blood begins	</connect>
			<connect>	Again The time for darkness returns.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Good. Struggle more and more	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Seems like you have grown up a little.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	You seem disengaged Well Enjoy while you can.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive means continuous agony.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	The greed only destructs yourself	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Can you feel my power?.....	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Haha Its been a long time since my blood boiled like this	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Oh I feel dizzy What a new sensation.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!!! The chaos is coming!!!!!	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	Youd better stop it. You silly human	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Are you trying to torture me this way? What a coward	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Looks like I dont have to be involved.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Thats noisy	</hunting>
			<danger>	Can you see the sign of death?.....	</danger>
			<danger>	This is from someone whos destined for death.	</danger>
			<dead>	Hahahahahaha! The gate of hell is opening!	</dead>
			<dead>	Do you feel it? This is the sorrow and fury of those who have been killed by you.	</dead>
			<stand>	What a threatening wind	</stand>
			<stand>	I can take you on at any time, kid	</stand>
			<stand>	Are you tired already?	</stand>
			<connect>	The festival of blood begins	</connect>
			<connect>	Again The time for darkness returns.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Good. Struggle more and more	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Seems like you have grown up a little.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	You seem disengaged Well Enjoy while you can.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive means continuous agony.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	The greed only destructs yourself	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	Can you feel my power?.....	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	Haha Its been a long time since my blood boiled like	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	Oh I feel dizzy What a new sensation.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!!! The chaos is coming!!!!!	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</scatleton>
	<skelion>
		<hungry>
			<feeding>	Delicious...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Chomp Chomp...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	I need to hunt in order to eat...	</hunting>
			<hunting>	The prey won't stand a chance...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Will I be the hunted instead of the hunter???	</danger>
			<danger>	Is there a graveyard around here?...	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't worry, no matter how hungry I get, I won't eat you.	</dead>
			<dead>	Together...lets go...home...	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm in pain...	</stand>
			<stand>	Ouch...	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you not hear...the screams?	</stand>
			<connect>	Took a short break...	</connect>
			<connect>	Again, the time of darkness is back.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Eh?...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	If you want to survive, be strong...	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	That one looks OK...You need to indulge yourself.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive is the continuation of suffering.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Greed destroys itself......	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I'm very powerful...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	...It's been a long time...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	This is a new feeling.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!! Chaos is approaching!!!	</perfor_s>
		</hungry>
		<bit_hungry>
			<feeding>	Nothing matters...I'm dead...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Stupid Normans...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Is this the best you can do?	</hunting>
			<hunting>	I'm bored...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Meh...	</danger>
			<danger>	Hunting, or not hunting...	</danger>
			<dead>	Don't worry, no matter how hungry I get, I won't eat you.	</dead>
			<dead>	Together...lets go...home...	</dead>
			<stand>	Stayin' alive? Stayin' alive?.	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you not hear...the screams?	</stand>
			<stand>	I'm bored...	</stand>
			<connect>	Again, the time of darkness is back.	</connect>
			<connect>	Took a short break...	</connect>
			<levelup>	If you want to survive, be strong...	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Still lacking.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	That one looks OK...You need to indulge yourself.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive is the continuation of suffering.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Greed destroys itself......	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I'm very powerful...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	...It's been a long time...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	This is a new feeling.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!! Chaos is approaching!!!	</perfor_s>
		</bit_hungry>
		<noting>
			<feeding>	Those days...I thought there was no fear and hunger...sad memories...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Heh...a futile memory comes to mind...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	Danger! Danger!	</hunting>
			<hunting>	That's it! Hahahahaha!!!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Fury never let the sword end...	</danger>
			<danger>	Here...	</danger>
			<dead>	The sorrow and anger...do you feel it?	</dead>
			<dead>	Don't be afraid of the dark...	</dead>
			<stand>	I'm bored...	</stand>
			<stand>	Resting...	</stand>
			<stand>	Ok, I will give you a chance.	</stand>
			<connect>	Again...the time of darkness is back.	</connect>
			<connect>	The bloody feast begins...	</connect>
			<levelup>	 oi o oO AAo||	</levelup>
			<levelup>	A IACIU.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	That one looks OK...You need to indulge yourself.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive is the continuation of suffering.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Greed destroys itself......	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I'm very powerful...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	...It's been a long time...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	This is a new feeling.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!! Chaos is approaching!!!	</perfor_s>
		</noting>
		<full>	
			<feeding>	All this food is making me sleepy...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Ugh...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	My body has left me.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	Danger! Danger!	</hunting>
			<danger>	Fury never let the sword end...	</danger>
			<danger>	The desire to break down...	</danger>
			<dead>	Back down to Hel, the door is open!	</dead>
			<dead>	The sorrow and anger...do you feel it?	</dead>
			<stand>	How long is it going to stay?	</stand>
			<stand>	Ominous winds blowing...	</stand>
			<stand>	Ok, I will give you a chance.	</stand>
			<connect>	The bloody feast begins...	</connect>
			<connect>	Again, the time of darkness is back.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Yes, even more.	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Growing up a little?	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	That one looks OK...You need to indulge yourself.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive is the continuation of suffering.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Greed destroys itself......	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I'm very powerful...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	...It's been a long time...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	This is a new feeling.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!! Chaos is approaching!!!	</perfor_s>
		</full>
		<so_full>
			<feeding>	All this food is making me sleepy...	</feeding>
			<feeding>	Trying to torture me in this way...	</feeding>
			<hunting>	My body has left me.	</hunting>
			<hunting>	It's noisy...	</hunting>
			<danger>	Looks like death...	</danger>
			<danger>	This is the end.	</danger>
			<dead>	Back down to Hel, the door is open!	</dead>
			<dead>	The sorrow and anger...do you feel it?	</dead>
			<stand>	Ominous winds blowing...	</stand>
			<stand>	Do you ever beg to be an opponent...	</stand>
			<stand>	Tired of it already?	</stand>
			<connect>	The bloody feast begins...	</connect>
			<connect>	Again, the time of darkness is back.	</connect>
			<levelup>	Growing up a little?	</levelup>
			<levelup>	Yes, even more.	</levelup>
			<perfor_1>	That one looks OK...You need to indulge yourself.	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_1>	Heh...	</perfor_1>
			<perfor_2>	Being alive is the continuation of suffering.	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_2>	Greed destroys itself......	</perfor_2>
			<perfor_3>	I'm very powerful...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_3>	...It's been a long time...	</perfor_3>
			<perfor_s>	This is a new feeling.	</perfor_s>
			<perfor_s>	Chaos!!! Chaos is approaching!!!	</perfor_s>
		</so_full>
	</skelion>
</monster_talk_table>